Hey guys
So another team move or I think I don't know we'll see how it goes
So I ordered a
Set of nail clippers, so we can all watch these reviews and see
You know I I got a decent
Aurora borealis lamp for six bucks the
Yeah
The most top working for it. Hi guys. Oh, yeah
Came from Teemo today. I just ordered this the other day. Hey Boston. How are you?
Boston's a member. Welcome Boston. Hey, Jamie
Yeah, so I got this from Teemo. It's actually from you know, the third-party seller. Hey, Yon. I
Took your wrench up
Back Barbara. Yeah, I got your back. Hold on. I want to see this. I have to go into my
to go into my
Sitting a little bit. Okay, so it's a little kit. Okay. It's a little nice guys. This was like five ten bucks. I don't know it was
Okay, so it's a little bit
Okay, look
Got a lot of stuff in it. It's cool. I like the colors red and black guys I have I have a
Male cleaners to my my heart's the light, right?
Got some clippers. I got you know, it's it doesn't feel like the most
Expensive you know, they feel kind of that some of them feel plastic. Yeah
but
Hi, hi guys. He on chat. Let me see. I'm gonna
How do you do this guys? Yeah, it's very nice. And so I got a little
This is just a little cleaner. So I just always scrape out my nails. They'll probably be better than they ever ever been in a while
And I guess so yeah, it takes it right out
Amazing sometimes we have problems for such a long time, and then it's like it's just it has a little simple fix
All right, so always look out for this best solution sometimes there's called hacks
Okay, I mean, it's like dinner. It's not like wow. I mean, it's like it's kind of getting and you really need to scrape up there
Isn't that oh, yeah, I think a lot of it up
the headaches are your headaches are
alright, alright, alright
at Brady, hold on
You know who my headsets are rocking
Okay, hold on
Crackling Amy crackling
I'm sorry, you can't see, hold on, okay, we're gonna move.
Testing, oh, how does that guy do that better?
Okay, probably because it was too close to my mouth.
So there we go, is that better?
Testing one, two, three, calling Will Robinson.
Hmm, how's your day guys?
And I got some rest today a
Little bit to eat
That's a start drinking a little bit yeah guys this is kind of taking up all the dirt, but it's like not super fast
And it's right by the right tool for this deal. So this is the one I'm using right now. So this is like
Wait, I mean, what is I mean, this is like this is a tiny spoon. I
mean, it's like
Guys, I mean, it's like it's like what it's like a hundred coax spoons or something. What is this one? Okay, so there's one of the
Okay, oh gosh. I got we got some good stuff though. I can clean out my other pipe too with some of the stuff
Okay, it's a little cool those guys. It was they know for six bucks a team who
Delivered, you know
The light to just it's like just cool cheap stuff. I would I would maybe take out
some of the more
Expensive stuff they have on there because maybe you're gonna get deal. I don't I got my
Hit phones or the battery. We can load some stage tonight. We can get all the energy cleared
I did kind of burn myself last night with a sage
Yeah, they all negative energy just collect and smoke and then go out the window be dispelled
Be dispelled turn to this then there any negative energy
being sent to me or
You have the kind hearted people in the chat
Okay, we have the power we do have the power to bless
So we have the power to bless where we are we have the power to the curse where we are to you I suppose right so
how about
We learn about blessings and you said conscious blessings when we enter we enter a place you know and
Throw our own homes and so far inhabitants and to everyone in our life
So
Noble are you?
Yeah, so we can invoke these blessings. Wow, here we go guys. Look at all the smoke
Sometimes you can see interesting stuff in the smoke if you look back. I don't know
Let me just see some
Hello, Vader. How are you?
The stage is really effective. I do think it's super effective
And I'm pulling out some of the negative energy
I know it's been probably used for thousands of years and has a very very distinctive and lovely smell
Hey, Jamie, or yeah, hey, Vader
This is a little sparky
Thank you, I want to get a demon out of
How do we do that in cards?
Well, I wouldn't say a card would do an exorcism.
I'd say the cards, you know, they can be used in conjunction with that.
I would say certainly perform a reading before you do any exorcism
or any other kind of magical working.
See what the energies are like and how things are likely to turn out.
See, just give that idea of a feel for the energy when you're about to do something like that.
Um, you know, I think I also think it's a very kind of this kind of judgment. So when we're like, oh, this person's demon possesses
it's like
Okay, maybe maybe even possessed. Maybe
They're possessive themselves. Maybe yeah, there's the ego is in total control of the onima, right?
and so
So when we say, oh, they're doing because that's you know, I think it's I think I'm not gonna ever go around my life and say
I oh, I rebuke you and then no call a woman something like Jezebel or something like that. Oh, and that's not that's not
That's not about like what I'm about, right?
It's like that some people will say oh, yeah, go do that go perform exorcism
Some people have tied people down into the beds and you know, there's horrible stories that Emily Rose case is based on a true story
Look into the true story of Emily Rose. It's just very sad stuff, you know, some of it might be
Some of it might be
You know mental illness, so it might be
Different drugs or some kind of poisoning or something like that
And it could be just the religious poisoning that religious mind control how it does drive some people nuts
You know, if you start believing in devils and angels and
Sometimes you'll take it
A little bit too literally working on salvation with fear and tremble. Yeah. Well, I also think that it's like
There's like perfect love and perfect trust, right?
And it's like, you know, we can fear God ultimately we should because he ultimately God is in control of everything, right?
but
Just it's like kind of like
Do your parents want to be loved or feared by maybe a little bit of both maybe like a little bit about okay
You'll behave yourself better if you're feared, but you know, I basically don't know you know that we're loving the benevolent forces, right?
I think that's similar to God
We love this so much that he gave us free will
So Ziggy what do you see what what where's my dick fix the
You need to take of the shit, okay? Always then hand out of people
Telling me I'm bothering you when I asked for it. Did you be flatter?
Okay, so there we go, that's okay. Oh, that's okay. That was the message that you Emily Rose wanted to send out
Yeah, the message is
um can I handle that um handle but they use those message uh Emily Rose would
want to just send out we handle that tell your friend Russ that's your friend
Russie's your friend isn't she I mean she's my friend too but you know she's
kind of new to the show I think she was hanging out with your group guys I'm
Her name is I
think
panel panel boots or something that in the chat
And I'll to say too much of me. I did doctor. I just
Yeah
Yeah, he's not on the please not on he's not on the blog list he's just
He might be or he or she they might be timed out
24 hours probably back a lot of people like are already time already time back in before they are
Asking about it. It's like, let's test it. You know, I used to
some two conclusions sometimes but
Me when people assume it just makes an ass out of you and me I
Can do it I can do it, but yeah, and see I said your dick pic is like five years ago. Okay
Well, you know, you look you look you look you look you look great. You look just look great, you know
What happened these last five years? You have a tough. You know, that's why I have what I had to its last five months
so imagine having
to mod it imagine being a mod and
Stens you a
Deepic I
Josh it every day. Oh
My gosh
The Kid-Pick?
Are you complaining about that?
Well, I don't even know. Is that a big issue, guys? Oh my gosh, there's...
You dick every day. I don't really have more dick pics than me.
Women aren't just like sending out pictures of boobs like willy nilly. It's like, you know
You gotta at least have a girl's gone wild t-shirt and you know
It's pity bucks or a hundred bucks or something. I don't know but that's the minimum
Okay
It's gonna send send it out to strangers on the internet
Fake photos
Ladies don't do it. Don't do it. I know we had I did have a problem
Oh, I issue somebody to you because then
Guys are sticking they do revenge porn and it's one sort of post
Pictures of somebody I know and we all we all know they're on the show
And Mike, okay
Maybe I'm just talking, or hold on, am I holding these?
I need to put these down, maybe,
because I think that maybe is the,
maybe is crackling.
This is Trixie.
Trixie.
Hi, hi.
So I had you have a couple of my drinks tonight.
You don't do your revenge for, I know,
it's not only is it illegal, but it's like, you know.
Just low it's like nobody really care. I mean it's like I don't think people really care except for the person that it's doing it
It's really it's really
Destroyed a lot of people even people have AI fake AI porn
and showing people and upsetting people with and people are
jumping to conclusions about it
So
There's always going to rest it and yeah, it's true, but okay well
Guys, you need to truce up again. Okay, I can't have my you know people fighting in my chat
See you uh
Who's that okay?
Oh deans, let me see. Oh, it's only personalized my phone
Okay, little themes, okay, I think I'll do see way
by the C. So it says, if I send you a pic, would you be mad?
Well, I would be mad, because I mean, I know you asked somebody else, but I mean, personally,
I would be mad. I would be, you know, I would say, finally he sent it, you know, I've been waiting
for this picture. I would say, a moment like this, some people wait a lifetime for a picture like this.
Some people last forever for that one special kiss. Oh
I'm sorry for my own life. Oh my gosh
Yeah, no one's no anyone's dick. I mean dick sir
Wieners are kind of weird to like especially the women. I mean women kind of like laugh at them guys. I think they look cool, but I
Mean I think they look pretty cool, but it's like
Sometimes they look funny. It depends. They're common all shapes inside. They're like balloon animals, right?
Just like the pictures of a raging demon and Sam and we've all seen lately. Those are not I don't think those are real pictures, though
You love the channel, thank you Phyllis. Thank you so much. I appreciate you. I
Love you
Okay, I love you guys so much. Let me see system controls vibration and
This phone has more settings than the Hall of 13.
Okay, let's see.
Hey, fellas, thank you guys.
Yeah, guys, the channel is also doing well.
I have a membership.
I would love you guys to join the membership.
It's so cool.
I love seeing the names in the chat.
I will see you easier too.
Who's the member in the chat?
Anybody?
Not we get to the green it's Barbara Barbara's a member
Barbara and I think Barbara's the only one in the chat right now, but we do have almost over 70
So hi shout out to the members. I always try to give members a shout out
No time
I used to hear that a Charles Manson wrote that song but he turned out you wrote some other other Beach Boys song or something
Yeah
Yeah do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
Turn it turn this magic really go full blast, right? I can't play it back and sing it
Okay, I don't know
I'm not I'm not sure the other words even though I'm sorry
They were a
Subpar boy band. Yeah, but they were on the first and also they were you know, I think they're probably one of the first
You know, there's a place called a taba stock Institute in London. It's in England. It's have a stock England and
It is where you know, there's a think tank a think tank where you know
A lot of ideas are thrown around and maybe instituted in some
The mainstream, right? I can't say too much about it
but
You know, you can look into it a lot of the world as we know it today is
Bake this is that's a manufacturing thing, you know, kind of
Programmed controlled but my control I don't know how to put it, you know, it's like that, you know
There's something going on right look there's really cool books available on Amazon for free guys
You can go to Amazon and try to search for like it's a big search for zero like dirt for like zero
Um, I think they're called zero because there's a lot of ones that are free. They'll say the whole section
I think of the ebooks that are free. I got a thousand of them on my
My apps, but who is tonight?
Maybe it was wrong. It's from the name and it's saying bad things we go
What are we gonna do guys, okay, so I
Do have thousands of books and I can't read cool stuff, you know
Looking for something that kind of be enjoyed by the whole chat, right?
Okay
Lot of self-hybrid a lot of self-help book a lot of the cults books a lot of
Tarot
Okay, maybe this will I'll find me a fine one that was just resonate somehow you see
And bear with me guys are thousands of them
Okay, we can look at the origin of names, words, everything in between.
What is bothersome? Definitely you're going to have to gather more rock songs.
Yeah, maybe in my other channel.
Okay, so this is about, this is called the origin of names, words, and everything in between.
Okay, so it's just countries. Okay, so if you're reading this on a boat, a plane, a moon, hot air balloon, extra stretchable planet, or literally on the sun, are you a bit warm there by chance?
Then you're most likely reading this in a country. Okay, so this is kind of basic. Let's see, so Russia was named after the Rus people of Rus, you know, the Rus were a tribe of Vikings who were thought to have come from Sweden in the 9th century.
I'm gonna call him in with Russia. Okay, it's not that the name comes from the old Norse term roads
meaning
The men who row as rowing with the main way that rods and all the Vikings traverse the waters around them
Well, you know, I think I think I think of Andrew. I think of the roux plant. I think of the druids. I don't know
Maybe that's just me
Australia is Australia is the country of the aboriginals of people who have their own amazing mythology
Okay
Yet the name what we know the country by today has its roots in Greek mythology the group
We've had a god for everything Dionysus with the Greek god of wine
Priests with the god of the vegetable garden, but the Greek god
We are interested today is noctis or no no toast the Greek god of the southern wind
Romans adopted
the Greek mythology for themselves, but one thing they did change was the names of the gods.
Zeus became Jupiter, Aries became Mars, Notius' name was changed to Oster by the Romans.
With the name of the god in the southern wind being Oster, Oster, the name became in
term for south and southern in Latin, and Latin is a language with a huge influence on the English
language. So do you guys know that Australia came from Oster after the god of the wind? Okay.
Well, isn't that interesting? Okay, isn't that fascinating? Okay
So it goes through a lot of these names, you know the Isle of Man, which I'm what is Japan named after?
I know Japan has nothing to say about Nippon or something like that
The Japan's famous nickname is Land of the Rising Sun
The nickname also shines some light see what I did there on the country's actual name too
The name is this route all the way to Chinese Jin Poon which translates to the sunrise Jin Poon Japan
The Chinese referred to Japan by this name due to when the Japan is in relation to China
So pan is east of China and of course is from the east that the Sun rises
The names of Japan are often associated with China as ancient China had a huge influence on the early civilizations of Japan
Okay
Is that interesting I don't know I'm just
You know, we want to have a request for a you know, I can tell you about Chicago, Liverpool, Sydney, Budapest
And a lot of other places I can have by the Eiffel Tower, I can say Statue of Liberty
Yeah, there's just a lot of information out there. Some of us interesting Taj Mahal kind of interesting a lot of fascinating
Stories, you know the gorilla where that came from
Gorilla was thought to be a tribe of hairy women or even just long-haired black women
That's from Hannibal, right? I don't I mean that's just kind of
Fensa fensives
Everybody, okay, let me see
giraffe
There's actually something called a bandicoot the bandicoot
Pigeon bald eagle the puffin who's not a puffin puffins for sale of the toughens. Okay, bullshit canaries my grandma used to look canaries
First paradise you have to look up with those some time. Okay. I'm just sharing some of you. You're so trivia. How's that?
Hey, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I
Don't not forget people kind of zone out when I read some time. I thought I had an interesting voice
Yes, not okay, let me see
Happens for sale
Happens
Happens happens for sale three little birds happens for sale
Happens that's from you know where that's from guys get who can guess where that song is from
Called happens for sale very famous movie
My god, my it looks so monstrous with this light
Anybody know
Happens for Sam
happens
Happens up. It's a sharp. It's a sharp little very poppins. You got it. You got the prize. You got it Mary Poppins good for you
Yep, you can also there's a movie called mr. Banks guys you can check out
It's a Disney movie. It's like, you know, it's like one of those like live-action ones. It's all about how
They made that movie and like how hard it was to get made because the author was just a pain in the butt to Disney, right?
She didn't like the animation. He didn't like
It was not she didn't take a thing this story seriously. Oh, this works. Okay, this works good right here, so
She didn't like it, but can you imagine you know how classic Murray Poppins is and the whole the freaking author of the whole book
Do you like the movie? I mean that is not an endorsement, but it was a fabulous movie. I think
Disney's gonna be very very mass, you know, it's all about the
His survey as many people as you can with the
You see illusions basically entertainment. Okay. Well, I mean
Pretty good tools are pretty good grim reaper network. What's that?
Is that work? Hold on. Ziggy. Uh-oh. Joe's there in the chat. He's gonna start trouble. Joe, you're starting trouble.
I'm gonna post the link. Let's do it. What is the Grim Reaper Network? Is that what is that?
There's IP2. That's what you got. It wouldn't nominate me for. I'm on the way out probably. What the hell? Come on.
Grim Reaper. I just call him Grim. I call him Grim.
It acts like it's the end of the world, which I mean, it's never is for him. It's usually it's for everyone else, but
I guess not easy seeing everybody go
Okay. Oh, here I am. Hey, look I yeah, okay myself there lights are on
Hi guys to watch. Oh, well to watch how many lights do I have? Hey, I was wanting to watch it home
I have six lights and now I have seven. Okay
Plus the link. Oh, hold on that. There is room. Oh, hi room rooper. I didn't know you're actual person. Everyone calls you grim. Okay
Again or grim or I don't know
Okay, everyone calls me Psyche or Psyche, you know, so I understand because some of you will get the
IPT was done
We're literally all P community out. Hey, you know what? I found somebody I really like
I mean, I've seen him before but I kind of like think he's cute now. His name is
Danger ranger. I don't know who you know that is
You're from across the pond. Hello. Hello, Gavna
Hello, my e-my e-
Blimey day. I'm sorry. I don't know the language that well. You can't download this but it's okay. I
Think the discord link guys if you are able to join it and he wants you I do have a discord
You can or you can just know contact me there
There you go
Yeah, well, we're just talking about Mary Poppins.
And so, you know, I do love, you know,
I have some friends who are Scousers
and I have my brother-in-law from Manchester,
pick up Benny and go to Danger's RV together, yellow.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I like Danger, Danger Ranger.
I think he's really cute.
Oh, look who's here.
Guys, I just heard some I just heard some sirens
It's the son of police
It's the son of me inside key and
Yeah
So psycharone is between me fucking you in the ass. I'm gonna guide you to this so
OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK
it is
Oh my god, I can't believe you came up your mother fucker has
What do you expect me to do with Alex after such a wonderful request?
Oh, I love you
Jesus, you know much you guys who's hurt me, bro. I'm still trying to heal from that shake grim
But you wouldn't mellows
Nothing to do with me
Yeah, it did because you were up there like I'm a friend. I'm grim
And then I heard you I heard you in the background. Oh, what is that he says the work is this I see
Hyperbore and what does it say with what networking or what network is this you're in on the weed. I can't really see it. It says the
Hey, okay, hold on. I
Don't know what did they say network? Is this something in a network?
Okay, okay
I get it. It's a little small. It's a little small. It's a little hard to see, but yeah, I see it now.
Okay.
You gotta check out of mellows. What is it?
Sike, Sike, if I can get a word in it would be great, but I come in peace, I don't come
in here to come here to start any wars or bring any crap to you whatsoever, Easy recommended
me to come across, I came across when his channel
closed down a couple of days ago i've listened in i like what you do i like a lot of the stuff
um i don't mind banter banter is okay don't have a problem with that uh i don't attack anybody
contrary to uh what alex may or may not think i never said you attacked anyone i don't
that's all I think of
that's all I care about
the BBA that was in Grimm
the double seven band boys
I was wanted
remember that
let's agree to disagree
this is the Tower Show
this is a psych show
I don't want to bring any personal grief into it
it's nothing to do with anybody
I came up here
And that's the reason why you know I don't hide from anybody
Thank you for coming up. I appreciate it. I love people come on the panel. It's amazing in our site
You just open a doorway to a whole different world because Grim Reaper
Is in London right there on the across the ocean from us?
And this is a whole new world and his friends are like our youtubers in England with a hundred case subscribers
Bear brain audit
eyes on the audit these people like um
Geniuses they they can all I don't know how to describe it, but you just
Open the doorway
into the next chapter so grimoire
You know
You don't talk about
He's trying to
I come in peace. I don't come here to cause any disruption. What? Yeah, they're so cool and they can help you when you help them like
the greenery the greenery
Like the computer shit like um
Green reaper and mellows. They're like a graphic designers. I don't know what they are
But they used to be on TV P and will make cartoons for them
Like, you know how the DJ lecture like you and me in the bushes
They will make better ones better than the one of you would say man like the fucking remember that bullshit better than that
Yeah, um as I was saying, um
The network is a network of people across the globe all with one aim, and that is to ensure
It's just to me it's it's a group basically of
Like-minded people who want one thing and that is protect our rights. That's it and the bill of rights over in this
I I love that. I love that. That's it
We don't have a Bill of Rights. We don't have a Constitution as such. What we have in the UK
is permissions which have been given to us. You have rights. We have permissions. Cops have
duties. Simple as that. I stand up for the Bill of Rights because I believe that it's the Bill of
And people will argue and people will turn around and say you shouldn't agree with First Amendment or the two's etc.
I don't agree with everything, I'll rephrase that, I don't agree with the way that it's all done
because there's some good ones and there's some that just go out for clips of use in my opinion.
You know, whereas I believed it, you know, everyone should stand up for what they believe in and what they're right
So I've been a long time. No, see they hear you. Yeah. Yeah, I'm here. Okay. There you hi
Hello, yeah, no, I agree. I agree with what he's saying. Well, yeah, I mean I do too and it's like so nice to have you know
It's like it's even like, you know, even
You know, he's a citizen of the UK and still he appreciate he can appreciate these rights
Because you know, it's it's it's in my opinion, it's a morality thing. Yeah, right
But if they don't have it, you know everywhere they mean they don't they don't have the bill of rights
They have it here. They don't have it very many other places. You know, I think there's
And I was like a lot of the work is for what to do. We're actually what he's trying to say is that the Bill of Rights was at the window and now
Grimm I'm talking about
And just read everybody like they are you because they are
Everybody's going through a difficult life. You don't know what the person next to you is going to
What does that mean? A difficult life?
Just treat everybody like they are you
You understand?
When you meet anyone on earth and encounter somebody just pretend they're you and treat them like you want to be treated
The golden rule because they are you
Right. Yeah, I mean that was like yeah, like he said the golden rule. Yeah, like that's what I did
But like what's your problem?
Can I just correct the miscommunication here? The Bill of Rights in America, every American
and every legal visitor to your country is public. Legal, by the way, he's, yep, okay.
anywhere in the US. When I went over to the US and visited the US 18 months or so ago I had all
the Bill of Rights except for two. One I couldn't vote and two I couldn't have a gun but all the
Now, there's no other country anywhere that gives you that protection and that's the reason
or one of the reasons why I believe that the Bill of Rights should never be interfered
with by any government, state or even town council with all the ordinances.
Anything.
Right.
Anything. No, no one. It's not even not even state and not state federal. I mean
Supreme Court rules, right?
Well, that that right at the Bill of Rights, and if it's you know, there are some decisions that they make that I think is a little bit wrong
However, you seem you seem knowledgeable about the US. Are you?
Yes
I am because I think it was just to warn you. He's like a fucking
no fish and says from hell. He knows everything. This is a very knowledgeable man.
So don't go down that route. Oh, no, I am. I want to go down the route. That's
Oh, no, go ahead. Go ahead. What happens? Perfect. Perfect.
Oh, no, no. Do you not think it's funny? I'm going to actually sum it up so it's not a long story.
But do you not think it's funny with the Confederacy being Democrats? And now it's opposite.
Well, that's because that's because the meaning of the parties have really changed. You know, they're right. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah
Yeah, I mean, but that's that sometimes parties evolve and but they're actually just
Dude, I was in the exact same thing
Well, I thought that was I thought that was weird, you know, you have pink hair people and the Confederates would have been like
Probably rolling in their graves
Same thing. They're under a pro was running pink with all the you know, red red and white and the flags and stuff like that
Yeah, what is it that rainbow thing? Yeah. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, I don't agree that anyone should be allowed to get away with
Defacing the I was just gonna jump and now you guys are done. Okay. Okay guys. Am I gonna get it? Am I in trouble now for wearing that speedo?
Guys, it was it was
Yes, yes you are. You disgraced the American flag.
Oh, I did not. I did not. I did not.
Yes, you did. What would Trump think about that?
Think about that, homeboy.
If we send that video to Trump,
you will be in fucking what time will be right now, bro.
Alex. Alex. Alex.
It's not that calm down. Okay. I don't want you to be in the stuff at least get boxers, you know
But it's true. Don't ask me bro. It's true. If Trump sees that
Alex has not an active prison, and I'm not even sure about what's on my fever. Hey guys, let's not talk about these things
I've there's a great
Fucking and a full player
Alex why are you first of all? You're screaming at me. I mean, it's like so loud. It's like
Then you're yelling stuff I say let's not talk about these that you're taking things
I don't want to talk about okay, so Alex slow your roll. Mr.
Okay, can can you play glycerine by?
No, I can't play guys guys you can you can always you know, and you know
You can play songs or
I can't play songs on my channel.
Well, I can everybody else play songs, but you can't.
Because I'm monetized as long as they're copyright. They can lead to strikes. They can lead to like lose your money
This is my favorite song. That's a good song play. Okay. No, no
Yo, come on you gotta play psych fuck that you get
Sorry, Alex. Alex, don't tell me what to do. Alex, don't tell me what to do.
No, he was being nice. He was being nice.
He's demanding I've been playing a song that I told him.
No, I mean, don't tell me. I don't want to talk about his topic.
No, no, he's doing it, but he's sitting in a green room for just a few minutes.
I know what I'm doing. It's like, you know...
You're leaving a song.
I know it.
Listen
I was in 90s. I was in 90s. No, and you guys can't even do it right you get
The let the days go by.
I never alone. I'm alone all the time. Oh, that's a sad, that's a sad lyric. Yeah.
Sing it! Sing it!
I never alone. I'm alone all the time.
No, you don't do it that way. You do it like you're...
No, okay, okay. You're my music coach, okay?
Okay, I mean, I'm not gonna prove it.
Yeah, stop.
Sing it.
Can you explain him that, please?
God, I'm just playing player.
You're you're the one talking. I'm not no they said that I didn't say that was not good river did not ask me to
I'm never alone. I'm alone all the time
Okay, stop is yours. You're making me stop. Stop singing that song. They're making me sad. Yes. It'd be sad
Yeah, you're making me sad now. My fingers are numb. So it's slowing typing. Yeah. Oh, I'm sorry. Me either
type. Yeah
Yeah
Hey, come on get give us a song. Come on. Come on
Michael your boat is sure hallelujah. I'm singing that one. I'm sorry that comes to mind
Okay, swing the low
I mean, at this point, we might as well hear Chubby Checker.
I don't know Chubby, I don't know Chubby Checker, I don't know any of his songs.
Do the twist!
Yeah, yeah, do the twist!
It's a twist, is it a twist?
Yeah, yeah!
By Dingaling.
By Dingaling, it's a twist.
Does he also sing?
You must be playing with your own dingaling.
That's all I'll say.
Oh my god.
Well, aren't we all, aren't we all, aren't we all right?
I can't sing that one, so.
That's only allegedly.
Very allegedly.
Here we have Amanda.
Hello.
Hi honey.
How are you?
Oh my god.
That's female.
Thank god.
Hello.
I just heard somebody that sounds it's just like Gotti on a beat his channel and he was you know
Gotti was just on my fucking telephone and he was acting like he wasn't on my door
It's weird. It's like my gosh Gotti. Why are you got his play pranks again? God is known
The uh, prolific Frank's got he's playing pranks again. Yeah. Oh my gosh. He's a boy though. I love it
I'm like, okay. All right. I'd know
It's him and be didn't know it's him. I can tell it's him and he was like, he's like, hey, where's mr.
No, no, no, you don't get it. You don't get it. No, he actually called my phone
Okay, and he was acting like he was like through at&t. Well, I don't have at&t
Okay, well, okay
How long did he fool you for?
Because usually, he's just fooling you for a minute.
Yeah, no, correct, okay.
Okay, I don't know, okay, I can be sad as well.
Yeah, one time he left my panel and he had to scream
and I was seriously concerned that he had fallen
out the window, but I think he was just,
he played the sound effect or something.
The other days go by.
Okay. How do we do it? I can't
tonight. We're having a great
night. Um yeah, we have uh
Manda and um um the Grim Reaper
here. Hey, wonderful. Wonderful
guys. You know, I don't know
how big I think he dropped off.
I think his uh his uh his voice
knocked him off the show. I'm
not sure. Yeah, hopefully my
phone works again. Um that
Me and bird had to go back to the vet today. Oh
How's kitty cat? Well, I said birds my dog dog. Yeah
It's okay, honey. I do have a cat his name is her name is Thumper
Here, I'll show you a picture of Thumper. Let me find it
How do I change this let's see here
Baby, I don't like Vinnie talking shit
venissere un bel reneggi.
Immaginarmente!
Alex everyone was saying that they were saying that on beat us. Yeah, there's no why would they say that? Why would they judge?
Let me think
Come on grimm
Why would they say that grimmie? You remember you said the you remember you said the 40 diamond that night?
I'm trying to understand why I was put backstage. I don't get it
Because when people annoy me I can't
Just kick your ass backstage for a minute if I want to.
So I was mulling, I mulled the bad stuff.
I told you, I didn't know what I was saying.
And
The song is making me too sad and you're in your
Wining about being from backstage because you know what if you're asking why would I say if you're obviously not backstage?
That means you're back on stage and so stop living in the past
By the way, there is an account called Princess Lane in the past.
Well, you don't hear that. It's okay. It's a bear, okay?
You don't have to understand everything.
You're the mastermind.
UJT and God. Why?
Why, Ziggy?
Why are you on your own show? You can run your show. You're so you want to know? I am trying
Understand
Puzzle it's a mystery some issues. I'm maybe I'll figure it
Okay, stop whining okay, no whining
you are you're on this show I don't want to hear you but what about how you're not on this show you got to keep coming
we're having that crazy spunky girl
spunky me though that's what I'm saying
he's so funny with a chubby cheese
because I can and that's why I did because I have the ability to
that was it because you can't because you have power okay
yeah by the way have a theory
burdo burdo pink burdo is a floaty diamond
Oh
Oh, hey, it's peak hours. There's all feet
Man and burdo is a transgender, I believe but I don't
Oh my god
The bird fly weird like whatever it's mixed or whatever here here man
Oh exactly no bird flies that way only one bird
my sideways will have a wing hanging off and a fucking dick hanging out you know what i'm saying
you can't duplicate that bird you know my boy gets it that's only one bird boy that's flono
I don't know about that, I don't understand what he's saying there
No, it was scary more than Florida flying away with a cock and half a wing
is that nobody gets it but him
That's more scary
Well, no, yeah, we'll let it out
I don't know. Let's let's let's
Oh
We're gonna have to learn Morse code to stay on these panels because anything you say
So we're gonna have to come over some secret language or something
Talk on your talk on your own show Alex don't come on my show screaming over
Can I ask him now, is Alex, does Alex have it?
Can you breathe for me? No, I can't I can't the see I cannot can you put can you show I can't no
I can't are if you I refuse to I can't I know I'm not going he's like I'm he's not gonna be meant
Next minute not for the next one minute. No, he's on
Yes, oh you're welcome
Yeah, uh, sometimes you can't have a conversation, uh, without problems, you know, uh, just
the way things are.
I mean, I would say you got a minute to speak.
Yeah, yeah, I appreciate it, but you talked about, you were trying to explain earlier
something that you didn't want to talk about UK and I totally agree with you.
I know.
Politics and they know he's he's talking about controversial. So I already I already mentioned tabs
Why do you get mad about it? I'm not mad. I'm totally calm right now, but I've been or let me from getting mad
I have to like just remove my presence
Bear with me. Well, I read my own show. Just bear with me while I
Yeah, thank you. Thank you. Thank you. That's the magic word. It's my show. So that's why that's why I put people backstage and you know
They have make rules and it's my show. You're welcome. I'll run the show, okay?
You're gonna miss one minute.
It's all time, you know, it's like, I just wish that you would play, I wish that honestly
that you would play that, that wish song.
Okay, if you say, if you say it one more time, I'm going to ask you to go for the night
because now you're really annoying.
I've already said that several times and explained why not, you keep bringing it up, stop bringing
it up.
If you don't want to play it, then I'm going to smoke my cigar and I'll be fine.
I just see that, just smoke your cigar and just sit there and just chat, or if you want to listen to that song, I think it's for free.
Can you be nice to me and everybody, JT and everybody?
No, I can't I have I have to be very a very cool
Why is JT
Here's the leader right of this to be called I don't I mean
They always suck his dick give JT a ranch JT when he just said I just almost cringed like I just
Have some like brainpower we
Gt shut up. I will kick this asshole right now
And it's like not you're yelling to do why are you?
Okay
We don't need you, you know, being the, you know, you to please Alex, you know, you don't have to be here.
I don't, I don't, I don't do that.
I said Alex, I didn't say Ziggy, Ziggy, you're the whole other thing where it's like, you know,
you just have to learn to be happy, you know, being part of the chat, you know, it's like...
Oh, yeah, I'm I'm very happy to be a part of the chat and I'm
You sound you sound you sound miserable. You sound very you very sound very sad. And I say, I'm sorry. I can't make you smile
You know, I'd love to like, you know, oh, no, no, you make you make me smile and that's what I'm saying
Oh
That that, you know jt is uh, really
Wow jt
Well, is this the same saggy from earlier and all day long
Because they sound like some depressed asshole like JT like what is going on right now, bro?
Who is the SIGI?
Is this even the real SIGI because this is not the SIGI I've heard for the past three days
This is a completely different person. Unless you're crashing from a drug major week
accusing everybody like flurry diamond is burdo and JT is you know
It's too confused again, it gets too confusing and then it's like that they make sense anymore and then I'm in Alice in Wonderland all over you
I just got out of that room
That's a great moment
My favorite part is the little door
She falls through the thing the rabbit hole and then she used to click and she gets real big
Then she has to drink to get small
And then she runs and funds and the imaginary cat and
She starts crying and then her tears turn to the other she's so big
Wait, wait isn't JT the one that came around and he was like hey, I found you
Let's see who this other guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy got a guy
Enjoying the join the show at least it's been a content and I'm not there's a bad person
Now you're in court and you're fucked
He didn't gonna spend like 10 decades and Joe by the way, he's fucked. It's the same thing here
You think we're not watching and listening and now you're here. Now you're in court, brother
I
Right JT said it was referring to this spin Alice in Wonderland. I'm just wondering how many rabbit holes do you go down?
I thought it was for me
Yeah, look at me a lot of them because it's like, you know
Can you do me a favor really quick? No, okay?
Stop asking me for favors. Okay. Stop asking me for favors. Okay. I'm gonna sit here with groom groom right now. Okay
Ziggy and Alex you guys are sufferable guys guys. It's not fun. It's not fun with you screaming at me
I mean, he's whining. It's a good cop back. Keep a cop, but they're both bad
It's just like there's both bad cops. You can't even reason with them
guys
You're ruining the vibes for that. Okay, now it's
Staying horrible names again. Yeah
Guys stop it. You have to sit backstage. You can make out backstage. I'm gonna talk to grimmer now man to man
The adults are talking. Okay, you can sit at the kids table, okay?
Yeah, so Amanda are you happy man, I think I got
Amanda I think I think I try to fix things for everybody, you know, I don't think people being timed out. I'm trying my best
Run run the panel and stuff like that. But guys stop it's not asking that's up
Demanding stuff out of me. I don't know. I don't know guys. It's not pleasant. Okay
Demand in the chat and then the mods will can address the mods might address you before I do if you're started demanding
I do something
You know, nobody really likes to be told what to do, right? So as long as I have freedom to do it
I want to do I'm gonna exercise that freedom
Yeah, so what what is there anything you want to ask me? Sorry, I mean I want to ask you. Well, let's see
No, it's very very interesting. Yeah, it sounds like you know, so what we're about to the UK or you're from?
I've actually moved to South Wales now. I was in Manchester, but I moved to South Wales and I'm enjoying it.
It's nice and quiet where I am. I live in the valleys, but it's nice and...
The scenery is nice. I've even started to talk well
A little bit
The sheep and the well sheep. Yeah
I I am like, uh, you know, I've done my ancestry. You know, we know we never know how accurate these those tests are but you know
I do have a large, uh large wells large
um
uk a large, um
of scottish and irish and german swedish
the majority of ancestors in the us can be linked back to europe because of what happened many many
years ago long before i was born or you or anybody else but you know we're not answerable for what
And I agree I agree I agree with you, but you know, I guess they can have there be a lot of the
People that disagree especially but there's there's even in California, which the state that never had had a like legalized slavery
Even California their seat their reparations are being sought for every single
I mean, it's like I think it's a little overkill
What's like, you know, it's it is hundreds of years later and a different you know in a state that had never existed it
But I know
They say that you should learn from your own history. I agree
but I also think that people should recognize mistakes that have been made in the past.
You know, Vinnie, I can't help the whistle, mate. Honest.
Right.
Well, yeah
It's like you turn around so I'm not talking to you because
Your great ancestor was related to such and such to such and such and they did this
Oh, yeah, what the hell?
Anybody you know even though I have the
You know, I have friends with people that people don't like some friends of theirs and it's like it's like some huge
some huge issue and it's like and then
They think because that their friend is has some kind of bad reputation and it's like everyone has
I've ever attached them as a bad reputation. I think we should just judge people on you know on how they treat us and you know
Feeling like how we want to be treated everyone should be respectful and nice and kind kind of people
And then we can get along a lot better, but people are always looking out for themselves and trying to be selfish and
Everyone wants to be number one. I get it
That's part of the problem. Unfortunately. Um, I will say one thing if I will respect everybody
While they're respecting me
I got you enough James Bond comment down. He sounds like James Bond
No, no, Ziggy so your mom's birthday is coming up. How did she know my mom's birthday my mom's birthday is today
Cuz you sound like you're 90, so I'll do this to pitch 200. I can't wait to
Stop screaming out first of all and second of all is written. Don't ask it my people
Why are you screaming Alex Alex don't scream
Thank you
My mother is 56 and she watches psyche
Oh, she does that's very sweet. Hi mom. Hi. How are you?
I call
Yeah, she's a mamba. She told me, huh? She told me. All right. I won't yell. I won't yell. How old is the old you are?
You're yelling. Hold on
I'm I'm 39. She had me whenever she was 16. How old is the old bitch, bro?
Second question, 90 years
The fuck's wrong? She said number
What is it? How old is she?
I didn't hear it. Say it again. I already said. I already so I didn't hear it. What is it? You're crazy, man
You're insane you're insane you're insane
The chance
Hey, could you be shouting while he was like, yeah, what is this? What is this? I
Don't know when you when you figured out. Let me know okay come back later
I don't need people telling me what is I mean, it's like please it's just the show
I don't know what it but he think it is the people talking on the show. It's the same
usually
So yeah, thank you when you does it abracadabra. I asked how old your mom is she went crazy
Well, I mean, it's none of your business Alice, but it's like I mean, but still I don't know
He's very condescending to her though. Oh, well
Whatever he just said
He's like, oh well
I just want to say hi to BK, he was saying it's a birthday, it's a birthday, it's a birthday.
Okay, Alex, Alex, please, I just want to say hi to BK, no one BK like him and a man doing a few others.
Christine for a very long time.
Thank you, what is this?
I just want to say hi to them.
I don't know
Daddy they're annoying me guys. They're annoying me
Dude, you know hey my mom knows Gotti to Gotti she said she loves you
Yeah, well, he's very lovable. She's very lovable, but oh, he's
You guys she watches you guys
awesome
Wow, who's watching move?
You're in my mom watches
What your mom watches way?
She's watching you good shit host on my mom watches what yeah
You're special. You're special. You're one of those special humans
Yeah, yeah, yeah, we grew up in
Know you are a circus freak you have small hands and it's not like cabbage, bro
Cabbage
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't
I can't I can't it's like it's like it's like two as they have a rope in my brain
And it's like and then I think a whining on one side and then that's screaming on the other and it's like
It's like I feel like
Stereo
I'm wearing I'm wearing loud headphones out. I think he's he's on
Louder than I've ever been put my microphone. I mean, I I mean no it goes up to 200, but it's up to 200
And he needs to scream at the top of his lungs.
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know.
Everyone, everyone, the upset goes, it's all calm down.
What you will find, certainly if you haven't seen it already, is
certain people will latch onto one thing and will then constantly wind somebody else up.
And that means that you can't have a conversation because they jump in.
And when you try to say something, you have to try and overshadow to be heard.
But, I mean, that's not good.
No, it's not good. It's a very bad way to communicate or getting a point across really and it's like nothing
It's all I really I do like to solve like you know solve things when it comes down to it
Do you wear tarot readings by the way? Yes, I do if you'd be interested in one
I can do one for you right now. I am I am interested but I haven't got time at the moment
I've got to get ready for work because we're five hours at least in front of you. So
I do tune in every now and again when you're live and certainly when I'm working if you're live,
I'll listen in. I might even get a chance to put a little comment in the chat every now and again.
I've I've listened to your shows and I've come to you know some of them are really
interesting some of them was like shouting matches but you can't necessarily always
control that you can only do what you can do and that put them in time out for a little
while but then when they come back they just carry on the way it is but that's
two people agreeing when there's stupid arguments going on or someone's calling somebody just
because they've got a voice which is louder than anybody else's, you know, it's just the
way it is.
I'm not going to mention any names because it's not fair on you.
We all can imagine and instead of, you know, everyone has experiences, you know, those
Spell it all out for a studio. Okay, here we go. Alex, are you here?
I'd never die on you
Thank you
He sounds like a little fucking decrepit old man.
I think I'm crazy.
Why is he saying that?
So he bought a voice box and I was like, I'm great.
Okay, I like I simply said that my mother was listening to you. I know I know I know
It's the ridiculous ridiculous
Come on
a little bit
My mom my mom listens to you. I know yeah
I mean, I don't know how to bring up and you put me a backstage and my mom was like was what the fuck she texted
Well, what the fuck?
Yeah, sorry, sorry mama. Sorry mama, you know, it's like, you know, I know you maybe you had to put on time out here too
You know, so you know, he's like a little bit
You know what she actually said she was like I had to put him in the bed at that certain points tail
Yes, well, yeah, it's a free so we know it's a free uh
You're your free spirit. You can't it's hard to control anybody but it's hard to tell you what to do
It's hard to tell me what to do. It's like we're not gonna get anywhere just telling you what to do
It's probably
That's a person though that is like trying to take over you though. No, nobody's gonna take over me, okay?
There's no vacancy there's no vacancy
Before me he was saying
Was the guy's guys who was it? Who was it? Who was it? I don't know his name. I don't know his name
Hey guys, hey, hey Brian
We're gonna just say allies you either have to just accept him or let him up or not be there cuz you won't change
Yeah, oh, I know I mean it's like that's him and it's like, you know, it's when we're dealing with the person with like, you know
Alice is a little bit
I mean, I'm nobody because what is sanity really bells, you know, you get a little bit
I know I get a little bit crazy too, right? Okay. So, but yeah, it's like and you can't really reason with them. He's
he's done some things that make sense to me but no I was talking about the
British guy he was he's right here he's still he's in the chair now he was down
the earth yeah yeah well he's the under I mean he's the earth even if you and
being we all are up down the earth you know my defense and I apologize to any
snowflakes out there I do say how it is I don't dress it up
Just recently I found out that my wife is very ill at the moment, she's going through tests at the moment and she's had a biopsy done,
trying to find out whether or not she's actually got cancer or not at the moment.
But when I told my son, and yes I do have a son, unrelated to me, just for those idiots out there,
was very blunt and I just gave the facts and I didn't realize that I was so
I can't control what's going on externally and what the hospital is doing, etc.
So, I'm not worrying about it.
Alex's problem is he doesn't know what's going on internally with him, you know.
Yeah, we've all got shit going on behind the scenes, haven't we?
Yeah, yeah. Alex has done a lot of cocaine, you know, it makes it all movie, okay.
But it's actually something called a serenity prayer, a serenity prayer.
Uh, and this is like, you know, it's something to say in these moments where we're like, you know, what do we have control of?
It says God. Uh, uh, grant me the serenity to accept the things I cannot change.
To encourage to change.
Oh, I thought like okay, no go. Oh, I know it's like a whole prayer. It's a whole little poem
It's like it's what you know, it's interrupted with that. It's a non-realistic question
It kind of takes away from it. So I just wanted to read it completely. Okay, what is that?
To accept the things that we cannot change because there's some things we don't have control
We don't have control about people's minds. We don't have control of the sun coming out tomorrow
You know a lot of these things are just taking care by nature or you know other people, right?
but it says
So there so we have to accept sometimes we there's things we cannot change and it's like, you know
You know, we can try to paint the red the white roses red and bright and we're spoising the roses, right?
This is a
Yes, Alex your wife is sick. What's wrong with the old Alex? What are you doing?
Okay, he explained it out, but we just rewind every right a few minutes. You're being insensitive and you know, I'm not not
No, he's not it's car being insensitive. He's been wild
Yeah, he's being being off the wall. Yeah, listen Alex doesn't worry me at all. Like I said, you look at what you can
You know, it's like Alex is Alex. He's always has been
He's that he's that way sometimes and he's not that way, but I mean he can
All credit to Alex when he's not
Drinking or anything like that. He's a really good guy. Yeah. Yeah, I mean, but there are times
When that's overridden by his other side, he's drinking. Yeah, I know I've seen yeah
I'm not playing any any cartoons Katrina. Not today
Hey, I haven't got time and be it's not my show. Yeah, I don't think I don't think you I don't think it was fine
Yeah, so let's uh
The only thing I have to say to Alex is that that was kind of messed up because you got me back stage
My mom was talking
Your mind could ever even fathom so when you talk you a little bullshit stories like my mom died of cancer I'd laugh at it
My mom watches him guys. That was it. I don't know. It's a kind of almost they get further like your mom
I don't know what you're saying. You're trying for you. He said he said your cancer. That was a weird
No, no, no, I don't like it
I mean, it's like, you know, it's funny that it's like they're
So, you know, it's insane, but I say, don't say that he's screaming things that you're not supposed to say, right?
It's like, you know, it's not funny anymore, Alex. I don't feel like he should be on the rest of the night.
I think he should be the rest of the night off. I'll donate the gong myself at this point.
Hold on. Alex, take the night off.
Ziggie Ziggie you're next. You know Ziggie you keep harping on me. See just join the conversation
I don't want to hear anything about you know bush glycerine or you know, you got put backstage
Okay, like you like a perfect age again, and so now that this one don't I don't know you're better
I got feedback stage 20 minutes ago. Okay, that's all I was so I was the one that was talking about my mom
Okay
I don't know, it's just like she's like my mom was messaging me right now and she's like
I don't believe you, I don't even believe you, I don't even believe you, I don't even believe you
My mom listens to you every day
I would have her call on the show, I need to talk to her myself
I haven't been up here for 40 years
Not yet
Oh
And I know it better not be a woman a woman's voice and a voice changer
This is like you. Okay. I was just banned from be this for good for Dawson. Oh my gosh. Yeah, she did that
That's not cool. Alex. No, he's he never be lucky. No, he's a guy
Yeah
Man my mom tried to
I can kind of hear him, but this can you turn him up a little bit
He has control of his microphone. So Goddy can turn up his microphone if he if you'd like
Your mic's a little I think your mic is your mic is high. Let me look at your mic once again
All the way up, but why are you so loud? It's so loud
Very close to the mic. Yeah, if you're close to the microphone
You put a little bit away from your mouth like that and then it's like you'll still pick up the words that won't quite be
You know breaking my ears. I actually was you know injured by being you know
Sta bb ed in the ear with a sharp object before so
Sta bb ed
Sta ped bb ed
Stepped
We we can't say there. We can't say I don't I don't like it's a violent
I just don't like violent language, but you know I think we can say
SCBV I don't know you say whatever you want. We just got to spell it out. Yeah, spell it out
You can use code words spell it out, you know, you want yes
Any word you can just you can say there's a code word for everything. Okay, just learn it use it
And we'll all get the idea. We don't need people are just like so. So there's anything on panel
That's it. Let's do it. He's like I'm not gonna fall for it. You said you said to me
I'm not gonna fall for this trap. Oh, I don't know. I don't such I don't such I don't such I don't such you know, I uh, I
Just uh, I brought a few of them, but I
Don't so got three. Yeah, yes, sir
Why do you think I am not a grim reaper but a grim paper?
Just out of curiosity.
Play on words.
It's obvious you're Alfred Hitchcock.
I'm out for what, sorry?
You're Alfred Hitchcock.
Well, you don't know me. I don't know you. Let's just leave it at that, shall we?
I actually enjoyed talking about it.
You're very, very, very, very cryptic.
I've seen the birds. I've seen the psycho. I've seen the northwest. I've seen...
rear window. I've seen many of your films. I think there's something in quantum physics
it's called the observer effect. Have you heard of this effect of the observer effect?
There's somebody observing. What does that do? The observer effect refers to the phenomena
where an act of observing a system inevitably alters that system. The effect is prominent in both
quantum mechanics and behavioral studies impacting how phenomena are measured or understood.
Essentially the very act of observing especially with that with that with measuring instruments can charge
Change the state of behavior of what is being observed. That's interesting to think about. Oh, that's so
You like to watch is that so psychies you like to walk?
No, I really don't I mean, it's like I'm more of the exhibition is I like to
I like to get I like to get in this video. I like to get in this video
I don't like I don't watch for people, but I'm not like a watch. I'm not like a
A collector of information like a spy. I think yeah, I'm more of a
I'm very poor at freedom
Fancy's the macabre the macabre yeah, you know, I
Loved you know Marilyn Manson good growing up
Dark comedy for movies, you know the accent. Yeah. Yeah, he's a little bit of a British accent. I think we're
You know, it's
Rubbing off on us Amanda. Yes, you think yeah, I know everything's going crazy in chat. Let's see
Yeah
No, I do understand about you know people that getting a you know
Unfortunately my father did pass away from cancer last year and another look at a lot of people are you know
We're gonna the baby boomers are coming of age. You know that we're losing a lot of them and
Did you say that I don't know who you are, sir?
Who's I heard a woman's voice who's that woman's voice?
Did you hear the woman's voice I heard a woman's voice guys just there that was his mother
That is that your real voice that's your real voice
You're really a woman and you're using a voice changer guy
I hear the woman's voice your voice changer is glitching. Did everyone hear it? I heard a woman's voice. It's like a
You ever hear playing these games like you stop these games. What are you trying to prove?
Who is that I heard my voice there shit, what are you doing? What are you playing?
Hello, got it. Are you playing games?
I'm not playing again. I'm asking you a question. I think you're saying to you sir.
Good evening page good evening, sir
What are you doing?
Life is a game. I think
well, okay, well you can go go go backs go with Ziggy and
Grim Reaper and you can go play chess or hold on be the ones to come and yell you
Hi, be the
I want you to yell because the
Well
Alistair he kicked off. Oh, yeah, so yell at God
Okay
Stop you tell me you say he's not like Madonna right now
Madonna the singer okay, but the Madonna the singer. Yeah, but uh, yeah
Oh god, you sing it. Oh my god my cover
Oh, she doesn't quite sound well. She sounds a little yeah, she's scared
Female boy
Oh gosh good guys with a thought west side story. We don't have to we don't have to be you know rival gang
Who are these people? I don't know page. I only know psyche. I know that like Ziggy guy with the t-shirt
I don't know. I don't know. They see it. I think they're a bunch. That's it. They're some kind of like
Discord secret society. I don't know if it's
Illuminati
It's either the Amish the Amish, the Mormon, the Satanans or all of the above. They're all of these are Mormon. Oh my god
I knew it. You guys know that the gay flag was just made illegal in Utah
You know, it's like the first state that has banned the gay flag at all, you know, government places. Oh, it's interesting
It's all coming together now.
Where did Paige come back?
Paige, where did you go?
I didn't write it.
These guys up there is cured of Paige.
She doesn't want to be part of this ultrify.
We're too many cults.
God, we need to take one cult and just stick to it.
What's a cult?
We're all going to wear Nike tennis shoes, I'm just hoping.
Okay, Gotti you would know about snow because it's like you know you and Alex probably have as much cocaine as
Scarface on in your you know your desk drawer. So leave me alone about I thought God knew shit
But he ain't shit. He just literally got as a guy doesn't exist. I'm sorry
the
I don't know guys guys. Can we all get let's all like I'm do voice lessons together and we can all like
Yes, you mentioned a vows God and like I
I have a page in my book. I just leave if you don't like my voice. I'm gonna see you later
I don't even be here. Okay
Later psyche. Bye. Later. Later. Later, bitch. Love you. Love you. No, I don't love you. I hope your microphone dies on you tonight and you're like
Well by being a we'll see you later
Let's see so I do you have a page in this book about on it's nice book or thing
Let me see where is this another? Oh, it's in my it's another book. It's in this one
Um, and Ziggy is not on the panel anymore. Oh, no, he is, he is. But I do have this, uh,
I think this thing with the vowels, right? It says
the tree of gallows or the ladder of vowels and it goes O I E a highway 61 U.S. Route 61 the blues highway
Okay, and then it has like some kind of devil square like some kind of square. Okay. Hey, P. G.
Okay, and look, and so I have this drawing. We got it. See, look at this drawing. See if this makes any sense to you.
Here we go. Here it goes.
I, I, it goes O, O, I, E, O, I, E, A, E, A, E, I, O,
and then I don't know, you use that in there, but it says.
It's like the diaphragm.
I, it goes I, A, E, O, and you inhale new oxygen.
Okay. Okay. Hello.
Hi, I ended my 60 panel like a people to come here and I send them here and you kicked me everybody
I can do better tear card readings and psyche
Please yeah, you are being sold things to me and say you already you're being sold
I guess like to jump and you're already leaving and now you're gonna make a big deal better. Okay, beta. No, no, no, no
Thank you very much for
supporting the show. Let me see. I don't know who this is. That's not Rado though. I think this is a
kick page too. What were you kicking? I don't know. Now, she's like, people are just leaving like
they know their signature. Okay. So, Rondo, okay. I want to beat this back there. Okay.
I just want to say one thing in all kindness. Everybody joined me on BKG where I can reveal
Okay, well be there, you know, it's like you just think yours that you're being a broken record and it's not very kind
I don't ever mess with you and say oh, you know be dead does I don't even know what you do
You know you're wholesaling whatever. I don't you got more tonight. This fake hiding is getting old. I don't know
It's like, you know, why are we right? Why are you fighting it? Yeah? Yeah, stop this out
You just stop it. You don't mess with around with my my my my trade be does right right now, but you don't do it
Okay, don't do that
Um, so, yeah, you know, so lessons, huh? Me? Yeah, that's what they say. You're you were a washed up actor back in the 80s
Washing actor back in the evening though. I was in I was in some like local community theater
You know, it was an extreme place. I did drama in my school. Okay. Now. She's gonna be there
You're saying horrible things like you're not gonna until you stop saying horrible till you stop saying horrible things
I'm not really message me and he said it's gonna get another time
Okay, please guys making stuff up. Hold on. Let me stay at home. It's like I just maybe make sure these right people like that
Can you get a face tattoo? Hello?
Hello, hello, don't say the n-word. Hello. Who's this? Why'd you say that?
Because I've been being an Edward bumps. So who is this? Who are I speaking to you? This is rondo
I've tried to come on before you always never you never let me on
Okay rondo, okay, so here's the question psyche. Um, you never let me go. That's rondo. Oh, yo rondo
So psych I have a question for you. How long you've been doing this for
Doing what what for youtube stream? I've been doing youtube stands like like, you know
October of last year. I've been you know, basically doing my life my life streams and then the panels since january
Yeah, I'm gonna go I'm gonna get you know the book of uh, you know Persian poetry and I'll be also doing also doing
Is it good for the psyche
I'll start doing her version of chill chill chill dude. I need you to chill
Rhonda, he's not insane that's fucking rude also say she would never do that to you. That's what she does
Yeah, she said it several times. She's like, oh, I'm doing
He's never kicked you from her panel
Yeah, she's not bought me on before and I think I mean I think if she was saying something very rude
You know like a little thing. She's like, oh, I don't like you. She's like, oh, I don't like you
You can listen back to what she said to me. She's like too much. She takes over the whole
Yeah, but you're gonna take, stop. Just give me a sec.
I was totally, I was completely flattered. I was gonna take you from everybody else, all these random people all the time
You're gonna take shit from them and let them come back and play let's play games
But like Vita can't say nothing. I brought back several times, but she keeps, you know
She keeps saying things that aren't true and insulting me and trying to say like that
I
Well listen back page because you didn't hear the whole thing and so you know you're not hearing the whole story
Okay, and so I know you know you're just gonna want to like you know, you know, but listen to what she's saying
Okay, let's listen back. There's no less him
It's fine if I'm not be friendly loyal with friends it's like it's so far where it's like I can't be like in the middle of
You know, I'm not like, uh, you know
in an Oreo cookie and I can't be in the middle of every argument.
What is going on? What the hell is going on here?
I don't know. Everyone's feeling like they're the thest thest thest be inside.
Okay. People are going to be angry tonight?
Or are they? I'm not I'm not pretending. I'm I'm I'm I'm annoyed. I'm honestly
I'm not really angry. I don't even get angry. I just get like
defensive. I get like you know protective of you know because
Sometimes not everyone has someone looking out for them, right? So I get me sure to look up for myself
Hey, sir, I don't want to be rude. I don't want to be rude. Don't take us the wrong way. Um, are you are you autistic?
My god, I don't know. I don't think I've ever been diagnosed. He's very artistic. He's draws pictures. Yeah, you didn't see his art
No, let me see some more dude
It's like you draw his picture. Go ahead. I did well. I mean I say I don't have
I mean, I don't have an idea
Choco, I mean he's I mean I can draw full screen. Oh fuck. Where'd you go?
I can draw something that says, you know, the reaper network and stuff, but I just can't, I don't know what he looks like. There's God here right there.
Come on, Roy, really? That's a masterpiece.
I'm gonna fucking put your masterpiece in.
Okay, well, Pay-Pay-Pay, listen back to what she was saying, and you'll...
She'll go understand I didn't even try and provoke her anything
I was being pleasant and then yeah, and then you know start attacking me for no reason and there's easy
I don't know if you know easy cameras on this easy. Oh my god
He's holding balloons and the whole I think he's holding no he's holding a
Well, no, he's holding on like a my favorite
She's drinking one dingle and ghost of my favorite dangle and ghost. Yeah, I did a couple
I did dingle or it's there's dingle. It's one of dingles and then you know, I have uh, you know
I've sat these scarlet, you know, it's been her she's right there
It's a okay, and then a time we all know we all know in the time from the chat
There we go. Yeah, everyone subscribe to be this kiddies go over there, you know, it's like a you know, you know, you know
was not a contest. I want to help everybody. You know, she's helped me a lot. I didn't say
anything to comfort that. There's, there's spunky.
Uh, so we have, uh, let me see. Okay. Let me see. Money for 20. Here's Alice, of course. Alice in my
Um, he's done a little little twig car. There's sort of diamond guys three diamond
Can you draw? Can you draw rondo?
I can try. That's the best player diamonds ever gonna look right there. Just get a black marker and like do a circle
And there's Christine. Oh
I don't think you know, you know, I don't think you don't want me to show her picture and I don't want to do the beat
There's a glass
Yeah, but yeah, I don't want to make rain matter that she already is but it doesn't need a reason to be mad
Just just do it. Yeah. Yeah, I love you. I love you. Oh, wow
That's beautiful
I think it's nice
Oh, okay. Okay. Well, anyway, that's why I beat his daddy probably beat. I'm sorry. I'm not bad. I'm not a good artist
Okay, well, I think I'm okay artist, but
You're beautiful. Let me see if you show your picture you look like Jesus
Rack well, that's not very nice to say be the
He's been talking this whole time has he been
He has something in the air tonight. Yeah
Man, do we need to see it too? Probably probably you know
Mod or something. It's Los Angeles. So this is oh, yeah, hold on. What is my mod doing? So what's the mod doing?
Oh, be oh, yeah beat is not crazy. The beat is my mod. Can you believe it? I mean you think you think I think I
I still love her. I still love her. What about who who who jubita I thought I drew that
The pics are crazy, well, it's just you know, I'm a little crazy
Things he's the grim reaper. What do you think of that?
Who thinks of the grim reaper this guy grim reaper? He thinks he's the real grim reaper
Well, here's I think I think I'm the grim reaper. I think the grim reaper is that
He's got a very complex, you know, it's very associated with Saturn, Father of Time,
Kronos, you know, it's like the planet Saturn, which is what my ruling planet, the planet
of Karma, the planet of Matter, the world coming to materialism, the planet of Time,
actually, they know how to time.
And so, yeah, that's interesting about it, but let's see, what else, the Grim Reaper,
Okay, hold on one second, Ida, give me, go ahead, give me one condition, you say you
love me?
Yeah, I'll give you one condition.
Let me do a reading for you, Mr. Saiki.
I'll forgive you. You say you love me come back and you say that I'll let like one let beta do a one reading for you
That's not repetitive. You pussy-ass bitch putting me
For you
Numbers one up right
Beat it. It's a missus. Do you want to hear reading or not from me? No, but you're making it. I'll be you just make it
Shut up
Oh, not Alexander the McQueen I do
No, nobody my ass. That's what you like. You like it bossy. Don't you you fucker?
No, I
asshole
I don't want it. I don't want it. No, I'm gonna do your fucking reading and you're gonna take it
Thank you, I got it what's going on guys baby, what's going on?
I mean, I know this is my little fucking life to come here and then he wants to be a bitch
And he doesn't want me to like do a reading for him
I'll do one for now. It will like open your guys. I you will have the biggest fucking asshole awakening ever
terror awakens
Now fuck you thank you for ever putting me backstage you can come back come back come back
Yeah, do the reading
I'll keep alec the alice backstage for the
That's what was missing. That's
It was the same
Yeah, guys, I think I take it. Okay. Okay, so I'll bring Alex back since the reason. Okay. Hey Alex
Ah
Well, I'm out of here. You can have Alex. Yeah. Bye
She sounds like Minnie Mouse the don't bitch right like we need
Needs more
She's gonna fly off to Brazil again
She's gonna flap away like it with her feathers
Okay, so Alice, okay, so Alice what do you do now you're docking summer Alice was what's the deal like what are you doing?
How many embers are there how many Duncan's are there oh, that's true
Duncan Duncan donuts
Okay
No, Alex. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
You he told you not to bring up on I don't wish to be a platform with I know
He's off the night. He's just like he just broke the rules for a serious everybody get pissed in their fucking cornflakes this morning instead of milk
Apparently
Who would do that?
That's what this is
Everyone's gonna be happy against
Yeah, I'm not serious, but like I don't like with my friends fight
Yeah, well, they'll be they'll be friends again tomorrow
They'll be friends in five minutes. Yeah, probably I was gonna say probably today
Well, I'm sorry guys, I'm sorry, I'm gonna bump people out. I mean is like
I was just trying to hang out.
Everyone's mad at me. Everyone's mad at me for everything.
I ain't doing anything.
Everyone points your fingers at Psyche.
Psyche can't be blamed for this.
God, it's all your fault.
Point your fingers at him.
Fuck you, it is.
The devil told me that you were conspiring against him
for the whole story.
There is no devil dumb dumb.
God got me coffee. Don't call me dumb dumb. You're not
Only only Chris will only Chris will goes can have that
I don't know. It's like there's the world is duality, right? And so if there is a God, you know, if the God is in the singularity, if it's in the duality, it would come out. It's true. It's talking about as God ended. The polarities would come out as the polarities.
It's really a giant joint. Yeah, it's a giant joint.
Wow.
Well, you know what? It's like, it's kind of, but I said it's like, you know, the Willy Wonka test. It's going to see who has a pure heart.
Look who waddled in here. Just wow.
Yeah, okay. Wow. Wow guys. Oh my gosh. The panel is just
Emptying out. Oh my gosh. Oh
Bye-bye. Okay. Oh my gosh. We just lost a little bit of weight on the panel. What happened?
Guys, there's those ghosts in the machine. There's there's there's some kind of technical difficulties. Oh my gosh
He cut please get a drawing
Yeah
This is rondo
Listen bro, get your permanent marker out. They're like you roll second one
I don't believe that's what you look like
I don't have I don't have enough ink ink for that. Come on, bro. Just draw a fucking circle. Oh
Just wonderful. He's just
Thank you, thank you
Yes, okay, so Monica Monica wants it. I can draw a picture of Monica. Yeah, you're welcome
I know it's like, you know, you guys there's something called there's a word. There's a word. I really don't I mean
It's like a word
The words not bad, but it's like it's like the way it's done
Okay, I'll put the word on a piece of paper. I don't want to say it's bad juju to say this word
I'll say this word. Okay. I'll say this is the word that I this is like one of the things that I really
Do you not care for
Now it's it gives you much away, but this
You read it smart yeah smart. Yeah. Yes. Okay smart who's smart
Well, if you don't know that then
Maybe look up that's the thing you have to work that one out for yourself. Hello, Rhonda. How are you?
How you doing?
I'm alright, I just wondered if you were trying to say something about the Grim Reaper, I take on the name, I look after a network of people, we share some thoughts and like-minded shall we say, but like on here there's a few people who are into tarot cards, etc.
Psycho's doing his best to not to allow this to become a shit show, basically, excuse my language,
but a lot of panels end up that way with certain characters, you know,
and I've been so patiently waiting to speak for about half an hour or so because...
The panel was going in the direction that I didn't know anything about so I can't comment
It's like yeah, I don't know
I don't even I don't know anything about where it goes. Yeah, I mean I say I have no idea what people are talking about
So it's like, you know, I'd rather not have it on my show words like I can't even respond to it because
I mean people say around and they say things in the chat and they don't know me, you know
Just because I'm older than most people doesn't mean to say I have to take a whole people's meds, you know
You don't know me first time up here
Yeah, I think it's hilarious. Oh, by the way, if you're wondering how old I am, I was created around about 15, in the 1500s, during the Spanish flu problem, I mean, created the grim reaper because they were seen to be taking away, but that's the history lesson.
I think I was like plague doctors about our counseling. Oh, actually, I would say like, you know
But I really do think Saturn like, you know, with the hand the sickle and like the the death mask
You know, that was especially during the plague, right?
People people read what they want to read into the name grim reaper
If you actually think about it, all the grim reaper does is move souls from one place to another
Oh, hello. Here's my old friend Denison. How you doing, mate?
Yeah, you put me backstage
Oh, I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know who did. I don't know
More prevalence than have more people doing it. So it's accomplished my goal. So thank you so much
Part of my vision. Okay. What happened to Paige? Oh, I was my viewers
I think you said people with page page left because she's doing other stuff
I don't know. Everyone's mad at me. I mean, I'm trying to do my best
Everybody mad at you Pat
because there's so many
Alexander because I can't talk, you know, I can't you barely get a word in because there's so many people and they're saying like a
Lot of strange things and some of the things are off topic
And I I'll say don't say this and like you bring it up and if they don't do this
It was JT and and you and and Ziggy got it
I don't I don't know. I don't know. I must I think I'm I think I'm losing my marbles guys
You know, I guess there's no way. No way
The bike did you fix the bike? I have to I they do have a like a repair you can get you know
Just the it's probably if you use the instrument place or something. So I'm gonna take it as soon as possible
How do you have some, you know, I said I have a little bit of a ability
Tell you don't save up a little bit now that I have the channel going so hopefully I'll be able to
Get it taken care of ASD. I got a tricycle if you want to borrow it
Yeah, I want to have a unicycle tricycle a little bit too
Do too simple. Okay, so okay, so how about
You have a motorcycle. I really like a motorcycle. Can you give me a Harley and I have a piece of a Harley
I don't think you'd buy a Harley. I could I could I could I could I could I could I could I mean I probably like
I don't know if I fall off but I can, I can, I can, I, what is that time you, I'll, I'll just ride, ride, bitch, you can drive it, you can, you can, I'll, I'll, I'll be holding on to it, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
The dog it was a dog
It was toad it was todo and no and I'm and you know
Mrs. Goldsch did have cats and the todo did chase the cats because Dorothy let the fucking dog run wild and do what?
Everyone's do I mean she that was her version of the glove
But it's actually you know she should have like rained todo in a little bit and say hey todo
You know don't do that because I don't want to you know
You know us to be separated and you know you didn't you came to the sheriff's office. We put down
Toad was a metaphor
Yeah, and the total actually total is the smartest one in the movie
He's actually the most innocent person in the movie
He was the one that the uncover who the wizard truly was he was smarter than all the
All the other people combined so
So I would you would you psych would you would you bang beat you guys seem like a good couple?
Well, that's the very interesting question. I'm gay and so you know
Bang women I say I am kind of interested right you know Chris K right now
That's where some stuff he said and maybe you know he wants to do some kind of three-some other
Whatever whatever we'll do it. Let's see. Let's do a Chris
Yeah, I don't know but I don't think beatle. I don't think beatle liked me because she used to say I was I was
Hey, I had some prints now. She says I'm like a like a evil frog and so I don't know years. Is she your sister?
Um probably in many many many lifetimes. Yeah
Yeah, old be the good old be the you know
You never changes old be the same the same voice the same if you look exactly the same, okay?
You guys act like very similar
We act very similar. Yes, we're both
With Queen or Queens in a way. She accused me of being a Colombian drug lord. Well
No, I mean Alex actually admitted to being one and then then he got a job at the NYPD
I'm just I'm not sure what is anyone so I told her that my name was else when you
Uh, I think usually being a serial killer. Okay. Okay. Let's thank you people big guy. It says no slander
So that means no accusing. No slander. Oh
Ripper wanted to explain something to you. I think you said, okay. Okay. I'm sorry grim reaper. Go ahead. I'm sorry
Who cut you off? No, I wasn't saying that I was just just listening in I'm thinking you're right about to so the book
or the film did put that
make Toto the most intelligent character in the film and then, you know, the latest version is sort of, like, ridiculous, you know, well, hey.
And he was a, he was a care and care, in the movie, Toto was a care and terrier.
And so this is like a, you know, special, you know, I think from Scotland, right, these, these care and terriers and this, you know, it's a very...
Special kind of dog. I love uh, I
Love those the spirit of these terrier. They are very very smart and we can learn a lot from dogs
You know and all animals actually okay, so how's the honor? How's the honor? You're gonna come search. Okay guys your earplugs
Hold on room Reaper. Did you say photo is the most intelligent character in the Wizard of Oz?
Yes, yes, the dude from the clip the little doggy
Yeah, yeah, it's more intelligent and Dorothy
Yes, the carly lot, you know all the whole thing everybody. Yeah, the dog. Yes. He's a smart boy
You know, how do you come to that conclusion asshole? And that's what you think sucks dick. You understand
Cuz you guys are retarded
Dog is the most intelligent character in the Wizard of Oz
bro you're lucky you're out in US
you might get convicted of that
you know what
you know he was a good dog
he was a good dog
yeah good smart dog
can I just say it never fucks his mind
it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just
well
that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that
Yeah, yeah, now they give it clear. What's up, and you guys are gay. No, it's right. Oh shorty
Why are you saying a horrible thing? I mean guys? Yeah, stop acting
No, stop acting like that. It'd be the panel panels is a bad example for you guys to follow
I mean there's he may be a but he can still kick your ass shorty
No
Yeah, okay, so anyway
And I'm not not a violent person. It's a total poops. Yeah
Totals housebroken, you know, Alex
You played the clip for me the other day
No, you want to see this
This one home the clip. Oh, no, no, no, no the clip. What's the clip?
Alex
We need what are you gonna do to me if I you pull me over and
I've been speeding on the freeway. What are you gonna do to me? I'm gonna say sir
Registration I'm gonna pretend it's bad. I'm gonna say step out of the car and I'm gonna throw you in the bushes
In the bushes, I'm gonna fuck the shit out of you in the bushes
Okay, my god. I'm gonna end up in the trees on the side of the highway
I'm gonna fucking just give it to you and then that's it my man
I'm gonna make popcorn and just fall my way
That's great
Everyone everyone loves everyone. That's a great
Cream get ready the real. Oh, yeah. I don't ask took off. I don't know. He I kick him off this time
So I was gonna shock call or maybe maybe I'll look into that on Amazon. I will take it. Okay, so 40 notes ready. That's right
I don't call everybody gay. Okay
You say okay, you say boys won't affect me. What does that mean?
For you girl. Oh, who's that?
Trans man. I'm very confused. That's that's already diamond. It looks like for the diamond without
Oh shit, it's diamond
My god with Alice is confused now. I think burdo is 30 diamond. I think JT is
Vicky, and it's very confusing guys
If you're confused imagine how I feel. I've been here the whole shorty is a trans man
Okay, well, there's nothing wrong with being trans.
I don't wanna say we're trans rights.
It's not July 1st, guys, 7-1, you know?
With 7-1, that's a good number.
7-1, okay, my birthday is actually 1-7,
so it's kind of the reverse of that.
Yeah, now for Irby, and also cancer
is the opposite of Capricorn,
and so I'm at at least six months
from my birthday pretty much, almost about six months.
Irby, hey Irby, how are you?
Yeah guys, it's getting a little hectic. I'm trying to you know, have a fun show. I'm trying to have a fun show
I'm trying to chill. I'm trying to chill. I can't I got guys. I got people putting black magic curses on me
You know, I've mobsters. I have military people in the chat. I have people are
having multiple personalities disorder people are are
Flandering dogs. I mean it's like guys this is more drama than
You know all daytime television combined, okay? I mean
Guys, I mean it's all here. I mean the what's going on on TV now nothing now. It's all it's all YouTube YouTube has taken over
Right means guys go to the gym
Uh and we're cool. It's my day off. You're drunk. So come up. It's okay. Sorry. You're fine. You went to the gym. Gym drunk
That's not the best thing to do now blame page for the drama. Yes, I blame page page
It's you know page. You're so nice that it's like people just walk on over the show. I
Love you page
So I know thank you so much. Okay. Good night. Bye
I've got I've got a short workout Dennis and always good to see a nice meeting you
Rondo
Hold on why why did why does Paige come over here and grow balls? Oh
Sorry, I'm out there. See you late guys. Bye. She came over here and grows balls. Just just like what's beta?
I've ever seen the witches of Eastwick like eventually if you put it like a few like strong powerful women together
They kind of will form a you know a cult based on wishcraft and then the guys kind of screwed
Yeah, but they're submissive on their channel very submissive women, but they come on here
They want to like they want to fucking flex nuts like what is this?
Multiple personality type shit. You ever see this? Oh my god
Yeah, I've seen it so much the past
Yeah, I've just said a lot of psychology. I'm dealt with narcissists narcissists of psychopaths
You know dark empaths and actually in the end regular empaths and a lot of kinds of people home. We have
Haysie
It was a joke
What are you doing now?
She's ready for combat
Yeah, baby, you know the obstacles away in between the two of you. She's like if he's like an Amazon warrior goddess, you know
You know what he can page they can't hit on me
These girls come up here and flex their balls right as soon as he said that page came up to flex our nuts
Page page has been a forkle balls, but she's always had these better forkle balls. I mean, it's like not she just grow a pair
She plays fucking trivia. Okay. She comes over here. I don't see her flexing at all
Not cool
I said correct
Because we roll over there. Well, here we go the fighting the fighting and all I wanted to do is come over here and join
You and the trivia and we came up and not and then it was a fight and I don't know why
Alright stocky you see that she's flexing nuts right now. It's okay
Overies
That bitch is in a war attire.
I don't mean...
Well, it's working. She's pretty as shit.
She's going to click her hair 30 times.
That's it, right? Because I thought we were cool.
Well, what's she...
We are cool.
Hi, Alex. I'm going to read up to you again.
Because everyone's talking about...
Oh, no.
Ready for work.
Yeah, we're going to say, yeah, maybe...
It doesn't relate to you because it's a different kind of war.
It's not like, you know, we're...
I mean, I'm in a relationship, so I can't...
I shouldn't shut up.
page is not, um, it's just that in, I don't know, Jan, Jan too, Ray, they're gonna send a clip to your
all I want is to get new nails. I'm sick of looking at those fucking purple black nails for
three months. Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, what are you? What are you? What are you?
Try like I was like the fashion police. I mean
Women understand what the word red means by the way, it's called man
Yeah, like which like exactly what you guys are like that what you guys are
Hold on anyway
I mean, jeez, I'm always more of these interesting names.
These are versions of a...
animals. So there's the cane toad. So as I'm sure most Australian readers,
this has a shiver go down their spine, the mention of the cane toad. Cane toads
have an interesting history. Originally from Central and South America, they were
introduced to parts of the Pacific and Australia to be a savior on their crops,
which kept getting on eaten by the other plants. The cane toad however went on to
become even the most more of a pest in Australia, becoming poisonous and able to
ways to deal with these invasive pests. The actual name toad is of a terribly boring origin.
All we know is it comes from the old English Tadij and nothing more. These toads have come to be
called cane toads because they were brought to Australia to eat and exterminate the sugarcane beetle.
With the beetle, obviously, being named after the sugar cane, it ate so much, though.
When they introduced the toads to eat the sugar cane beetles, it eventually became to be called a cane toad.
Perhaps Australia will next introduce a cane wolf or a cane eagle to eat all the cane toads.
With that, guys, okay, yes, even though it's more interesting than people just fighting, you know,
and I'll bring people back up, like, but I'm just, you know, just chilling for a second.
My show if I want to like have me stressed out. I'll fucking go to somebody else's show, you know, it's my show
Okay
Hey, how about clownfish when I get to about clownfish this clownfish are rather funny and funny fish
I'm not totally sorry for doing that. You know funny fish clowns
Ah, so when the female clownfish of the group dies one of the males will change sex to become the head female
I'll let you decide if you think humans should be able to do this or not.
They come in a variety of colors too, most well known are the orange with white and the
black stripes.
But the orange can instead be red, yellow, black, or even pink.
It's because of these bright and colorful patterns that they've become known as clownfish.
As clowns tend to wear bright and colorful clothing, luckily clownfish aren't as scary
as clownhumans, though you fear a professional clown reading this, I'm sorry, I'm sure you're
Clownfish are known by another name, anemonefish.
This is because of the unique relationship
that clownfish and sea anemones form.
While sea anemones might seem like nothing more
than dancing underwater flowers,
they are certainly clever enough
to become BFFs with clownfish.
Not only are they happy in the relationship,
they are instrumental for each other's survival.
Clownfish clean anemones and eat their dead tentacles.
In return, clownfish can get the,
sea anemones left over food and even use our singing tentacles as protection for other predators.
Clownfish can even live in sea anemones and so its perfect relationship. I hope you can have
a relationship with your significant other as good as the one between clownfish and sea anemones.
Speaking of clownfish living in sea anemones, we are about to meet the most famous clownfish of all,
Nemo. The name Nemo means nobody.
which represents how a lone little Nemo felt
and stuck in the sea.
He was named after the Jules Berne character,
who was also in a perilous underwater escapade,
Captain Nemo, I'm sorry, Captain Nemo, Yema.
Okay.
Are you okay? What kind of gay shit was that dude like
Nemo come on dude, we're like
Well
Yeah
We're bros
You gotta be like a little brother. I know we're bros, but I don't know if you do okay anyway
My you guys know what a matriska dollars. It's like this Russian dollar. It's like infinite doll. Are you gonna are you gonna see later, brother?
Um, okay. Adieu, uh, mom
Fair fair friend brother. I don't know fair for Frotzer. Bye, Frotzer. My brother or mono
So yeah, yes. Hey left not
Hey left not are you talking to Ziggy, I don't respond to you. Hey left you I don't respond to left nuts
Yeah, you're supposed to say hey, right night, and then we're gonna say right now
That wasn't funny it wasn't funny and I actually really funny
I'll talk to you guys. Bye. Okay, please. Oh geez, okay
So we can read about this stuff. Do you want to guys know my McDonald's? I mean, that's interesting
Okay McDonald's is a company that's been scrutinized in more recent years
They're feeding families with no worries. So up the moment people started to wonder to themselves
What on earth is McDonald's putting in my mouth?
Since then the company has tried to maintain a good image in the public eye and in all honesty
They have I guess I mean you see the golden arches more or less everywhere you go
McDonald's is actually a fairly common surname. In fact, it's one of the most popular Scottish
land names there is. That popularity might be thanks to the fast food chain, the name
surname McDonald's, which can be spelled McDonald's, which means son of Donald's, but also McDonald's
is, but which McDonald's is the food chain named after? Well, there's actually two McDonald's,
The brothers started out in 1937 selling hot dogs from a hot dog stand with a shame hot
dogs are no longer on the menu and from here the food grew more popular and led to opening
other restaurants entrepreneur Ray Kroc visited the restaurant as they had purchased the brand
of multi-mixers.
Here Kroc style restaurant like none other a limited menu with a focus on speed and quality
crocs fell in love with it promising to make McDonald's a hit with the rest of the country
Okay
Huh interesting, okay, how about Nike? What is Nike Nike?
Perhaps Nike started life in 1964 with a completely different name blue ribbon sports
It's more than safe to say this is far from the most exciting name
So thank goodness that one of the most famous shoe makers in the world eventually gave themselves a more exciting name
But what does the name even mean?
Well, it's it has roots in Greece. They're literally a goddess in Greek
mythology called Nike. Why is the goddess and not one of the more well-known gods imagine if they were called Zeus's shoes that
That's a shoe company is named for
Well, Nike's the goddess of victory being a company that makes sports shoes and other sporting goods
It makes sense to have a name it for the god of victory as you know victory is kind of important in the world of sports though
Don't trust me on that not too good on facts when it comes to world of sports regardless
It makes a pretty good branding if your company is literally named after the goddess of victory
Yeah, well, we can all name ourselves wonderful things, right?
Okay
Wow, there's some interesting abstract nouns I
Like this one loophole
History clue sarcasm
Okay, guys, okay, so I'm sorry I mean is they oh here God he's back. I'm dying. Oh, wow
I'm sorry. I thought you were I didn't know you was using a vector. I thought it was Ziggy so
Looking at close card when you get a chance, but not really you're ready. No, I got I got you I got you
I got you I like to ride away. You know, that's my favorite right away
I'm reaching I'm reaching for it right now. I'm reaching for it. This is something, you know, you know exactly the card
I like you're the best. You're the best. You're the best
No, you're the best
Okay, I'm I'm I want to pull two cars free because okay, but what do you there's something you're sad
I mean you're you're in like that, you know the blue nice black virtual real
But there's some kind of regret about something is some kind of sadness or regret who is that?
You know this is that isn't the five of cups and the five of cups a little bit
I mean, he's in like the black row, but you know, this is a kind of Saturn, but he's gonna sad about something
I don't know if in regret or sad about something he feels like something's been spoiled, but there are cups still stand
There's like, you know, there's a few cups. Maybe you know needs to be repaired, but there's
here there's a perfectly fine right there there's a perfectly fine cups you can read so i don't know
it's like i do i do have regret i regret yeah i regret putting two grand on my breaks today
Oh, that's expensive, huh? Well, then you get the three of cups
So you got five of cups and then you got three of cups and so this is like, you know
Can be third-party situation, but mainly means you know
Celebrating having a good time and coming together with friends love ones and celebrating but you know in any group of three people
There's always gonna be a power imbalance. So you always want to
You know, make sure you know your place in the group or whatever
Power of three power three. Yeah, that's okay. Hold on. Let's go. God
What on here? Okay. Well, okay, I need to pull this two more and there's these swords and
What is the one of the tennis swords which means like I think probably means you felt like you've been stabbed in the back about something or
betrayed or
I don't know if you had the energy or you heard somebody's feeling to their words or something like that
But it says you're gonna be moving on this is like the hand and then we have the the six of swords
This is really moving on so taking those
the swords you're stabbing you just you turn it into like you know protection for your boat, you know, you just uh
You know, you turn into like a little little uh, you know upgrade for your boat, you know
You take you take anything negative and turn it into something positive always positive
You know what they say no sword forged against me shall do me
Yeah, no weapon. No weapon formula against me shall prosper. Yes, that is in the bible and it is
Good a good thing to
Oh, you're welcome was a little more cards come out party a little regret a little a little feeling like
Maybe you've been betrayed by somebody but then also like the ability for you to like move on and to
Yeah, you know sometimes, you know, it's just like Mary Poppins remind me Mary Poppins like you know when she finished the
The nanny job. She's you know, she said it was time to go
She goes back in the sky with her umbrella and you know goes to the next place
She's needed it's kind of like you get you were kind of being called to certain places and maybe when oh
Yeah, I'm not king. I don't know but you did but they you know, but yeah, but I would I'd say you know
Be careful with it. I hope that you're not the one putting swords in people
You know I say and I hope you're not having a source putting you either
But it's like you know we all do and we all do sometimes in the store to me words they can be
I don't know I have a sword collection actually. Mm-hmm. Okay. Well
I need to I need to know learn how to use them. Okay, so I got
Okay, yeah, okay, that's so sorry I was talking so okay, so
It says you oh rando a drawing fool do it now. I didn't draw a rado with a rado is drawn. I do have him in the
Book he's right here home
Guys and next time you say I didn't draw rado. Hold on. I mean I drew him he's right here
He's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so, he's so
Well, I get I'm gonna draw you. I'm gonna draw you in your in your but you're wearing now. Oh, I'm gonna draw you guys
I mean, I put you across
Yeah, I was purple, but it'll do for now. It's gonna on these it's kind of a simple
Okay, let me see get dead. Okay. Okay. I'm putting you next to flirty diamonds in the book by the way, okay
That's all right. I'm not insecure
Yeah, you're very me. You're a very good-looking guy. I'm home. Let's see. Oh, that's the eyes
Okay, there we go. I got it. I got it. Yeah, okay
Okay, guys, you ready to see it. Here's here's God. I'll call it. I'll call this Goddy
Goddy
To I'll call it Goddy number two because you're in your next authority diamond, okay?
Jesus that looks like a thumb
That looks like exactly like your thumb
What the fuck with thumb?
Yeah, that looks just like your thumb guys again. There's sort of diamond
Like yes, oh my god
Yeah, hold on the first time be mad at me hold on a second
Right. Uh, let me see someone in the back chat. Oh, hold on. Yeah, here we go. He just sent you four dollars. I
You know, you change that one into the picture of Rondo. Hold on one second. Uh,
Rod Rondo, I'm random guy in the jack. I'm Rondo on the panel. Okay. You you think that looks like me
That did not look at me. That's it. That's God. He is. It's a picture
Because
I don't know I don't know your pictures a little bit too black for me. I don't know come on. Don't say
What would you say?
I mean, it looks like it's like the like the absence of absence of all late. I mean
It's very no the people that's not yet. It's not you come on bro. You're burnt in a coal coal mine or something
You're on YouTube monetize you can't be saying a shit full screen me
No
It looks like I missed you so I can draw you
I can I can I can draw you like this. Okay, I'll draw you right now. You look like I got I got I got
I can't fucking leave the house without getting made fun. You're fine. You're fine. You're fine. I'm on YouTube
This is why I'm on YouTube
Okay guys, I got your picture, okay
Okay, I got perfect. It looks exactly like you. I think and got all the okay guys and again guys
This is not this is not meant to it's gonna be good. Yeah
Okay, guys, this is not miss it. Okay, and this is also not I
Mean, I'm trying to like, you know color in a little bit. Oh, this is not it's not hair
It's it's like okay, so you ready home and your name is
Rondo
Rondo, I'm gonna rip your R-O-N-D-O. Okay. Let me see. Okay. What do you think? Rondo, how do you like your picture?
Welcome that
Yes, I mean it's he thought it's very nice white teeth, you know
And I didn't have a
I only have this color. That's when you care you really do a good job
The from hello razor. Yeah, the guy how rich is actually a good movie
I like a hellraiser they have I guess part two or three where they go in and he goes in it's like a church and like and then uh
Pinhead is like in the minister of the reverend is and he's like standing like she comes over and I think that
There's like some kind of minister with her and he tries to throw
Put up a cross and the guy's like and he's like oh sick
You shall not create graven images
Then the cross works the melt the guy's ah
Which one was that?
I think that was like hellraiser probably two or three. It wasn't the first one, but yeah
It's like uh, it's what it's the one where the girl from the first two was the best one
Yeah, I think that might have been two. That was really good
But there's one where they went to outer space. I mean that was kind of weird. I mean that was weird. Yeah
It's leprechaun. They did that too
Space was good Jason space is really good Jason a space. Yeah, I think I saw that when I was probably
Play eight to ten years. Well, I said Friday the 13th part eight Jason goes to Manhattan or space
I don't know. He goes to space eventually that one sucked Manhattan was bad. Yeah, space was good though
Yeah
Yeah, you've been transformed to personnel. Yeah, I've got it done God. He's got he's a managing model here
That's why I can expect him I expect more from him than uh, you know, just a random chatter. I expect him not to fit
Are you gonna let Sebastian up for like six hours again?
He was pretty good that day.
Um, he didn't do a bad job.
I can't like leave my panel like asleep.
I have to be more careful about it now.
But, um, especially, you know, there's people unpredictable.
You know, it's it's better to you drink a little bit less than you. I'm just having a couple beers tonight
You're safer with six hours of Sebastian than five minutes with me up here alone. Oh with you. Oh my god
Well, thanks for the game. Thank you. I don't I don't know
Last week I felt it was like with like KZ. Oh, no, not KZ. But they Ilya Goddy and you know
JT all all running the panel
I'm still you know here. It's I'm gonna know one strike. I did it. I did it one and there's a reason for that because
Nothing happens. Nothing happens
Yep, I'm I'm trying to
You know behave myself
Always successful, but you know
Leaf's going up here for like an hour alone. See what happens. Oh
Yeah, he's been no he likes to see that he likes to like dog names and he likes I mean
It's like I can't like believe some people are putting like the breaking my rules and have their own agendas with the drama and stuff
I you know, it's kind of cool just to have a chat. So thank you. So random guy. Okay. Thank you. Yeah
Yeah, I hope you like that drawing, you know, and thank you for thank you for your
Your super chats. We like the drawing
Maybe else when I'm drawing, you know, I can take care of it for you now if you
Want to send a donation? Otherwise, you know, I'll sort of I'll sort of waiting list for for Josh
So bad guys so bad
Not home so, you know
And a panel you don't even use any vulgarity. What's up, Sam and he already has you know, we're just talking about you
That was one. Yeah, so hey summer
Yeah
Yeah, let's not make fun of you know, I say I just don't like people calling anybody that word. It's like, you know
Just one of those incendiary words that people have said, right?
Very effective for manipulating the masses
Yeah, I know and most of us we're just kind of not not calling anybody that we're saying it in general overuse term
But that's pretty good see your people don't come
No one
What?
Wait, what do you mean?
See your people don't care no or enjoy what is he talking about? I don't know see my bike. I mean
You mad be mad bra
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
What do you want? Oh, you are watching my show on your TV or I hear her page
Dynasties
Oh, you're voices are familiar
Watching Dynasties Susan Lucci. Oh, yeah, Dynasties, you know Dynasties
Dynasties, that's not that's been canceled since like 1978 reruns man
No, you know, no one watches those
So poppers are terrible. I mean, it's like that really think the lowest form of
television. Let me see. So, it says some statement can't type in. He has borne it. Okay. His wife is
in the dungeon. Oh my god. You're a dungeon, um, Gotti. What? Do you have a dungeon they're saying?
Do you have a dungeon? You keep your wife. Yes, I got two. Oh my gosh. Well, he's a music guy.
I don't believe it. I mean, it's like my show is not appropriate for people's mothers. I mean, really, I mean guys
Well, some people have played show for the mothers, but yeah, it takes a really cool mom
You know, I don't maybe it's not really cool, but I don't think. Oh, it's really marathon night
it's a
Dungeon waffle dungeon wife delay the wife's life dungeon with dungeon wife. Oh, I don't know
When it's been good enough on night. Oh, wow
I don't I don't I don't even know it's you know, it's been guli me is that it's not like Boba Boba Boba goo
Is it like there's something in like a you know, I tell you deli or?
No, okay. I don't know. I don't know it sounds like it's under the villain from you could do that
You want to have a swing movie marathon? We could do that
We can do it after the freak-off one night. They're like a horror horror fun
No, it's like it's one of those like have you ever seen God?
Have you seen I probably asked you it's called a goodbye uncle Tom
No, no, it's not something I would watch
Yes, it's an Italian movie. It's a one of those
Shocky mentories it's very interesting. You might think it's interesting. It's spirits. It'll trip you out. It's Italian
There's children by Italian
It's about basically it's about the slave trade and you know, and it puts it it kind of like puts it in like very graphic
You know, I mean, it's almost like a film like a documentary
Right that never happened. Yeah, I understand but that's like the first part of the movie
I don't want to deny stuff like you know, Michelle, but I'll say like yeah, it's a funny exaggeration, but uh, yeah
You know, yeah, you have to be careful with the denying stuff to happen. I don't know
I wasn't there. I wasn't there and I wasn't there but you know, and there are you know, psychological operations the government
Walk a moldy walk a moldy. I am a kukaracha according to beat up psyche. Can you read is the Psalms?
Like Tom 91 and then tell us they had a suck cock
OK. Well, Alex, close your eyes, stick out your tongue, and then just smile. Just smile, and then you'll feel something.
And then, alright, so now read us a song.
OK, read us a song. OK, I'll take it. Let me add it.
From the Bible. From the Bible.
Yeah, I will read for the Bibles, but someone who wants to say a word about it.
So you're mocking the Christian. You're literally mocking Christianity.
Okay, anyway, I don't know he's trying to like that always goes well, doesn't I'm not I'm not mocking anything
I'm like, I actually do want to read a song because I think the Bible Psalms are good and I don't think wrong
I'm not mocking Christianity or anything. You want to bring the wrath of the Holy Roman Empire?
Well, it will not happen my actually my uncle has had contacts with the Vatican. So I'm not really perfect
So yeah, he was the same kind of thing as like, you know, who's else of the canon?
There's some other cannons, okay, so it says okay, so this is a prompt as in Psalm 86. It says a prayer of David it says
Psalm 86 a prayer of David it says
Hear me Lord and answer me for I am poor and needy
Guard my life for I am faithful to you save your servant who trusts in you
You are my God have mercy on me Lord for I call you all day long bring joy to your servant Lord
For I put my trust in you. You Lord are forgiving and good abandoning
Sorry, sorry about abounding in love
And to those who call to you
Hear my prayer Lord listen to my cry. I hear you when I'm in distress
I call to you because you answer me
Among the gods there is
None like you Lord no deeds can compare with yours all the only one that you have made will come out and worship before you Lord
They will bring towards your name for you are great and do marvelous deeds you alone are God
Teach me your way Lord that I may rely on your faithfulness
Give me an undivided heart that I may fear your name. I will praise you Lord my God with all
I will glorify your name forever for great is the
your love toward me. You have delivered me from the depths and the realm of the dead.
Arrogant foes are attacking me, O God.
And ruthless people are trying to kill me.
They have no regard for you,
but you, Lord, are compassionate and gracious God.
Slow to anger, abounding in love and faithfulness.
Turn to me and have mercy on me.
Show your strength in behalf of your servant.
Save me because I serve you just as my mother did.
Give me a sign of your goodness
that my enemies may see it and be put to shame.
For you, Lord, have helped me and comforted me.
There we go.
That's beautiful, no matter what religion you are.
You can connect.
That was beautiful.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I hope that cleared the air, and I was, you know.
I don't know. I don't know. I want to say something to you in a rustic Italian, but I don't want to
Can you read a little about the spirit of destiny, do you know anything about the spirit of destiny?
Well, yeah, she was on the show the other day and the spirit of destiny
So you're talking about the fates, right? This is also called, you know
They're called the Norns and the Norns in a Nordic belief, but they're called the fates and there's these you know the power of three
We're talking about there's the
Made mother crone these three is a very powerful also Hecate is one of the triune goddesses
This is like, you know, she is these three aspects that guard that different spaces across her. So I have my hecate thing
I was just gonna show you
Because they're talking about fate and you know, I think that's one of her names is you know, she's associated with
Oh, you're talking about you're talking about Kabbalah, the spear of death. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
Be like a lightsaber or something like that. I was probably some fake relic like all the rest of the work
No, I don't think so. I mean what if you didn't win the war?
I mean, so he was on the way and then he lost it
Well, the spirit destiny malfunction, what's going on? He needs his
Money back on just New York. Okay, so
It's like you give you high blood pressure. You put a button on your headphones and say a beep. I'm coming back to earth
Beat mm-hmm. No, I will not be doing that. I don't even know what that means
You want to ask when to work for a fellow white Christian or colonized? Okay? Well, I'm I don't know what's going on
You know, let's say, you know, we're all
Uh, we all have white eyeballs that our eyeballs are usually white on some of them. I mean, let's we all have
Oh, you mentioned that could say Bobby's into that. You said he's a priest
Yeah, but oh, yeah, so Bobby is a priest. So yeah, he didn't mention. Yes, then I know
I'm very familiar with Tech of Day and said, yeah, you can you know, there are
No, she's a goddess of magic and so of course, you know, there'll be the good
You know, and also the goddess
Yes, because she's kind of like, you know, she's kind of like a rich kid gal or she's like, you know
Kind of like she runs around with a bunch of ghosts and demons and you know
She kind of is like a ruler of hell. It's kind of more akin to Lilith. I would say, you know
but
You know, she is they
You know, she guards the crossroads. She's like also this liminal figure that kind of takes you between life and death
She's also a very powerful shapeshifter and illusionist and a lot of what we see may just be some the magic, right?
That's where the power comes from
Right, so he channels it from there. You don't channel it from there. You channel it from other places
Hey, you're talking to you're talking. You're not you're putting words in my mouth. Bobby channels it from Hecate. You channel it from somewhere else
Well, I don't know what that's really none of your business where my you know, I think I you know
I would I would say yes
I have a relationship with the you know the father and the mother and it's like you know, I even you know have a
You know, I'm a fondness for Kali, but
Yeah, but you know Kali has a lot of different
There's something called the Mahavidya. There's these 10
Forms of the gods so there's you know, there's Kali, but there's also Tara and Tara's a very compassionate form of that
There's also one called Kamala and the Kamala is also very
No, no, no, it's not the same person as the calm. It's in the Inga. And so there's also like Bagala Muki and there's Matangi
There's a
There's one that called Chinamasa that actually cuts off her own head and then drinks the head is drinking the blood and everything and
They're staying on top of this corpse. I mean, I mean
It's very hardcore. Yes, very morbid. It's awesome. There's also these like, you know
People call the agoris in India. They're their devotees of Shiva the way to and they do they'll do the
the very worst things in the world, they'll do cannibalism, they'll do feces, they'll cover themselves in dead ashes,
sometimes in cremation grounds, and yeah, I'm going to say these things.
What about Ganesh? You know Ganesh?
Yes, Ganesh is like, basically Ganesh is like, you know, he's the lord of all the animals,
but he's also the lord of the goddess.
No, that was my Indian waiter.
Oh, cool. Oh, please come on. Yeah, I don't I don't think they well sometimes they do use the gods names because they
You see there's not as many gods. There are people basically, you know
I think God
Yeah, be careful, you know careful with that. It's a very powerful fiery name of fiery name
Okay, so it's you know, you don't want to like start laying fires everywhere, but you know, it's a good mantra to
We come familiar with also it's like she has a very I mean a lot of the
The Abbot's hearts maha vigils are not big fans of marriage or having children or men or it's a typical
divine feminine life
but
There is a there's a very maternal aspect to her that I've seen and she's a she's very
Very a mama bear energy. So thank you. You said Amanda is my
Bad bad old buddy. What's there? I don't I didn't say that you were talking to me in the chat
Leave me out of it, please
I know you're bad. Oh, you're like, you know, I
You're count the bill buddy. I don't know just just one people one person looking out for you in the chat
Can you say a prayer for Sebastian? He's in a lot of pain right now
Of course, I want to get your bad paper a little back. Okay. You're gonna give some pain. Okay. Hold on
We're gonna say a prayer. Oh, I'll find a prayer
I want to give a good prayer for Sebastian really hurts
Prayer for pain. Well, you know
pain is
Often to get our attention about something
It's a perception okay, so pain prayer. Okay, it says why are you gonna say that?
Because I'm just saying that sometimes something is painful. It's like saying oh have a look at this area
Sometimes it's a symptom rather than the problem. It's like it's like showing that there's bringing attention to something
It's also, you know, if we didn't feel pain, we would not be able to get very far
So it says free says this is a prayer from freedom from sickness and pain. So it's your blessed Lord
I don't want to thank you for me having no legs
Yeah, that's my helpers. This might this is for you two goddesses your blessed Lord
Oh, but I really need you now. Oh, Jesus, you are the great physician. I seek your healing touch reach out over me
Send your spirit to heal me lift my natural defenses
relieve my pain restore my health and above all else. Oh Lord heal my soul lift me up inside knowing that no matter what happens
I'm your child. I'm your beloved and my place in your heart is secure all
This thanks to the Lamb of God who has also suffered taking away the sins of the world Christ heals all wounds
He relieves all pain and dries my tears.
You are my restoration, dear Lord.
You are my salvation.
Bring me from sickness and pain
by the grace and mercy of Almighty God.
In Jesus' name, amen.
Amen.
Yeah.
Yeah, the war as I saw someone's mentioning it. So the war is in Ephesians
It says something about war. It's very interesting. It says in Ephesians the Apostle Paul describes this a spiritual battle
That believers face not against physical enemies, but against what your forces of evil
The past is often referred to as the armor of God teaching where believers are instructed to put on spiritual armor to withstand these attacks
Okay, and so it is like there's you know, the armor of God is you know, there's like the know the sort of truth
He sees himself as a holy crusader
Who does who does he's the best of Sebastian?
Well, you know, it's like you don't want to be like Joan of Arc because you know good things or bad things happen to her because she
listens to too many of these voices that maybe we're trying to
Lead her the wrong way, but the poison burn her as a witch
Yeah, yeah, I heard a hair tick. Yeah
Hair sick. She was she was I think 14 or 15 years old. That's where she led a whole army, you know
Love children children's army by the way. So
What is the best thing for?
Hold on. I can't read some of these comments because they're insulting. It's as much about to get a little icy hard and calm down
Were you but maids are muscle relaxers. Oh, hold on
But mason's are muscle relaxers. Yeah, mason's states
Well, I love you. I really might you I swear you don't have legs guy dude really
I mean, I know you're I heard you were maybe in a you know, we'll survive here. You have to have your your amputee
Why are you doffing my no legs? I'm not I'm asking. I don't know
Why do you repeat things you see down there all the time? I'm not even this review. I'm just asking you
I'm sorry, but nobody knows. Oh good. Okay
Okay, there's nothing you see and I've been it's like, you know, it's like
He said like you're managing just fine in the I'm not ashamed of it
But I don't need everybody know my business
I'm not trying to tell you business
I asked you and you've you've also mentioned it on on my show before in the panel before you know
I have to be carried to the toilet every time I have to go
Who does that?
You said there's just a woman on the TV talking I have nurses
Okay, he talked to one of them
I want to see how yeah hold on hold on okay guys you're gonna get the nurse
Hello hello this Rosa. Why are you gay? Uh-oh, okay a wrong number
Oh
That didn't go well guys. I didn't go. I don't know how long have you been gaudy?
Okay, thank you. Oh, I was I know
Terribly rude. Yeah, I told you not to go there
well, I'll go I'll go I'll go over the guy I want to go and
You know my show. It's my show. I'll go wherever I might mine my my show
My show mine. I share my toys. It's like I'm not like a person that says, oh
You can't come on my show. You're you're not welcoming. I always go. Hey everyone can cut everyone's everyone come in
Once the 40s everyone no
People say oh
Like I'm selfish. I'm trying this. I'm trying to show you good about you, but you share the wealth
You know, you know, like one of the best was that awards the whole show
Fucking kicks people off the panel for no reason. You know one of those. Well, I mean I I mean I have to develop the panel
But not for like, you know, but it's not for long
Yeah, I'm usually very forgiving. I think I've been banned from chess, you know, the first time I've been on the chats
To this day, I'm still banned and then I can do about it. You know, it's like so, you know
It's like who really cares where you're which hat you can go into. You know, you can just go and alternate accounts
Okay, psyche which past food did you get with food? Yeah, I didn't I just had leftovers. I
had leftovers today, so
It's uh, I gotta make an appointment. Yeah prescription people pretty backstage are calling out a person. That's all you
That is say about our boy
I'm being full of respect with all of you that stuff. Oh, I'm sorry
system, what do you think?
you'll do
The butt burger you said the butt yeah ass burger
You made yourself
Episodes of a South Park where Cartman he wants you to see people getting attention for having Tourette's
And so I guess he takes having all time or none. Oh, I know not Alzheimer's is um, you know, um, it's the other one
It's uh
I don't know. Um, what is it? We're just talking about it. She said it, right? It's that uh
Asper, asperger so asperger's and so then he starts putting the burgers in his butt and he starts selling me
Everyone likes that everyone's up there is great. Yeah, it's really great, but it's like
You know, it's just like it's just like the
All the concentrated gag gas from all like the different cashews. Yeah, you went into one horrible
You know
Sauce so I don't know then yeah, that was a good episode though. Let's see that
Um
Yes, oh, no, I think it's still good, you know
They actually have made some like hour-long hour-long episodes and it's a bit on the paramount network
There are a comedy center. We did a little deal with
Paramount Network see some episodes there. So there's a few of them there
Yeah, that's the kind of lackluster, but the
Boy, there's no way you're gonna be a fireman. You can't carry 400 pounds. You gotta carry 400 pounds deadlift
Well, I think my my ex-girlfriend weighed about 400 pounds on that
I think I was I was stood her rolling over on me in bed. So maybe I can qualify the firefighter
That's what triggered you, huh?
No, no, I was I mean, no, I'm not sure me. I was I was seeing a fact. I did date a four pound woman and she did
No, she was rolled over on me when I woke up one day monica and no is it was it was Linda you gotta watch out for a Linda
Yeah, and
Yeah, watch out for those lindas guys. Let it gets around
Yeah
Certainly does I think yeah, it's the same
Whatever whatever Linda it is the same lens. I mean it's like Linus are all the same. They're kind of like there's some other care and energy
Little bit hornier Stephanie. What's your nationality? Oh, yeah, hold on Stephanie or your time with the Bastion or stuff
I don't know Stephanie. Stephanie. Yes
German
Yeah, German good and talk. I the reason is
I think I have close to no
The one through me for a loop. I thought the German. I know well, you know, I can't help out Polish and a little bit of Mongolia
Well, yeah, with the Mongolian that
Mongolians came through to Mexico or not or what is now South America of Mexico the Chinese actually went there
Mixed with the the natives and the Spanish and now we have Mexicans are the best best people in the world
Love Mexicans
Actually, the reason was attracted to that strange
See
Oh
Mexico
Yeah, song god. I'm gonna sing with me. Oh, Mexico
Thunder this we're every time I go
Margaret
Fish tacos. It's where I want to go home. That's Mexican radio. You're singing
You know spray spray out a
I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on. I'm on
Toxin but mostly they'll just cuddle up and be nice and furry and wonderful
Yes, you know, I know he's like you should invite Gita. So you talk makes your hair
I don't know. I she was here and then she wanted she was wanted like me down and stuff
I don't know. She's a she she likes me one day. She hates me and I didn't do anything
I was that I was trying to be diplomatic just it they give you the poor cat is rubbing up all over him
He's like, can you move him? Oh, he's allergic. He needs to get the claritane
Get me a little blame him stuff. He nobody wants that
You go just in search the search David if you start if you shave the cat, you know, it will have like less of this at the
hours
It'll look adorable. It looks just like that the stinks cats. They're just the most charming charming looking cat
They're actually very sweet. They get cold. There's no hair. So they get kind of cut a little more
So he's just oh come on
The cat is not into them. Well, that's a very big insult. Okay. The cat is cock walking. Well, that's what they're for
Justin give
Yeah
Wait till the cat falls asleep and then and then it's like, you know
Then pet the other cat. I don't know. Sorry. That was Boulder home. I cast this first
Let's flag after a year and a half. Whoa. Oh my gosh, Justin's first first flag. Oh my gosh
I was I was many I've seen as many red flags this past year than they sell it all the party cities combined
Okay, so
Oh, I mean it doesn't have my ass. What what does that mean?
Wait, why are you being so good?
Ziggy it's like you being weird
Nobody else is even saying anything strange. You're talking you said a man. It doesn't have my ass
What does that mean?
Actually a carnival over here with hair. Oh
What is it? What is it? He's like he's like the Lord of misrule or something like that
Now it's a Mardi Gras. What he's the new the new king of
Comus or something like that. I don't know. What's going on here? I
I'm actually there
Carnival, yeah, yeah, there's Carlos in Brazil. There's one in New Orleans that's full of voodoo and and uh, no
Yeah, I think you should take that job. You know who Coleman, you know, you know the God comas is
Thomas there's a God named comas and
Coman comas is actually the guy. He's like he just I think you'd like him. He's the very uh
interesting character, so there's something called the crew of Comus that's in the Mardi Gras, that's kind of like what the crews are called, but it says,
Comus is, let me see, it says, I didn't put it as a god, hold on, he is a certain kind of god, let me see, it says,
Comus, in Greek mythology, Comus is the god of festivity, rebels and nocturnal dalliances.
Cupbearer of the god Dionysus, he was represented as a winged youth or a childlike stature.
This mythology occurs only in later antiquity. During his festivals in ancient Greece, men and
women exchanged clothes. He was depicted as a young man on the part of the point of the unconscious
Dionysus stales the revels of the little islands of Andros and his ship now
More than the harbor, he leads a mixed throng of Satorai, Satyrs, and Bacalantes, and all
the Selenoi, the silence.
He leads the Gilos, laughter, and the Komos, revelry, two spirits, most gay, and most fond
of thinking about, or drinking about, that which may be great to light, may be...
they reap through the rivers harvest, okay?
And it says something, one more thing.
It says, there's been a number of,
Things meant said about him. Okay. I just know that he would he's like this part kind of like it says in Renaissance times
an allegorical painting of the reign of comas was begun by
Montenegro for the studio of Isabella the best day the paint picture comas is a ruler of the
Land of Baca Nile seated on the left of a company of Venus and Cupid
Beside an in yet of the sea inlet inlet of the sea John Milton's later
mask of comas
Inbends a new genealogy for the god describing him as
Thirsty and I sent this figure here as suggested in coast as allegory to the attempts to seduce a virtuous lady
whom he has kidnapped are only narrowly
Defeated by her brothers. So that's interesting. He's also the god of like, you know
He's like kind of like kind of like a low key kind of character where he have points out the gods
Downfall and pisses everybody off
So how many necklaces I don't know how many just the how many necklaces will you guys give me guys?
If I show you my my nipples, I'll show you them. So absolutely. His lady is eight. Yeah
But if you keep waiting for that, you know for onos was this his father
Yes, yes
He's the he's the father of you know all those gods and he swallowed them up and then his wife rea
But yet to destroy him to become leader
Yes, well, at first it was actually Uranus that was killed by Fronus, and then Uranus
turned into the foam on the sea, turned into Aphrodite and stuff like that.
And then Zeus eventually took down Fronus, because the same thing happened, they wanted
to maintain their rule without sharing it with anybody, and so he was afraid his kids
Yeah, but then he eventually vomited them all up and Athena was born out of his
His brain he had a really bad headache one night and she's popped out fully grown
Hey, I show you this picture that I took earlier this week. Okay, you took the pictures. It's your property
Is it a little bit of a disdain on Justin's face? Look at the disdain when he saw what his girl was doing
They look like AI. Look how disgusted he is with her in that fucking photo. That's who is that?
That looks like that's some dirt photos. That's not that looks like
That is really disgusting isn't it let's say aliens look at that's what Justin knew that he made a big mistake
What is she doing? She's, she's, oh, she's, oh, she's picking her nose. Yeah. Digging for gold and he's looking at her like, oh, man.
I mean, she's, I mean, she's a gold digger. Oh, I get it. A gold digger? Yes. No, no, no.
She's a gold digger boy. Oh, he's, fuck this. It's a very, it's just been a very unfortunate coincidence that they have the same meaning.
Oh, look at this thing. He's very sexy, even though it's a shirt off. Oh, look. Speaking of gold diggers. I usually am not wearing a shirt.
My sexy Samoan.
Well, you're always wearing a hat and that horrible be a step. You just got Gotti
Hey Stephanie
the
It's I'm sure it's not as good as New York pizza or like, you know, you know, it's not as good as New York pizza
But the value of the astronomical wonderful you get it you get an 18 inch pie
For $11. Well guys, you know, you can like sneak into one of the 10 they have displayed before closing time
You can get free up to places day for the night. You can see you can live in the Walmart
Amazing guys. Yeah, it's just really good. See here's the thing the Costco hot dogs are pretty good
However, you can buy those same in the same thing with the pizza
You can also buy a raw and not cooked. You can buy a not cooked pizza
And just and it's I think it's over a price nobody
The same thing with the hot dogs, Costco's hot dogs are like number one.
Nobody cares about pizza and hot dogs right now, okay?
This is a very, very dumb conversation.
You don't like pizza and hot dogs?
Well, it's not because, I mean, we're rating our Costco's food now.
Guys, come on, guys.
You gotta try them.
Look, you're telling me that you don't have a membership?
I'm not gonna try them.
You said you don't have a membership here, either.
So why are you like...
You know you can...
You have any friends that have one?
No, I don't have any friends. He doesn't have a membership here. You don't have any friends to have a membership
I know friends to have a membership here. I know I know you do
So I know
You can ask your friends for a pass
Costco and then you can get stuff in the food court. Okay guys. Hey kids. He forgive my
Dogs you should I use are you sake you should get hot dogs and pizza?
OK. Maybe if you're in California, they also have churros. The churros are amazing.
And you can eat Krispy Kreme donuts, too. And then it's like you'll be really full.
I think some of them you can get donuts, too.
You can put pizza sauce and cheddar cheese and mozzarella onto a Krispy Kreme donut.
And it's like a sweet pizza bagel.
Have you ever had a chicken bake?
No, I'm not really the chicken
You don't like chick. Are you a vegetarian? Are you vegan? No, I'm more into beef and the fish
Okay, it's like a little bit
It's too plain for me. I have occasionally that's so food bombing, haha
I remember if you guys any like real Costco heads out there in chat
The real Costco heads remember when they had they used to do an ice cream bar
I'll be a woman and then they would hand-dip it in
Chocolate oh my god guys and put nuts on it. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god
Yeah, if you're not still you're that was this lemonade guys. That was lemonade. Yeah, so I'm not I'm not hungry for pizza or
Or hot dogs ever again. Okay, so you ruin it for me, okay? I barely like what I have a donut anymore
Damn you. Okay, so anyway, you're gonna put it in your
But for oh my god, but
Okay, if you can put it in your brain guys, you guys are being disgusting hey guys, please
Your butt
Yeah, let's not put food in our but I mean it's nasty dude
The no wonder Boyle can't keep up
It's a woman. I hear I hear that. Is that her talking? Is he like on the phone or something?
I hear the people do the leave alone here. I hear I hear
They're fighting. That sounds like her. Oh, it is her. It is her. Oh, it's domestic violence. Oh my gosh
Well, God, you don't play this is their private fights
Don't let them fight
Guys hold on do you need to help?
Stephanie just wink wink twice come on panel just blinked twice at me at all
I hate fighting I come from
I don't like fighting either, but a lot of people from abusive homes are
To fight all the time. They should just knock each other out. That's sad. That's done
I was lucky not to that's why I get triggered when I'm on your panel and everybody's fighting, you know
Well, I'm sorry. I don't mean to trigger you and there's there's you know, there's always gonna be this complex in the world
And I thought this is a safe space. Well, you know, it's you know, you can only escape is you know the people inside the
There's you know, the lunatics that occasionally sneak in what can I do if you know, they they go not see
Than their nature to do so six bad. I mean say
Why did I kick stick off with he's annoying me for some reason guys? Can you remind me why I kicked him off?
I haven't really remembered
Fucking beer that yeah, yeah, I think he was like the fighting his yes, yeah
I don't know if you're fighting the beard is very insulting. I know it's like it should be you know
They might neatly braided into like, you know, the the cultural
You know, so Samoan knots on it and he just has a growing like a it's vulgar
It just hangs there like like I don't even know it's just really nasty. Oh
Sick come on. Okay good
Come on. It's too bad. I mean, I'm trying to do better. You better too. Hey, we're actually got these caregivers
Yes, we are guys one step. It takes a village, right guys. It takes a village to raise a gaudy or to
at least keep them
keep them from, you know, trying to take over the world
so it says, okay, so here's, oh, butt plugs, butt dugs, oh no, well butt chubs, okay
well that's in your way to, it's in your way to do it
you boil fire
Yeah, well, you can't fire them Goddy because it's unfortunately
I think they're I think they're inside these years seniority over you because she has the MD. No, they're fired
Well, I mean, it's like yeah, I figured out that I figured out the hierarchy already. I mean, I'm pretty good
She's not a nurse to the MD is she I'm not sure
Okay, I'm starting when it go where
You're gonna wheel him into traffic. Oh my gosh
Bunky you're not going to do anything. I'll all wheeler. He says that I mean, I'll wheel I'll wheel you back out of track
I'll will you add a check. Thank you. She will do in there. I'll put I'll push you back to the side
I underestimate how good you were can I
access to your to the wireless of your electric wheelchair so I can
I'd play Frogger. Wow, that's great. Yeah. Oh, you play Frogger. Okay, so a fragger
You said it's a frog and a fragger Frogger. You would never go play Frogger. Okay
Pac-man I play one game. I play it's called gardens garden escapes and it's like you
It's been garden and it's like, oh my gosh, it's taken forever to build this garden
But you do a little match match game match for you
Hi, Lola, Lola's come in and say hi to Gotti. Lola, show Gotti your, show Gotti your Gotti faces. These are, these are Gotti faces.
Lola.
That's how gangsta looks like you.
Welcome Lola, welcome.
Yep.
Okay.
Yeah, she didn't like that.
No, she doesn't. No, she doesn't. Look, she's right here. She doesn't, she doesn't, she doesn't like saying hi to you.
I just say, oh, she doesn't want to say hi to Gotti, but say, be nice to him, he's nice, he's nice, okay.
Oh, she's like, no, okay, I'm sorry Gotti.
No.
I don't want to bother her about your voice, but I'm sure I'm
personal. Hey, did you get a man? Stephanie, I never told you
this, but uh, Boyle told me that if anything ever happened to
you, he would make Mongolia's butler.
Okay, well, this is some kind of inside joke.
Not funny. Oh, sorry. You didn't know that one. Mongo is Stephanie's son. Oh, okay. Okay, Stephanie. Yeah, okay
So, okay. Well, it's kind of weird you say that better son, but okay anyway
I'm you guys you guys can uh, you guys have your relationship. I meant to do it
Dingle you were the only one with me in this job interview spirit. Oh just that's what they call him. Oh, okay
That's what she calls them
Yeah, well, it's not very nice. It's awesome. I mean she should know I mean she's she said she's part Mongolian, right?
down mongol down
Okay, well
Yeah, maybe it's time to everyone's been a little bit too silly on the panel. We'll see he I don't know I do it's awful
Oh my gosh. Hi Lola
It's he's a mongo jr. I
They call him dumb dumb. Oh, well, yeah
No guys, some people aren't very nice
People that are gonna talk behind your back and they're gonna think oh well this person's so stupid
They don't even they don't understand we're talking behind their back, but you know sometimes a person will know
Sometimes the person
Will gesture this like kind of quiet anger
Might come out. It's the worst was inappropriate times. Why don't call him down? Oh, yeah, never never don't yet
Go just look what you're doing. You're spreading joy. Okay, but anyway, that's enough with the conversation. Okay, I
don't like
Gaslight I don't like gaslighting very much
Having a version to it. I have it's kind of like little
little
It's only four weeks left of money can afford. Okay. I don't I don't know
All these all these comments are being made all these accusations got you got you're not you're not being nice to me
We're you're being
Cool cool
Yes, let's see. I rubbed while there's not cats. Well
Where did I eat? I usually see you eat something
I'm drinking a beer. I had me something to eat today. I had some leftover burger
Look I got you're saying that you're body. It's gonna be my fault to you. It's gonna be like, oh, here's what the fuck?
What's the fuck?
Like you
Come at me like Tony's the Prano, you know
Got the wrong order of you know pasta Mar-Nar, right?
The mozurel and then you know, you're like, I want a red pepper and it's like
Like I'm sorry, sir. Then you want to put a hit on this. Let's die on the diner. I don't like it
I hate where I do that, I don't think you do.
I keep dropping the phone in my face.
I'm sleepy.
Well, I keep dropping the phone in the chats,
or not the chats, in the panel space.
Yeah.
I did delivery, yeah, I deliver comments.
I deliver fresh contents.
And it was, unfortunately, it delivers too expensive
That's tobacco is too expensive. So I have in 24 hours. I have smoked
Yeah, well, where is the home?
I think I don't have it. Where is it? I had it. Oh, I think it's yeah, this is what I have left of it
I've got too much tobacco. Okay. Okay. Okay
Hello, Chinese food Chinese food
Hey, you want some Mongolian Mongolian food and that's all I wish I could get a job
I need to make money or I'm going to be starving off. Okay. Yeah guys
I really there's a website called snag a job.com. There's also that you know, I believe I'm working from home
She said should you get spunked? Oh my god? I don't even want to go full show you're running here
Oh, who's talking to you, buddy? I'm talking to ghost. Okay ghost. Hey, please answer your god. What I do
You know what you did dumb dumb?
All right
Like this time to apologize, you know you say that like you're gonna kick me off the panel site
I don't like that tone. You fucking just said who you talking to God. Who you talking to?
Are you talking to me? Are you talking to me, man?
Am I talking to me I love when you fucking about panel hosts try to show off for the rest of the fucking audience
My fucking expense that's never gonna fucking happen
Oh, please
There's a Costco pizza back there. There's a Costco piece. Yeah, nobody wants that Costco pizza shit
So yeah, it's just recommended it's those are so highly, you know, we spent like five minutes talking about it
I couldn't get off of my mind
Yeah, you must have thought it was very relevant to conversations to bring up, you know
Costco pizza
No, okay. So Anna minute. You're my uh bottle be my
Hold on you're in it
You're my battle be my battle. Oh
No, hold on. That's not nice that you stop it
Helen they're super amusing. Yeah, I'm very confused but it's chat. Are you talking to me?
I didn't go yet. No, I just did right there. Hey, if I listen to you or you get some stuff that I know
I hope to be entertaining
Hey, are you talking to me?
I'm here you must be oh, no never money just one you're my bad at home guys
Come on. We don't want to fight battles. We want to we want to win the war. Okay?
Wars because it's been it's a guy's a spiritual war not a
Material war
It's all wars
The know it doesn't good wins because a bad one then there would be no life
It would be destroyed because life is actually the only good thing left here home
They're assigned to be our battle buddy psyche. Okay battle buddy. Yeah count the billet buddy
He wants to be my
Battle buddy for some reason
Well, I know you're very
Maybe he's he's smart and he just knows that you're a good fighter, right Justin. Did you use you're a free Willie won?
1994 you see free Willie Justin Justin you see free Willie
Willie
Remember that there's like a killer whale
You know I almost fell on the film the kid luckily
He tried to jump high enough, but the movie whacked. I was it was sad. Yeah
Billy died. Did you kick ghosts off or do you just leave?
Ghosts if you're like Casper you got offended
No, no, no, I hate to call somebody a dumb dumb and they get offended
No, he well, I think you know, I think he's being sued by the dumb dumb, you know
Candy company right now for overusing their trade mark. So no, it's not his Lee is worse
So most goodies goodies. Yeah, JT. Yes, you're the most goodiest, right?
So, let's talk about guys, let's talk about being, like, thinking for yourself.
That's what I would love people in this world to be able to think critically about.
This is a can of fallacies.
Okay.
I want to say that.
I don't want to say that comment.
I won't say that comment.
Okay.
I'll respect you for that.
But I do have this, I do have this, like, list of, like, you know, these logical fallacies.
We all are guilty of, you know, some of these logical fallacies.
There should be a short little list, if I could find it.
Logical fallacies, whatever it is, okay.
Okay, so it says, okay, it says,
mental traps and thinking errors.
So these are kind of chronological fallacies.
So number one is cognitive dissonance.
conflicting beliefs. So if you like believe like, oh, you know, this person is a good
person, and then you believe, oh, this person is the devil. It's like you're going to have
like a little conflict in your mind about trying to figure out which is probably some
more in the middle, right? Okay, then it's a spotlight. It says,
So there's a spotlight mental trap. So people think oh, I'm in the spotlight. So whatever is happening right now is very well
So it's like, you know, it's self-consciousness. That's who we're so self-conscious. We're gonna be biased
You know, we're gonna have a bias there. Okay, three anchoring effects. This is information
presented
effects thinking about it
So it's bias comparisons assumptions
Magnet
Negotiational negotiating prices, etc
All these things are anchored in and so it's like the as you learn information
You'll start developing the bias based on what you hear right?
And we have the halo effect it says more more weight is given to the first things mentioned
It's called the honeymoon phase. You know the honeymoon phase always comes first. It says e.g. variation in grades
It affects the first impression, okay?
So then there's the gambler fallacy, gambler fallacy, illusion of prediction based on what just happened.
We say, oh, I just got five black cards in a row, I should be getting a red card, but that's the logical fallacy.
Okay, we also have contract effect, so it's value based on comparison, or the contrast.
So comparison, so there's a value based on comparison, this is the bias.
Then there's the confirmation bias.
It says the filter into the suggestion
is with current beliefs, echo chambers.
The repetition is effective.
So repeat a lie often enough,
it'll start to become the truth, right?
Okay.
Then we have the beta,
beta,
the Bader-Mannhoff phenomena.
It says it's increased awareness leads
to coincidental pattern recognition.
And so sometimes these things that we think are these,
you know, big coincidences or just actually coincidences
are not like some sign, but sometimes they are.
We have just three more left.
There's 10 paradox of choice.
It says too many choices to make decisions are more difficult.
So the more choices you have,
the more difficult is to make a choice, right?
So you really want a more limited choice.
You can make it easier choice, right?
If you have too many choices, it's hard to decide.
Then we have the survivorship bias.
It says that data represents
represented doesn't necessarily include best known info.
Focus is only on...
The winners right so there's a survivorship River survives the business of ever they'll say oh here's the example
It's the follow but it's kind of a bias right and it says two more says self-serving bias
It says success equals our action and failure is added rules actions, right?
So nothing's our fault and the number 13 is the hindsight bias. I knew that would happen
So what do you think guys that interesting? I did write that down
It writes us down. Hey Tommy. How are you? What is it? I talking about I'm Joe
I'm talking about these logical fallacies and these you know people believe all kinds of things the based on very
The called it's very
And tenuous information or tenuous or
Something now it's my turn to read something do you mind? Okay? You've been reading all fucking night. Can I get
Five minutes. I'm gonna read something psych as soon as you guess what I'm reading. I'm gonna stop reading. Okay. Okay reading Dante's inferno
No, no, I don't start. Yeah. Can I start?
Yeah, I was guessing after all right ready. I'm getting ready
All right, here we go
Whoever guesses it I'll stop
Say St. Paul's churchyard for instance literally to astonish your son's weak mind
St. Paul's church never painted out the name they stood years afterwards above the warehouse door
The firm was known as sometimes people knew to the business calls
No, it's no they sell that's what the thing was right. I'm not done
And sometimes but he answered to both names. It was all the same to him
Okay, oh god of the devil right no no, but it was a tight-fisted hand at the grindstone
A squeezing wrenching grasping, scraping, clutching, covered his old sinner hard and sharp as flint,
from which no steel had ever struck out generous fire.
Secret
And self-contained and solitary as an oyster, the cold within him froze his old features,
made his eyes red, his thin lips blue, and spoke out shrewdly in his grating.
Moby Dick.
No, a frosty rhyme was on his head, and on his eyebrows, his wiry chin.
He carried his own low temperature always about him.
He iced his office in the dog days, and didn't thaw it one degree at Christmas.
Oh, it's a Christmas Carol. Oh see that one word. It only took one word for you to get it
Christmas time. Wow. It's your bedtime story. I like it. It's Charles Dickens, you know, you leave out certain words
You never get it
Well, you know, and you know, that screws, you know, he actually, you know, he did learn a big lesson, you know
You can't take it with you
I'm going to blow your load, please don't do that in my chat, Luke, it's disgusting.
What you say, load?
I have a load, I can show you that.
No, Ziggy, Ziggy, Ziggy, Ziggy, we can read, we can read Christmas Carol in our own
time, okay, I cannot have it.
Christmas in July.
Hello.
Oh God, oh God, roses are red, violets are black.
You look good with a knife in your back, what the fuck you're pulling at, no.
Okay, well guys guys, okay, I think it's time for a little break on the pan. I think it's time for a little break, okay?
Very nice, you know, what why are you reading my screws? She's being scroogey. Who's being scroogey, Gotti? It's being scroogey, okay?
I don't know who's being screwed. I don't know. What's the point? What's Christmas in July? I
I already saw that that guy Lars or whatever. He looks like that's like Santa Claus
I've had my Christmas in July, but I really don't even care for Christmas anymore very much
Why did I kick Goddy? That was awesome. Oh that was home
Do they have sex in romance novels?
Why did I kick him out because I feel like it. I just feel like it. He's he's
Give me an uncomfortable feeling
Chunky is always, ignores a nickel.
Cherokee always ignores just a nickel.
Northern nickel, I don't know what that means.
Ah, Alceruna, yeah, he did.
Tommy loves the trans, probably.
Amber, no.
Okay, Amanda, yes, okay.
Ah, Amazon days in July, basically Christmas in July.
Okay, well, it was Christmas at the beginning, you know.
The Amazon sleigh, dropping gifts at my house.
Not me having to
Pay for the you know these packages, but I just know they have to have good deals
huh
I'm just being exhausted. Yeah guys. I mean I
Got any ones to read depressing stuff. I can be Sylvia Platt. I'll put up it. I'll make everyone
Gonna go go to bed and cry. Okay, but I'm not gonna do that. You're going to bed. Good night
See Goddy, I can Goddy and you're making everyone's you know
Yeah, you
Spoiled the mood
Bye smoke. I'm just kidding. Hey, this one's a good one though. I mean I'll lay you back up God. It's just like
Why
Why you're so perfect so perfect
Infallible
And I'm so flawed. I mean, I'm just so
Might as well be talking about God on the pillow, right?
You're just perfect
I'm so evil
I'm actually I'm actually not for you. I mean, it's like maybe a little bit but not evil and like a yeah
Human beings or y'all we're all I have a little bit of a dark side, right?
I'm not a
You want to
Hey, hey, hey, hey, and you know what it's just like
Why
Why are you guys coming like I'm not talking to everybody talking to certain people
Why are you coming to my show to be like rude and terrible to me?
First of all, I never did any that's maybe I think yeah
Maybe I've kicked you off panels or kick you off the panel because you know got a hand that I've had it like yeah
I never did anything to you. You guys are just
Have this big glee with it hating me. It's the you know, it's just like it's these out of your pores
You can't hide it. It's like and so
No, I don't know you might it's a guy's taste a lot of energy to wear a mask
And that's why maybe now maybe I've been like no had a lot more energy and like
If you had less energy because you know just maintaining this mask is
Is a lot of his energy stopping? Okay? I don't wear a mask. I was I'm as embarrassing as I can be I mean
Embarrassing I'm like the bull can just let look at me laugh and point and just you know, just be the
laughing stock, okay
What else is there that's been my life, okay, so but
Yeah
Is it shows baby doesn't show space and yeah, these people are just mean they're not nice to me
he's
Insinuating I'm some kind of like evil miser is making these cryptic messages at Christmas in July
I don't like it. I know it's just gaslighting. I've been through years of, you know, my I'm key ultra through a Russian
Okay, they're the worst. I mean, they're the best at it, but it's like it's kind of the worst for
victims of it, but
I've been okay. I've been okay. Oh
God, so we have
If people backstage, I mean it's like God he's saying you could go smoke a cigar or something. I just need to
need to
Give me out of my element look at my eyes. Well, it looks so relaxed. I'm kind of high
Tell me you should think before you
Hit on okay. Well, hold on. Let me join. I don't know Tommy Jones hit on somebody
I know a dozen people hit on on page, you know recently and you know
kind of
Don't kind of bad for patient
Use they're a bit too much energy on negative stuff. Okay filthy, but look but look who I feel filthy
Look, I haven't look where I'm deal with. It's like it's amazing that it's not
much more negative, okay, I
It's surprising. I'm still having a smile on my face and again a good heart
Because most people would have said fuck this shit like that. I mean, it's like, you know, I'm
Maybe I'm a glutton for a punishment or a sucker for pain or something, right?
She's suffering from success and I feel bad for her too. Well, I wish her success. I mean, it's like guys
what's this about? It's like
suffering from
Well, I think she's successful too. She gets you know, she has more people in her chat than I have so I
Hope that's not too negative just on his observation control you take in right but it's hard because they're sitting backstage. I like them
They're just gonna say more
Negative shit like they're not it's not gonna be like oh, you know what you're doing a fucking good job. You're a good
You know, sometimes it's that and I'm like I always like
Then I'm sad guys. Sometimes we can't take any positive things said to us
We always like we'll doubt that but then we always will believe the negatives
That's how people will try to program this sometimes stop being weird
I'm being a weird thing there
I'm being weird. We see you were you were literally
Just on my panel being very very odd. Okay, we'll see what happens. We'll do it. Yeah, let's just uh, let's just throw caution to the wind
I'm just here because I want to have gay sex with psyche
Oh, I see you at the any through down three or four gold pieces on the threshold
You could tell I want to have gay sex with psyche. Okay. Well, yeah, okay, so there we go
We know I think not a not a respond not a conversation just more
Oh, let me have the spotlight and guys go to your own show. I mean, I know it's boring when I read stuff sometimes
Like I know I just read like a little whole page of the power cut interesting
I know it's boring every time you don't have to like then then it's very more boring. No one wants to hear the Christmas killer right now
it's in the middle of July the
Hardly even really want to see it around Christmas time. It's a little bit depressing and
And you know
Poor tiny Tim is never gonna, you know, it is Christmas turkey or I don't know. It's ironic that
It's meant to be
Positive good vibes yeah, I know it's not it's not ironic, but it's like that's what it's like when you have light
it will
Track darkness it will
see you didn't just hear he wasn't a part of that you're not hearing what he's
saying you think he meant wrestling he's not he's reading the Christmas Carol
wrestling what about wrestling I hope you put on a stocking and your name on
Christmas my stockings unfortunately don't get filled anymore they do the
probably piece of black hole I hope you yeah I don't have the stock anymore
And yeah, but the Bible quote I mentioned is that we don't wrestle with, you know, with the flesh and blood, we wrestle, this is wrestling, right?
So we wrestle with the principalities and the spiritual forces.
And the wrestling is also kind of a spiritual thing, too, because you're trying to pin something down, right?
You need one? It's talking to my name, yeah. It's okay. I barely even get a Christmas gift anymore.
Cause it's kind of a, I'm the funnest time, two times.
I did have some pretty epic stockings growing up though.
Yeah, now it's about, you know, it's just for fun.
Yeah, but I have, I have like 14 or 15
meets the nephews, so it is kind of like, wow,
it's like, you know, trying to, you know,
get gifts for all those people and let Goddy up,
that was big, Goddy was,
Hello, I mean psyche. Hello
This thou sense a tad of jealousy in your tone
Not at all. It's one of annoyance from like, you know, my noise
Yes, especially
Big British accent. I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm refraining from kicking you off because the chat is like oh the crowd turning on you psyche
Not not really. It's just one person said why you should maybe wait. I wanted at least five
That would be a long pin, so that'd be illegal in wrestling. I don't know. Maybe it's maybe it's the Turkish rules
I've never known you to be jealous man
I'm not jealous. I'm just I'm very annoyed because I'm trying to like run a show and like, you know
Of all the years I have known you. I've never known you to be jealous
God II you're really annoying me. Oh
It's not yeah, I'm not yeah, I'm not jealous my friend. Yes. I'm annoyed. I'm annoyed and it's like it's my show
You're supposed to annoy the host show. What do you mean by my show? What is this? My me me me me me me?
My my show
Nobody else is my it's my decision to bring on my decision to have my decision when to go out my decision when you go
My decision my decision my decision me I
Face the consequences of everybody else's action except you know, it's they don't so they don't care
It's a free fall on my channel to do what they want
But I can't do what I want on my channel because I'm more freedom than I do sometimes I need to trim up the beard
I will
Yeah, today you should beat yourself to a barber. Oh, you're messing with a barber. You're a trim. Yeah
Unfortunately the barbers are too expensive or quite expensive. I have a electric freezer. I can use
Yeah
Guys and why are people saying I think that's the thing. It's like no, I'm not jealous and it's like I'm guys
I'm the last person to be jealous. It's like I'm
I want everyone to have have whatever they want. I want everyone to be happy. I'm not it's like not a competition for resources
I'm it's like I never cared what other people had or not see that that's not that was important to me
So it's like that everyone's day. Oh
You know, Mr. Big Pie started saying why they went to jelly and then it's like now
It didn't it was sort of saying jelly and then it's like and then now they're saying gels. It's like no
Gels is what I
mean I experienced
The evil eye on me, which is the result of jealousy, you know, I feel like you know
Sometimes all this negative energy projected to me all the worst thoughts, you know
Projected that meaning like it basically is based on you know evil eyes based on Andy
most of the time right
but I
Know some I know some egg magic. So okay, can you can a tries like you like try?
I'm trying to get to sleep
He said try what though ambers on you. What did you say? Try what rev it up?
Have you been stressed like you have I've been from have I been stressed?
Sure, I've been stressed guys
Little bit stressed and so you know and so it's not
I think like I've let him I keep letting him up. He just start keeps reading
The book and I keep saying I'm Jake Chelsea. I don't even if it's not referring to me
It's just they keep saying it to me and I don't like it
Like it's them getting like the weirdness like oh
Again, it's like why do I keep like I'm like I'll keep it giving in here. I'll bring my he's gonna say that
They're saying I'll talk off here. What go ahead
What
Yeah, what what the answer is the answer is
Come again come again. Yes. I don't know what coming. I don't know what what what what in the but I don't know
It's like I kind of have conversations people are being very cryptic. Have a conversation. Go ahead
I'm trying to win everyone know everyone to talks in circles and it's like a lot of word salad. They get structured
I'm trying to have I read something for five minutes. You bugged out
Then bug out. I mean, I let you read it and then you know, then you had a nice or had a nice laugh
Oh, yeah, you know, it was all grease screws in the Christmas
You took it to heart you thought
You had a screw now you you create a
No
Tell him what I'm here to tell you shit. What the fucking wrong with you bro. Tell him look me rabbit. Oh
your skeletal from the 1980s
What's wrong with you you stupid team you you guys are retarded who you call them
But I've been watching for the past week my friend
and i see how stupid you are bro bro you spunky jp sneaky you're a little bunch of freaks
why are you fucking weirdo you're a bunch of freak motherfuckers yeah what there's no challenge
you better freak the fuck out you weirdo i'm just here to let you know it's over never started
This is what he wanted that you see this is this is what he really wanted
This was me or Alex you. Oh my god. All right, you you
I'm not I'm not lucky ability
Lifted I'm not that way. You're right. You think you're todo. I'm todo great wizard of
You're not you're not to you're not todo. I'm told you're no wizard
You're really more like you remind you're like the wizard, you know cuz the wizard was a kind of like, you know a flim flam guy
And then, you know, and then, you know, there's, you know, there's a thing that's kind of like the
What are you trying to say?
No, no, no, but also, no, the wizard is also, you know, the wizards
Are manipulators, basically, of society. They're a bunch of old crippled freaks for all of them. They're all crippled
This guy has fucking diabetes and a fucking hemorrhoid
They weren't you crying the other day, but you can't take a shit
I was taken shit. Yeah, a couple weeks ago. Yeah, a couple weeks ago. How tall are you motherfuckers and I'm
JT the nuts freak exactly
I'm so glad I got you both here now
Now I'm gonna juggle you to like my nuts. I'm gonna juggle you to like my nuts right now
like you what's going on
what's going on not this going on
you know what's going on
that's what's going on
your bullshit
is everybody having a good night tonight?
I'm having a great night. I'm doing fine. I'm doing fine. I'm having a great night
I was reading some Charles Dickens and
Dickens you can't read shit
Shut the fuck up with that bullshit you read
Bible and the verse shut up with that garbage. You're such a loser. You're such a bum
Shut up with that bum shit loser
read it on the verge of your stupid garbage
everybody wants to cool down a little bit
yo you guys think what you guys are like a little cult
you guys are a little occult
crew of losers
the Mormon
ah you Mormon losers
you guys believe in God you Mormon losers
what a
you guys are freaks
okay okay
you guys talk to your sister bro
you guys have incest
you guys talk to your own mother
no no no no stop
what's wrong with that
Alex stop it
like what
I told you don't
they got supposed to like
lander like whole communities
of people you know they actually
like they don't like that
it's against to us you know that
say Alex's diagnosis would be
if you were to oh yeah I think he has that poor impulse control probably you kind of like malignant
narcissism with like you know the you know psychopathy and like a little bit of Machiavellian
maybe someone his parents never listened to as a child an ascension seeker he wants attention
ADHD you know you know he probably is ecliptoid I don't know I don't know I don't want to diagnose
him but I mean it's like he stayed out of
Yeah, he became a cop so he obviously would be able to put as a is there anything he's a cop
This is here to guard he's a security guard. He might pop him
He's like he's like that. He's like that one that shows the parking lot the mall
He's not I'm gonna read another book for you ready. You tell me what it is. It was the best of times
It was the worst of how warm peace warm peace. Oh, wow. Wow right away
Yes, I know I know I know I actually know it wasn't war on peace. It was a oh my gosh
It is all right. Okay. Can we correct please God darn it Josh darn it? Okay?
We got it. Well, I'll get it right next time if there is the next time see if that's better than
I want to read anymore. I don't feel appreciated
Hi, I like I like when you read it's like
There was a once a woman her name was Mrs. McCabe. She had a 23 sons and she named them all Dave
That was kind of an unusual thing to do. I
can tell you their names, but I would take a
Long time. He's the guy was a screw ball. Yeah, what's the fuck is this crown thing on me?
That crown thing it means that you are the top one of the top supporters of my chat Ziggy congratulations
Well, you're one of the top three chatters tonight. He's been really active. He loved my love my show
He's so active in the chat. I think I'm number two
Yeah, you're number two number two
You know some people say that it's you know city position, but I think it's uh, it's number one
It's as good as number one. It's as good as number one. Okay. Oh, yeah. Oh, there you have to activate that
Or does that just happen?
I don't know. I didn't have to activate something activate like just doing some gifts
There's some kind of thing wave can get like some kind of rubies or something that I can buy
It's just kind of super chess or something with I don't know
Haven't seen the results for that. Yeah, I don't I just turned on one day. I keep opting into every kind of thing
I see
on the on the YouTube
On a seller page, so I don't
Did you see that?
Thank you come again
And well, yeah, because I think his area is sort of racist because he's not Indian
He wasn't racist at all. They were racist for bringing it out. I'm sure they were but I mean, you know
It's just that it's a part that didn't age well. Unfortunately. It'd be like really psyched. There's a lot of people like that in the world
So yeah, it'd be like
No, but how about how about how about how about the how about the Chinese guy that was like, oh, I know it was like
60s that there wasn't yeah, I'm gonna say
People by doing a nice caricature of these Indian people that would come over here and work
We were rewriting history
What's true, I mean I hear you know basically hear the
The world's like a basically a giant home home depot on the on the North Pole. I have no idea what's going on
Yeah, who the fuck knows you even care. There's really matters as long as they matters the matters
He's my favorite character on the show characters aren't real
It's a show. He was real to me. He doesn't say it's real to some people. Now. He's gone. His wife is gone. His kids are gone.
It's like believing in Papa Smurf and Murphy. It's like they're they're not ever gonna. Why are you bringing them up?
Well, why are you why you mentioned Smurfs? Because they're fictional. They're fictional characters.
Yeah, because there's no such thing as a Smurfs like you. We know that.
What's wrong? There are Indian American psyche that come here from another
Oh, I think I think need the Native American
The Hindu
I'll touch a meant the feather ones. Oh my gosh. Oh come on guys now. This is coming outrageous again
Yeah, I don't I don't I don't mean to buy an unique is you know word is all right. Yeah, it is completely outrageous
It's impossible.
The whole night has been kinda outrageous.
Mm-hmm. No, not me. It's like, you know, it's kind of a little bit above average night
It's got a nice 43 people in chat
You notice that he got jealous as soon as I was reading this fucking Christmas Carol
I'm reading his thing. You know that. Yeah. Yeah. No, okay. Okay. So both of you guys can go suck on your own dicks
I mean, please. I mean, what's the fuck? I mean, I'm done with it. Okay guys, just go away
Let's go away. I don't want to talk to you anymore tonight. Leave me alone
You're just insulting it. I'm not jealous. You have a green eyes, but
Yeah
Jealous, what am I jealous?
Jealousy is a
Mental disorder like why is anybody jealous? Everyone has the same thing a life
Everyone has the same thing opportunity. Everyone has the same thing, you know a breath a new day at some time
Some you know a village to walk or move a village to do anything right that we have given chance to live, right?
So
Not gonna hate on life or me or the world
Hello guys, yeah
Yeah, let's not be in a page up and page is probably pretty nice
What the heck? My thing's on it.
Okay, okay, it's fixed. It's fixed.
Oh!
I thought that was Goddy breaking into the line for a second.
Jimmy's Cowboys.
Oh, guys, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Guys, I tell you, just like, don't be mean to me.
Kind of like, you know, respect the host.
Kind of like, if you don't like me, you don't have to be here.
I mean, it's like, when I say you're a harp on me.
I wouldn't do that to you.
Is that is it funny? Is this funny guys?
Don't be a funny. It's like
Little bit desperate at this point
I thought I thought I was a desperate so you need a Santa hat for Christmas too. I don't want a fucking Santa hat
I don't like him you remind me too much of the Addis Addis for Jean Cap and
It's already been
That's me negative figures that in my mind
I'd rather just wear the top half.
Yeah.
Swamp magic users, it was, it was, you're doing,
it's all time, time, time, let me know.
And it's like, but it's, yeah, swamp magic.
It's like, you know, it's like, it's like,
it's like basically, it's like MAGA kind of stuff
where it's outdraining the swamps and, you know,
kill, kill some frogs and
Everyone will be happy right kind of bread and circus to feed our
Basically savage these violent evil desires the humans have is that like you know the only the only we can safely
Explore these feelings. It's like through movies or like you know self-interpection
It's like they come out all these different ways
Everything's repressed
Someone tell Tiffany I say hi I'm not allowed to do that
Who's we allowed you? You're saying they're talking my chat your comments are coming on the screen
Tiffany and Tiffany when I say hi to you. I don't know I don't think she's this if you like to be very much
Maybe I'm wrong
Give me a look a little minutes like
Chill
Don't say oh look is like you these shows. I mean it's like I've had enough
I don't like people putting words in my mouth.
I don't like people trying to attach their,
their storylines or feelings to me.
It's like, I'm sick of being in the middle of these narratives
instead of just on my own and speaking for myself.
So you're not very nice.
I'm just trying to chill.
We're chilling, we're chilling.
Yeah.
Okay, so Ziggy, I guess Tiffany does like, okay, we're fine.
I'm with someone and that someone doesn't like her.
I'm trying to be a good man.
Well, sometimes, yeah, sometimes our partner
won't like somebody.
Obviously, we're supposed to choose our partner side
in their eyes.
I know you're very nice, but I think we should be able
to be nice to everybody, right?
But.
I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I guess I
I got secrets. You got it. Okay
Yeah, anyway, it is cool to be kind. There's no what does it say tweaker suck on mean people suck or
Don't kind of repeat the same thing, right?
Most of them are
Not ready to deal with having God in the tea was on panel is like having a devil on shoulder and no angels
Yeah, exactly. It's like having two devils
It's like they're both talk telling me bullshit. I'm like, hey, we're hello. I'm trying to talk to the real God here
Okay, I'm not gonna refer you. No, no guy. You're not the God
Okay
Here's a Morse code speaking in Morse code now guys, and so you can even someone translate it for me. I'm not
said f you see
Hey, why oh you PSY CH a got it. That's so more. I'm busy typing. Hold on. Hold on. Oh, okay
I thought I was reading yours. Oh, you're typing. Okay. Oh
What if you take your typing, you know pretty slow?
Okay, okay. Now. What seems to be the problem?
No problem is
Trying to tell
What's all this chill? It's just cuz he was reading
no, oh
Mr. Big Pads put a curse on me. Okay, things have never been the same sense my life might not know what I'm gonna
You're right. You're right. Did he really do that? He did. Yes. He said he hexed. He hexed me. He said
But don't you like our like a protection or something like yes, well, that's why I'm still alive obviously
But you know what? I talked to saints about I don't know if you guys know saints
But I'm from the same saint is like mr. Big Sides arson emesis
They actually have a video of them or a saint almost folks's eyeballs out, but yeah, I told saying about this
We're fighting in the trailer
Yeah, that was that's mr. Beep. I'm saying yeah
Beat him up and took a slow fighting or were they making love well say
They almost poked his eyeballs out, but yeah, and then mr. Beep has kept trying to you know fighting yeah
They're both trying to fight dirty guy. I don't know but gay wrestling match and the guy took his phone
It was weird. Yeah, dude. Why are you gonna use trigger words like that JT?
No, I can't say that I can't say the other wrestling okay wrestling is
Not
Guys football's kind of gay, you know, it's like you know male figures games kind of gay, but you know
That's fine, you know, but uh, yeah, so
I forgot, I forgot what I was gonna say, but, yeah.
I don't know.
I don't know what he did.
I mean, it was this thing,
he just basically had chaos magic on the screen
and they could probably put it up.
He was one of those chaos things.
I called him out on it and then he said,
oh, well, he's like, well, I'm a,
I'm a, he's like, I'm your hex, 666.
I'm powerful.
He's like, you mess with the wrong person, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah.
Oh, God.
Yeah, so I told Stain that I told Stain and then Stain was like, he's like, oh, he's like,
Mr. Big Pipe's magic is nothing compared to like our kind of magic, right? So
I got it. I got it. They're so annoying. Oh, I'm doing magic now.
Right. Well, the real magic is actually just, you know, being able to utilize like the earthly processes, like, you know, the
you know, speech, speech communication,
you know, your passion,
your
resources, and your emotion. You're supposed to kind of create a mix and
create a beautiful life out of the ingredients, right? A lot of people have a very uneven
distribution of ingredients, and people are too much fire, too much water, too much air, too much earth, right, and
part of our life is to balance our, the elements that in ourselves, and don't forget about the spirit, like the highest element.
Don't say you like me back or shill explode. Okay. Well, I don't know.
So, as Jamie says, Marcy, sorry about earlier. Okay, we need a circular protection on sticky
of the
guy and I am very guy I am so
Marcy was joking or was he did he actually hear he was absolutely serious
He was absolutely serious, and I mean I can sense he was he was doing to protect you. Thank you dingo. Yeah
Why is he doing that like you were always there I was and yeah
He's already getting very sexual. He's
He's in love with page and so he started hitting on her request your presence Marcy. Oh, yeah, that's true
come to me
and the other guy too
Marcy
Marcy wake up it's Marcy
it's Freddy it's Freddy talking to you
John listen wake up
you fell asleep on your dream
she's coming up she's getting ready
hey don't do this for me hey Tiffany
hey Crystal
I really enjoyed Marcy
I enjoyed Marcy
no I'd rather I'd rather
maybe the angel on YouTube be like
I'm not sure if it's the devil, you're good at the devil. He's doing swat magic spell right now.
Oh my god, what is it called?
Swat magic, so you know what? You know that the way to defeat swat magic is to cast a lily pad spell
Because the lily pads, they float on swamps, so there were swamps that fell like voodoo
I thought he said SWAT magic. These are all meaning words. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay guys. Okay. I'll guide you can say but
Sorry, sorry, sorry. JT just riles you up a little bit. So I have to kick him off. Yeah
Well, he's no he's saying that you know, he said SWAT man. No, we're not talking about swatting or any of that
I know you're going. No, I know you know, I know it'd be favorite topic. No, no, no, we're not gonna talk about that. Okay
Oh, I thought it was was it was it maybe you a couple days ago. I think I'm a
loss. Oh, yes. Wow
This is laughing you're protected. Yeah, I this is tripping me. How bad?
Marcy, you know, I think I think that I am protected because I
Proven to me John. Yeah, I'm Marcy. Tell me Marcy. Are you coming up? I don't know. I don't know. Yeah
Come up if you ask it nicely
Marcy Marcy Marcy Marcy Marcy Marcy Marcy please come up a crystal crystal crystal you too in the same fight
He made a voodoo of Saints. Yeah, I mean it's like people that just make voodoo dolls. It's like that's kind of like
Who knows if it's kind of like a little low sort of sympathetic magic
It's very you know, it's just like it basically it only works if people get kind of scared because it's like it is a
Similar representation, but it you know, it's nothing really people that that's the only thing they do is kind of sad
It's just like you know
If we do is more effective as a scare tactic than actually
The magic is I don't understand my opinion, but
We're gonna have different different views about that
Hi guys, thank you. Can you see where you slice second second second second day of war?
So it was the first day yesterday. What is it? So yesterday was the first day of the war. Well, I'm a lot
I survived, you know survived the first day first day is usually the hardest, right?
Crystal Marie, Ziggy, Miss Liz, Amy's Cowboys
How's everyone doing time here? Oh, we have another guest. Oh, yes
Yeah, now we have the now we have the devil and the angel on each of each of my shoulders
He's not the devil
No, no, I'm you're the devil god
I'm no devil dude pages pages the angel and I'm
You're the devil
What you're the devil you are
I'll be the devil I'll be the devil. I'll be the devil. I'll be God and the devil
Whoever will give me a deal. Oh, you wish. Okay. I heard a way to
You're talking about freezer spells yes freezer spells yes someone else yes, there's freezer spells back
guys
The ice will eventually melt, you know, it's a yeah, it will freeze the progress but
Yeah, okay. They just gonna show some magic. Yeah guys, a lot of the magic's effectiveness is that if they like get you to believe it
Like it's like, you know, you don't know about it all in here and all in here and that is what the magic is, okay?
That's it. That's all
It's actually suggest it's a suggestion. It's a suggestion. He reminds me of the entire world. Can you make the wind blow?
Probably if I wanted to if you put my mind to it like you know, maybe fuck. I don't know
I could do it. I could do it. Hold on watch
No, no, no, oh my god
I know you're gonna do that
That's back door way
Completely offensive god, oh my god
So scatological are you okay? Do you need an energy you need an energy cleanse too? He needs the candy bar
I need a snickers. I need a snickers. I need like you know everybody's like you take a chill pill and
Then I will the spells those bells deck bells deck simple just like magic
Yeah, Gettysburg was the bloodiest battle in the war. They said the ground was a soaking blood. It was like a swap
Yeah, but I think that's not that's probably not that's probably not true. I mean, it's like, you know, it's not good
I don't think that's true. I think it's like an exaggeration
Like when the third watch had a cherry tree, too, right? He didn't even chop down. You know blood is good for grown crops
I don't know about that man. I think it might be a little
I was gonna say
Tiffany, where is the internet?
We had a sex magic.
So you study magic. Yeah, everybody's got a thing leave her alone man. All right. No, I'm not knocking it. I was asking
Sex magic is a little bit advanced guys you can read Elsa Crowley you can read about it. It's a very it's a lot about you know
Consuming like the fluids and stuff like that. I don't know
If you want you guys
It's it's about drinking period blood. I haven't had drinking period blood as far as I can tell so I mean whatever you have fun
Bon appetit guys
Yeah, it'll taste like pennies. It'll taste like pennies, but you know, maybe it'll do some magic
Yeah, that is right. You have put blood on very vegetable. Okay. I think I've studied the dough. Yeah
How do you think they turn the baby oil pink?
There's companion planting as well.
Yes, there's wet companion planting
So I think certain plants or vegetables or whatever next to certain other ones that don't like either
Diminish the nerd nutrients or steal from or over girl like their companion
It's like you're like your little twin flame plant buddy, you know, right?
What did you put you should put poison plants around non poisonous plants or they not compatible or do opposite the tracks?
Don't know we'll have to I'm you know what I'm gonna. I'm gonna look into that
Okay, I'm gonna look into that
Belladonna is Belladonna next to mint. Okay. I want to know about that. Okay, so anyway, they don't need to address
Okay, Jamie don't
What's wrong, what's on Gotti something's wrong
Nothing's wrong. Jamie. I don't do interface here. I'm looking at some new shit. Oh
Well, I'm not
I know what you're looking at. What is it?
Yeah, my name on it.
No, remember I was banned from the panel for two days?
Something's going on.
From where here, no here and a few others. Yeah, not not by choice. It was something
They were some YouTube was I told you it was active weird. I think I was signed out though the whole time
I don't know what it was. I don't know weird and same with my like
Everything's kind of been glitchy and fucking. Yeah
You guys have to get on here or no
Yeah, I didn't have to for the longest time and then all of a sudden it's asking me to sign off
I did have to last night to get on to stream yard
Yeah, I'm rooting me, but nobody
Shut off on my phone
You know requires you to log in through your account, but it didn't like you for like a year and a half
They get me. I mean you but you but you weren't were you broadcasting from it or not because I think no, no, I don't broadcast
Yeah, so it's like you don't need you don't you don't need the account if you're just uh, we're on panels, but if you're and have your own panel
I think you need you need that. Okay, so
My lighter like keeping the account active as well
Like maybe if you're just gone for a long time that the server means you to like actually like clarify that it's you again, you know
No, I was in I think I was in a different state. So maybe that was it. Oh, well, that's probably logical
It kicked me out. Yeah
Yeah, sometimes it goes by the IP address and stuff
So, let's see.
Oh, no, no, hold on.
It's made, it made me do it too, probably server.
Yeah, actually, no, I did have to log in today.
Yeah, I don't know if it was a server,
but I think sometimes you log everybody out
and log back in.
It was a server error last week.
I'll take a break.
Yeah, everyone takes, you know,
everyone needs a break sometimes.
YouTube stuff is like mostly training sometimes that everyone needs to probably at least a day a day a week not
We're on YouTube. I know you guys just some YouTube
Well, it's actually you know, it is like, you know our job stressful
They can't be you know careers can't be stressful because they're trying to maintain the career
I haven't been successful in the career
I never get stressed on here. Are you doing it? You're doing it purely for fun. I'm doing I'm doing it
for, you know, a career.
Oh, that's true.
That's true, that is a difference.
People say, oh, you're working from home.
Yeah, it's called, you can work from home.
This is a new thing they have called, you know,
computers and telephones.
We can pretty much provide any service to anything
from our home now, so.
I know you're Jamie me too, but it's like, you know, you get you get a armor
Is she being attacked on it? Who's attacking? I can't really bring I can't bring it up
And it doesn't need to be strung out everywhere ever again
It's done like it's worth it's not even worth the drama. It's just not as long as she's all right
Okay, sometimes we have to just remove some people from our our energy and then things things won't prove
Yeah, okay good
She's okay. She's good. She's good. She's good. I'm Mojo. Yeah, I love Jamie. Jamie's one of the good ones
Definitely one of the good ones. She's my girl. She's always got
Marcy you come up and say hi. Oh, we love Marcy. Yes, Marcy come up, please
Who I've been begging all night
They're coming yeah, I am
Ziggy
Actually, you know what? I think that there's only like two people that I dislike really and I don't even like I don't hate
I just dislike their energy. Mine. They irritate my energy
Mojo's one of them? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, nobody here. No, I'm pretty much everybody knows who ears my energy
There's only two people in this whole community and that says a lot
It's Scotty, it's Scotty and Michael Superlinguini, those are the only two people that I can't...
I knew it, I knew it.
I know, obviously no, I'm not really a different person when they're around.
I don't know if I know Scotty, I'm not sure.
You don't want to, you're good, you probably will, you'll be lived the rest of your life fully without knowing him.
Okay
Gwendolyn guy strange
His name is the Voldemort is the name that she let me mention because I do not
Said me
No, no, no, are you kidding me?
Oh, Scotty, you said Scotty?
You think this is what's ever come out of my mouth about you?
Not.
Well, that's what I heard, though.
I'm sorry.
No, it's not going to cost you.
Well, you heard it wrong.
He's all the Chinese guy the Chinese kid
Little guy he looks like he looks like one of the seven dwarfs which one dopey. Yes. Yes. Yeah one. Yep. Yep. Okay
Okay, not that I'm judging any way's appearance cuz I know I'm fucking I'm not perfect and have a huge forehead and yeah
Yeah, yeah, but it's like he has fetal alcohol syndrome
Oh, sorry, was that wrong was that bad?
You're just making, you know, that's an insult to the children of the people in the world
You're not in that you're not you're not that hell
I think I graduated from hell and I graduated from hell. I am purgatory when Emma fired me. It's kind of like yeah
I'm not don't bring up Emma. We don't talk about Emma here. Yeah, I talked about I talked about whoever I want here
A thousand people in her room at any given moment. No, she does not last time I was in her room
She had like 25 people I had for your 50. So I was there yesterday. She had 700
Oh, wow, 700. Well, that is probably bots because she did not have that kind of number, but maybe she does maybe she's
Sensitive just annoying on purpose, and I understand what you're doing
You said you said I'm annoying
Yes, you're trying to, I didn't think you'd say that at one time.
What happened?
I said it in a variety of ways.
He's very sensitive, but I think he's very sensitive.
He's hard beyond me.
Yeah, he's sensitive.
Oh, I'm jealous.
I'm jealous.
I've been nice.
And...
He's the man I call him. I call him God
Is everybody your favorite?
I'm something for my Jeep and I just have to walk through fucking Spoodville. Oh that Patrick guy
He's like a porn. He likes to like jack off of people's backstage. I
Don't I don't think so. I don't think so. I never saw Patrick
Thank God wait wait for the day though
It's coming
I hope it's not today. Yeah.
But at least he doesn't in the backstage.
Well, that's, oh, guys, the panel's getting so full right now. Hold on. I'm sorry.
Hey, guys. Hey, psyche. Hey, Paige. How are we doing today?
Good, thank you for asking
Feeling better still feeling good
No, I my nose is I don't feel sick, but my nose is kind of clogged up
I don't know if you can tell but I got like some sinus. Maybe it's my sinuses. I don't know. I don't feel sick
Yeah, like if your lymphatic system needs to be drained as well
Like it can affect obviously your eyes your ears your nose your your glands your lymph nodes
If you have I don't know if this is correct. I should probably Google it, but you know how Google is, but if you have sinuses
Isn't it like like like
Like lifelong or can you develop it like later like because I'm like
No, like if you have like sinuses at all, you know, yeah, you can definitely develop
Issues as you age and you can it just be you can develop allergies as you age to is
Weird because your immune system and your body changes as you age right and also say if you go through like a really rough
Cold or flu and it can like weaken your immune system
And sometimes it doesn't quite like reboot the same and then therefore you're susceptible to shit like that and then it can
create bigger I think it would uh
Detailer I don't well it would go away after like
Like my body is not keeping up like when I was like 18 years old. Yeah, that's what I'm trying to say
Mm-hmm. Yep. It's normal, but like it sucks. Just go see your doctor and see if maybe you have
You know, maybe you have a fucking you have like pelps that can grow in there, too
Which make it hard and it can feel like a sign of infection
But really it's a growth or you know, just be mindful of that stuff and get ahead of it
Nip it in the bud if you can right?
Hey psyche, can you show the side of your head real quick?
Not sure why those light up headphones. Yeah, they're late. Oh shit
Yeah, the very fancy
Like up
I don't know got it got it
Sometimes I'll sometimes I'll be in a bitchy mood, and then I'll I'll kick you off the panel
Goddy for the past like four hours
He stresses me out. I mean, he has that he's attacked me like I didn't start with him
I was you know people's for attacking me
So, I'm low. Yeah
he is on the rack, yeah, well whatever, men have a cycle too, it's actually longer and we're dry out, but a little bit less intense.
Yeah, it's called, we like the fight.
Because we have it all the time, we have peanuts all the time, men have peanuts a lot.
And if you give us chocolate, we don't like the fight as much.
Just give you guys just ten of the little chocolate bars like a weird
What was that? Was that a bug?
There was a spider on me when I walked in my door and then I just felt like something tickled me, but it was just it was your hair
Normally it's my hair
Yeah, normally that's the culprit why are you on the that's nothing
I was smoking a cigarette the other day and there was a hornet that laying on my arm
But then I was smoking and I fucking just like ash and it like hit I guess the hair in my arm
You know, I thought that little tingle and dude
I fucking like my dog like cuz my dog likes them for some reason she likes to eat bees and like I don't know how she does it
Eat them. I don't know. She's not got stung yet
And she came running over, but I was like, no, it's just Ash like we're all good
Honestly, I don't like bugs. I don't like bugs at all
I don't like I hate spiders. I have arachnophobia. I don't know why but they freak me out
I know that they can't if there's just sneaky, okay, so listen
This is why every other bug gives you the opportunity to defend yourself
You can visually see a bug the other bug bite you or try to right for the most part. You know what's up, right?
They give you the chance to defend yourself
Spiders you just wake up in the fuck the morning or you like pull your pant leg up
And you you know it was a spider you know what bit you but you never see that little motherfucker. They're like night ninjas
That's rude, you know
My dad but they are black
They're not like the little ninjas. Oh, they are black
No, they do
You know, they're basically like insect octopuses. They got the fucking eight arms. They're all creepy and and
Weird, but yeah, they do they do carry like a lot of babies in their stack and stuff like that
And so maybe it's not the rest of you to kill them
That's like you're killing like thousands of babies too, but you know as you should
Spider babies, but they're still babies sword
Know a lot about spiders because I have to know the most about what I'm scared of
It ordered for me to be like, you know and understand why I'm scared of it
But no, they are they're they're they're fucking they do carry tons of babies
I've ever seen that one video where that the chick smacks up spider with the broom
Yeah
Fuckin hundreds of fucking little babies and their eyes are reflecting
I think some spiders are actually, they don't bite you, but they're good at catching mosquitoes, believe it or not, and bats are really good at it, you know.
Well, man, it's insects, it's like, it's just a web, but you know, they actually can cross breed a spider, like a silk weaving spider with the goat that can cross the DNA and they can milk the goat, and then they can turn the goat milk into the strongest web of material, stronger than bulletproof vests when they make this one.
that shit up. I swear to God. I swear to God. It's not a mix of a goat though. Yes, it is, it is. Look at it, look at it, look at it, look at a spider goat, look at a spider goat. Yeah, but you're not mixing a spider inside. Yes, you are. They make the DNA of a spider with a goat. I swear to you, they do, they do.
And it's a
I've been to the silk farms in China. I have I've been to the silkworm farms in China
They do they make a lot of stuff out of silk. You can't mix the DNA of an insect in a fucking water can a mammal
You cannot
Not even page let me guess you can okay. First of all, you can mix it tomato and tobacco like in the Simpsons, right?
What did it say? What did it say? All right, go ahead. Okay, spider goats are genetically modified
goats that have a spider's silk spinning gene inserted into their DNA. This allows them to
produce a protein in their milk that can be extracted and used to create artificial spider silk.
This silk has the potential applications in various fields, including medicine, textiles,
It's stronger than a bulletproof vest.
They can spin it out of the milk.
They spin the thread out of the milk.
It has the stuff in there already.
They made tomatgo.
Tomatgo is a real thing. They have actually crossed tomato and tobacco.
Yeah, I mean I watched a lot of like, you know discovery channel and like, you know
Science I'm really interested that I've you seen like if they also have like this
Artificial stomach for like growing a lamb and they can like it's like a plastic bag
Basically like a plastic bag, but it's the artificial womb and they can grow the from it from an embryo into like a full lamb in this like plastic bag
It's kind of like like similar to the womb. I've seen that
There's also I don't know if this is a
True or not, but there's I mean
They had a website I was at the website they had something called celebrity meats, and they take it take a DNA of a celebrity
And they can make a sausage out of it. They can create a meat like you know beyond meat
They can make a celebrity DNA sausage, and they make it a sausage and they can get a generous Kanye West and some other people
I don't know
Right, I don't know, yeah, it's kind of, it's kind of, it's kind of, I mean, it's like, it's not, it's in its cannibalism, but it's not, not really, because it's thought, like...
People be doing, being doing way too much.
I don't trust that, uh, that Beyond Meat really very much, that, uh, or the, uh, what is it, what's the...
the meat substitutes. They're kind of not that great. Hasn't even tried them. It's not bad, but it's like, it's not real. Here it goes back.
Yeah, go ahead and listen to it.
The tobacco.
I had to go on my little deep dive of Google.
Yeah, it's not even cooked or made up. It's real, I guess.
But the world and he said something about still too strong and still, but they're not like fucking
Looking out fucking still though. I think there's a process
Yeah, yeah, they do process it but it's like but it's not like silk. No, it's by the spider
The spider there are the spiders trying this it's been the silk alone
It would be impossible because spiders like will bite each other when they're in close proximity to each other
Well, and so they could go like spider-man
Right, I don't know but I think they just, you know, they do this powers.
It was a genetic match. I don't know. I think we'll be on the Spider-Man world now.
I think I think the world has gotten weirder than Spider-Man. Spider-Man is pretty weird.
Oats are funny as fuck. My friend has some and like I'm, they're not like big on scaring their
goats but I'm like big on scaring the goats because I think it's hilarious when they faint.
And they scare me. They like to fuck with me so I fuck with the goats, right?
So scared of them when they just fall over.
Yeah, they do fade, they fade, they can climb trees, they can faint, they can climb up
really like narrow mountains, they can scream, they're so cool.
They'll eat anything, they'll eat anything.
Like they're fucking sweet.
They'll eat a shoe, they'll eat a shoe, it's a sock.
They'll eat the same cat and shit it out like it was nothing.
No.
No, no.
God, you have to ask Flurry Diamond, Flurry Diamond makes the milk.
So Tiffany says for funsies, uh, the every, uh, yeah, I mean, oh, I hear like James Earl Jones voice. Do you hear James Earl Jones voice? I heard, I heard that. Did you hear that? Marcia? Yeah. Uh, Goddy, you don't want that milk. It's sour. Oh, okay. Yeah. What is it? Where's Alice? But Alice was here today, but he was just behaving, you know, and I had to kick her out.
I'm not doing that with you, I'd like that that was really involuntary. I'm sorry. Oh
Well, you're all good. I mean, it's like I'm sorry if I lost my temper in the same
I use my temper guys and I get annoyed in a sleeper. I do have like a lot of
Just say you know, I'm just like, you know, I've always it's dressed up person. So, you know, I try I try to relax
Why are you apologizing to us? You literally lose your shit the least out of all of us like frequently
I even get mad more than you do. So like you says a lot about how calm you are, right?
But everything builds up you guys and sometimes it's just our day to fucking be
The chaos, you know what I mean? Like sometimes we just it's our day
I don't even know
The idea of crashing out in a locale is this a really offensive to me
What do you know what it means okay locale is so like a streamer that people will say oh look at that streamer. They're like really
You know, I'm stable. They have some flaws. We can just like harp on them point out their flaws
We can eventually drive them crazy. Maybe they'll you know, unalive themselves. Maybe they'll, you know, get really, you know
strong out on
Like you basically like, you know brainwash them and try to destroy them. And so that's basically what some people start to do
That's like a really cool idea for people. Yeah
That's the idea of a locale and then we have like, you know
Crashing out is basically like when the locale would be it goes under as much stress and eventually, you know
Crashes out or rage quits or spurses or they've been cooked too long. I don't know. You know, there's too many cooks in the kitchen at the time.
I have a different opinion. I love crashing out.
Well, that's why I thank you much of the bullshit, especially when everyone's trying to debate and shit.
It's a different meaning. It's a different meaning. Can you just say crash out like, yeah, you see me falling asleep in like the 90s, like when I was growing up, but it's like, now it means like, you know, it's like, you're like, just going nuts on your panel and, you know, you're, you're, you start screaming and losing your emotional shit and stuff. And so that's kind of crashing out, I think, in the panel term.
You're just like crashing your emotional vehicle into a wall.
Well yeah, you know you're filling your cups you're spilling your cups here
You're like you're you know in emotions can be like the waves right it can be like it can be like you know
You know up and down they vary if we need to like stabilize them because they do affect our logic and our
Thinking if we're doing our emotions, we can't even we can't function, right?
Guy I think I take it as a I use it in a different meaning just like I use done something in a different meaning
But I use it like
I've debated somebody for so long and it's like finally I'm just gonna crash out and I'm just gonna tell them like hey
You're dumb. This is why you're dumb
And then I'll just like keep going, but you never really you never fully go full crash out. I got you
Yeah, you're like a New York people and stuff. Yeah
This is more like a yeah, you know, you know
It's just like it's held somewhere. It's where you really think and that's you know, good loser temp loser tempera stuff like that
That can be there. That's that can be funny. It's better when you say crash out though
Yeah, but people I mean crash hadn't really like Benny they were like you know
He had mods trying to say oh donate so he'll kill like by like all this and drugs and alcohol and then he'll
And then he'll you know have a meltdown or there's something like and these are his mods trying to like
They're doing behind the scenes. They like the message got revealed and stuff, but yeah, okay, I've seen yeah
I don't use it like that at all
You know these people call Lisa a whore cow. They're called mini Manson egg a little cow. They've called, you know, Benny a little cow they call
Actually a lot of IP two people locales and stuff like that. You know, they call Syrax's as one and
They've been trying to call me once in a while. You know, I think Pye was just joking
Pye was on the show last night. By the way, were you hearing Pye was here?
Loka was more like
Anorexic people because you know they got
You're taking low cow. No, it's a low cow. It's a LOL cow. It's like somebody's like a cow. Like a cow you laugh at and you're like, you milk them. You milk them for like, you milk them for entertainment. And then once they're like drained, you're just like, you're just like going for it.
First time I've heard that. They're like vampires. Psychic vampires. And they will try to, they'll try to like raise your energy. And so then you, so then you have a big energy crash and then they like will suck up the energy.
I've seen it happen. You have your Santa Marte statue arrived say oh wow God you're into the Santa Marte cult. Okay. Well, you know
This page comes out
Ave Maria, I'll be Maria. All right, so
Cards like I have a tarot deck there's really pretty I don't know where it is right now
Well, I mean, it's like Santa Marte did remind me a lot of Hecate and like, you know, God, he's like, oh, well, so you're not, you know
God, God, you have no
You have no place in telling somebody what TATs they work with and they don't work with and I don't know
You came up with that and other things to annoy me, but
Yeah, and there are universal
Black these dark goddesses that you just associate with Statter like Colby's associate of Statter. Colby is also
There's these goddesses that bring
Deaths in destruction, but you know with death always comes the
Rebirth or growth and that's where the whole Phoenix
Story comes into you know Phoenix is reborn. Yeah, pie. That's cool
I was supposed to be close someone supposed to be our locale, but I'd like to someone was all well
You know we's nobody's gonna be a locale. I'm not gonna let people be called cows and different animals here
You can we call it crazy like a fox, you know people we call that or can we call it like you know?
They, you know, you know, sneak as a cat and, you know, loyal as a dog, you can say nice
comparisons, but not like, oh, let's just milk this person until they're, you know,
they're destroyed.
I mean, some people I don't know.
What, maybe there's, maybe think of stamp collecting guys, there's better hobbies than
Heard of the people, right?
Where's Jim?
What character?
My commitment to what character?
Who's saying that?
Oh, Mars Marcy.
Thank you, control.
My commitment to the character is...
I don't even know what she just said.
But you have a character. Your character is a ghost and so I don't know if you're like you have other characters
I don't know ghost and girly character. He's certainly I'm not saying you're anybody you're very fancy
Yeah, I'm saying you're just you're just ghost me and it's like even if you are character. I like
Ghost I just think there's other characters that
I don't quite maybe like
that. I like you have accused me of playing a character if you don't even know me like at all.
No, but if you ever ever this is I mean online
really is a role play in a certain way is and so it is
are you trying to debate or is pay trying to debate no so like if they were
trying to debate I'd be the exact same way we're all being cool right now.
No, we're all being cool, but it's just gonna be a testament to that because I've always been cool
And then like when people join in that's usually when she dips out because then let's get it
Okay
Final crush out those don't crush it don't crush on it. Not yet
Oh, you dropped a candle. Well, we shouldn't be that's why we shouldn't be burnin shit. No, I'm not
Funny bone on this fucking metal chair. I do it every time. I need to move the chair. It's my fault
My problem. He went also very funny. Hey, hey, what is my toe or like hit my
Think it feels like electricity. It went like right in between. I'll take you know, but I'll take funny bone all day over
It's a fuck you stop your tow man. You feel like that shit's broke
I broke my tail not long ago. I hit it off my fireplace hearth and like I had to go to it
I was literally on my way out for a dinner and we had to like limp there
It was brutal. It was like that for a while, but what is the pinkie tail?
Well, the pinkie tail is the only good thing the pinkie tail is good for is it takes you wee wee all the way home and
Then uh, but you know the big tail
You got me on that. I actually thought I was listening
If you ever seen junk have you ever seen jungle feet and how they're spread out like a hand
Jungle feet nobody made
They're made for climbing some trees brother. You can run up the motherfuckers
I don't I bet I do have my second show is like longer than my big toes. That's kind of weird
I heard this people that's an abomination
It's abomination. Oh my god. My demon of shit. Okay, I'll be there is here. No, I'm not gonna cut it off
I'm gonna cut me. I'll cut you off and or in other negative people
I was you do you know that's to you got two good ones like y'all give it to you do a good night. I know
I'm on top of my shit. Okay. Yeah, you're on one tonight
I'm on what I'm on it. I'm on my high on life. I'm very happy guys. I'm very happy
I'm bringing
Mike's
It's harder
Oh, that's why it's my bad
It's hard. It's harder. It's harder than
It's harder than hard. It's harder. That's harder than you are right now
Not as hard as I am
Okay, nevermind. That was really inappropriate
Okay, okay, nevermind
Hey, what's up?
I'm drinking too much beer
But Chris Chris came got me all riled up and then now he's disappeared. I think he's in love with the this old lady
The apartment below him now
He just left me for this lady and I was banging on his ceiling saying he was interested in her
There is a point thing. I
Love life is
Really really
My gosh, okay
Okay, baby. I love you, bitch
Thank you. Wake is tarot. Thank you for never give you up. Oh, Jamie. Of course. I would never give up on I don't give up
I don't give up on people people always give up on me. I
Like I'll give you a million chances. I love people
Yeah, I think people like you know, I'm in a very
Fatherly way. I would say like I was like this one everyone to be well
Yep, Paisie you're shuffles. He's shuffles something. Oh
I like those. No, oh guess. Oh
Are you okay, so you look like you're passed out
Where's your mouth open? I'm nodding out. I'm on draw. Oh my god, not again
I'm on nighting out on drugs again. No, what you think if you really take it too much
I'm gonna call the the paramedics for you and
Your dress in the back chat please the paramedics can't save me. I'm on too many drugs
He's like I bad
Like we're seeing her trying to like raise the vibe. He comes in like
Lump on a log
Not probably on probably not like being serious. He's trying to he's trying to mock me. I think like
You're trying to push the more button, but I push the lead button
You want
You want him back on the you want to give him another chance right now?
66 I mean what we're gonna talk about is there a purpose you want me to debate them or you just
I'm just giving you like a freebie like you get to decide
Okay
If you misbehave you're I'm gonna kick you off again, and we can't even talk shit to me cuz I actually
And I still ate it
Well, well brother, I mean
You know why psyche
Oh, it's getting late brother. No, you're like
You were this all
I'm a gremlin. I'm a gremlin psyche. Okay. Why are you are you like the
Are you like a Moli or like what was that? Oh, no, it was there was it was wasn't a little cute
Can I say the our word psyche can I say that our word? No, don't say it. Don't say it
What's the other word? Can I say that would you look like a dumb dumb ninja turtle?
You said remind me of a dump. I don't know why. Dumb. Dumb. Okay. What?
Guys, I have a whole thing of dum-dums in a little jar in the backstage. Help yourself, but
you're being asked to leave the show. Security hasn't supported you out.
And you're just in the green room, but
I don't feel I don't feel like I have you up through being that asshole. I told you I'm not in the mood tonight
They keep doing it. I want to have a nice time with age
No one's in the mood for anything like tonight. There was a little edgy today, you know
I was just getting up late last night or something maybe I
Was I was grumpy today too. I'll sleep when I'm dead
Well, yeah, we have plenty of time to like not be alive. Like I sleep a lot. I do sleep a lot
I sleep way too much. I sleep usually almost I'm sleeping 18 hours a day like over here
So it's fun it close to the plot of Brandon Conan Brooks with the antiviral
Black Archie. Okay, so it goes he's falling off goes get back up here. Why are you guys be falling off?
Well, where did you guys go? Why are you back stage?
Well, you said you're gonna put a single
I forgot I'm sorry guys. I had the worst short-term memory. It's it is like I was like, why are they back stage?
Oh, here's got it. He got it. Hey the whole games here. What?
Well, you don't like gay guys on your stream psyche
I know I have it all
Gay guys on the stream. You only want straight disarmers
I'm not doing a very good job because my panel is mostly gay and trans transgender
what
it's
the
I know
My mutuals think I'm sure
You're not
You can tell he means it
I would never say something like that. I'll talk like that. I'm serious
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Well, I'm talking to the birth that ass up, dude.
He said it.
He doesn't have a girlfriend.
He kind of do it like one too.
See, I understand.
I understand.
It's like, well, I didn't play with a girlfriend
if I wanted a girlfriend.
You know, it's like women are, you know,
I can barely afford myself.
I cannot, you know, take on a silent partner or anything.
But, yeah, so women can be expensive or they can also,
things too and so it's like I think it's a really art
It's because of the help and manifesting is anything.
So, you should give them the respect of if she wants,
you just sleep with her,
then you should grant her where she really was.
That lady that I dated, she just wanted to sleep with me
so bad, I was like, okay, I was Buddhist,
a very strong Buddhist at the time,
whereas in Buddhism, it says-
You were a strong Buddhist when you were sleeping with women?
Yeah, that's kind of like,
that's kind of why I like, you know,
even like dated a woman because I was like I thought I was like I just had the feeling like
I know the idea in my head was like some kind of magical initiation that I needed to do
I was like 33 I was like oh my god I have an experience
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Two males and two females. We can still have the yeah, it is gay stick. I mean, yeah, you're on a gay man's panel
Sex with a woman and creating life that's gay
You have to become a good drag queen you can be 30 diamonds like understudy
I'll become the next
Well, you know, he's but he's fine. He's probably alive in Argentina right now. Okay, so
Marcy I just see yeah, I understand. Yeah, man. Yeah, man. I meant her
I'm it's done to a stunt double because remember when she like put it down and like flipped over on the tape like
She's flipped over like did the summer solid and like I'll sit that up. It's funny. It's like Stig would do that
So she hurt
We just look like
Oh, so
the
It looks so sad. It looks so sad when they're sitting backstage. I just have I'm going back
You know, I need a daily reminder about who's panel
I'm actually gonna go like this
Hey, how are you put that fucking finger away asshole? No
No, don't do that. We don't kick them so far. Oh
shit
Look what you guys did. That's how he was kicking her. Look what you know, he did he's kicking everybody out
Which I'll chase the psyche off board that ain't right
Hey, so what are you chasing that? What are you chasing that with?
So this is for local
Well, you pissed with a little bit of four local I feel it there
You guys you see under my name now look can you read it now look
What's a good idea
Hey guys guess what
We didn't know you know you should put under your name. You should put never knew that. We got it. I should help the label. I don't think they would know me.
Normie? What? Is that a trick by old P?
No, it's not. It's not on Bates from Psycho because he's calling me a psycho, but it's okay. It's okay. I've been called it all my life.
Well, you don't drink your own piss?
No, I don't drink my own piss.
You don't drink your own piss like Bear Groose?
No. No, we don't.
It's disgusting
You don't have that bottle of pee pee near by you. Do you do several me or he does
You want to see the no, I don't want to see it. Why do you know I got names for all of them? Why do you have that?
Are the names
Thank you. Thank you. They smell it. You like you live in a trap house. That's what with no plumbing
You see like a neighbor. I mean, I'm gonna call them for you to the power company immediately. Well
Okay, okay, okay, that's fine. And so I feel their power for free
Well, they're not you know, you name these p-bottle sick. Do you name them by flavor? Do you try to flavor and in name some of them?
I put a date on them. I put a date on them
So there is a like a certain amount of like aging on them
I open the bottle occasionally to release the pressure
because there's pure air gas. It's pure alcohol, right? It's a pure vodka that you just pee out because it's just like you drink so much vodka. It's pure vodka as you can re-drink it over and over again. Oh, no, okay. No. Well, I'm sure it tastes fine. She'd be waiting for the national holiday they're living. Yeah. Hey, Denny, Den, how are you? I'm trying to figure out a reason for this. Yo. Are you mad at me, Denizia? Are you okay with that one? What are you even crashing out, buddy? No, listen up, Den. Okay. Paige is crashing out.
You guys don't that doesn't make sense. Hey, it's not crab. We go you're a very prairie page
What how long are the nails that you have on your nails?
I'm going to nail on nails. Can I see your nail the prosthetic nails you have on your nails?
Listen, I have a full-time job and I can't get into my nail tech until she has time for me to go in and I have a
Day off so just give me a break guys
Can I just ask
Right, how how do you like five weeks? How do girls with these crazy long nails?
Right on in all honesty, this is a genuine question. It's like he can you like not put yourself full-screen?
What is that?
This is an it's like a male kid got on Timo adds like a million pieces
Thank you, I don't trust that I don't trust that like no, it's a grooming kid. It's like
cutting your nails
It's like kind of something that's not expensive. It was just like 650 ships pretty good
And I can see my nails I have a million things
All these so I see you know like that the shipping the thing the thing about these Timo items that I don't trust is that like
They're shipped. They're literally shipping them from China and you're paying them $2 more
I got both of these things I ordered within like a few days like they were like you're almost I don't have to keep from China
But or like even if it's like a warehouse, it's
You have to ask yourself
You have to ask yourself how is this so cheap and that's really questionable as to how it is so cheap
Right. I know it's probably cheap materials and it's like, you know, but it is, you know
Some of this stuff is kind of cool and it's kind of like harmless, you know
I was gonna ask you something earlier
that
There's the guys are all right-handed and boring. I'm I use my left hand
I bet I bet that I'm actually in me dexterous. I'm the only left-handed person here
But not you forget racist. Yeah, but are you fully ambidextrous? Whoa?
I can figure your mother with her left hand, so I'm going to go yes.
I am ambidextrous.
Ambidextrous.
Can we, can we just like leave people's family members and their health out of like, you know,
our resources? It's kind of like the lowest of the low to bring up that kind of stuff.
And whoever else did that, I don't know who that was really. I just, you know, hurt sick, but you know what?
Yeah, it's not something to joke about. It's not funny. And it's like, it's just pretty like,
at this point, offensive and lame. And it's like, so let's not talk about people's families.
I'll be honest with you, everyone was talking every time.
When they talk about mine, just let it slide because we want to get the chat around it.
There are no rules.
Hold on.
Gaudi, what are you saying?
Gaudi.
Oh, okay.
Yes.
In the wheel, the wheel is always turning and then some people fall off the wheel.
And they have to go in the chat, Gaudi.
Okay?
And I love you, Gaudi, but it's like, you know, I'm not in the mood today, Gaudi.
I love you, Gaudi.
God he's a fucking ma he's a mod he can be modding the chat. He's gonna be up here gal advancing around a panel
Yeah
Yeah, well, you should but you know you can just you can just say you can say like the stream and the chat you
Everybody can say that you don't have to be a monster
Everybody should be liking and subscribing if you've been here longer than 15 minutes. Let's be real. Yeah
Okay, and I should get my rich back
Well, it goes
Goes goes you're just threatening like last night. You're like, oh my god, you're doggie
You're like, I'm gonna report. Hey, you're just like last thing
I don't I don't I don't I don't even like I don't even like I don't like I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don
It's uh, so this is my safe place, but yeah, but it's it should be your safe place
Who else would you say Paige?
I'm just saying hi to the chat because no one's fucking acknowledged them in like a hundred years, and it's free
Hi, I'm Memphis and my hey members. I had members and mods and everybody else tiffany white t-shirts
I
Yeah, I'm not gonna lie. I'm so proud of you but I believe I well
I don't I believe in it like with like religious reasons
There's like Catholic say the burn stage like
It's my own religious I don't fucking know what you do
Well
There are certain Christians that will call anything that it's that it's outside of the Bible or anything
Everything everything is witchcraft, right? And so it's like everyone will say that about everything so it's like, you know, it's not everything
Okay, so I mean Nancy. I got you. Hold on speaker
Oh, she's so cute when she's hunting the bugs you're gonna get that mosquito for me good girl page
I'm not gonna lie to you. It's just that it's I watched and city is like one two three
the other day
because my girl want to watch him, so I watched them and
It got me a little freaked out. I'm not gonna lie. Yeah, that's it's real. That's the shit. I see I see the dark
I see the good I see the bad I see all this stuff the creep that but between the veil is what it's called
She's like it's not real. Why are you burning it? I'm like it's like having a gun like there's not a robber here
But I have a gun, but there was a robber here. I have a gun
Yeah, you're right. Yeah, you're right. This is like, it's a triangle. I have something to say to you, and I have something to say to you, and I have something to say to you, and I have something to say to you, and I have something to say to you, and I have something to say to you, and I have something to say to you, and I have something to say to you, and I have something to say to you, and I have something to say to you, and I have something to say to you, and I have something to say to you, and I have something to say to you, and I have something to say to you, and I have something to say to you, and I have something to say to you, and I have something to say to you, and I have something to say to you, and I have something to say to you, and I have something to say to you, and I have something to say to you, and I have something to say to you, and I have something to
Well, you know you can do crystal gazing which is just you basically put a candle behind it
You get going to kind of like a little bit of a trance. You kind of blur your vision
Yeah, but you can see a lot of you start to see things move around in there and it's like, you know your mind will
Start so
I got you. Don't be mad. You're still a mod. You got it. No, you know, you know, take his mother away. Give it to go.
Okay, so yeah
It's still the official position of alphabet corporation that he does not receive a wrench
Well, let me see. Hold on. Oh, here. Oh, we have another guest. Hi, I'm just here because I want to have gay sex with Psyche
Okay
Dari deserves a second chance being finally a topic. I know he's he's fine
Thank you, I'll do it. I'll do it if we stream in Psyche
We have to stream it
I already have a gangbang land with Chris Kaye
I didn't say that
Hey Psyche, maybe a signal could be the girlie in the middle
The honey in the middle
Oh no, look at the four cameras now Denison
Chris was a real woman and I kind of
Look at the camera man
Yeah, it seems like a waste of
To be frosty, I think psyche wants to be such a sleep though
Putting it behind the camera seems like a way
I would just like I would just bend them over time up and uh, and uh, am I way with draw me like a french girl?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Well, that'd be
So here you go, and it sounds like you have an audience that'd be seems like it could be private issues
Oh, so it says
Kind of content on it. It sounds like everybody wants to see it's like you
See, oh, yeah, the go picture goes. I'm trying to find it. Let's make a deal here. Wait a minute. What's wrong with our beautiful sassy?
What's the matter?
There you go
Oh
That's what he looks like guys
He's one curly hair on his head and he's a big
He's a banana he's a banana for a smile and his eyes are like
Cheerios, and that's his real name. Go GHOSC
Yeah, that's his real name is John
Ghosts it's ghost ghost T. Y
Real name is Clarence. I'm gonna call you. Thank you
I'm gonna call you and we're with the hard R
No, I'm about to say it to you. I'm just kidding. Oh my god
That stick is gone. Oh my god. I missed it. And he was like, you know, he wasn't a great guest. He was not my type.
Okay, guys, he's actually, you know, I would never hook up with, I mean, like, really, I was into...
Would you hook up with, would you hook up with Ghost's picture though?
Ghosts a picture. No, it's like I mean, I don't it's a cartoon. It's like a vented a paper cut
That logic that debating it does get you know
They put my desk in the corner of the classroom and I was like the bad
kid in the class at the second grade or something and I was in the corner yeah I was I got put in the
corner during choir
Like I don't even remember but who gets put in your corner during choir
Probably like made up my own lyrics to the words problem
When I would come out of detention my history teacher would say oh you're finally back from your home room, huh?
They didn't even make it through to home.
Didn't even make it halfway through in one detention door back into the next.
Yeah, he would call me by my last name and say, ah, you're a homeroom away from homerooms.
Yeah.
And God, God, he made me sign a fear of God, but I don't fear, I don't fear, I don't
fear men, even though men are.
Well, I'm always with a chance great being my homeboy one would leave during third hour
I'd look at one and be like, bro, you ready go home and smoke
Yeah
Okay, we're done for the day here walk out the class
That's the way it should be trades
So we actually got the leaf or half the day and never went to that bit. So we were actually how America intended
Yeah, exactly. We're supposed to be kids with our own kids.
Yeah, I don't necessarily
I don't think it's a bit every be kings and queens because then who's they gonna make who's gonna build the castles
He's gonna maintain that he's gonna maintain everything
No kings and queens of your own destiny in other words
Well, we are in America. It's supposed to be think we'll completely get rid of teachers
How much is how much is nature how much is nurture? I mean how are we just programs from the beginning with the revision?
Yes public education
We're told this world view we believe it. We just we're told it leave everything you here. I mean, yep
There's like we're not taught to think critically. We're just taught to
Believe because the current temperature of society. I would say it's 90% catered to
Which is bullshit
Do you think we might replace teachers entirely with AI, though?
Well, yeah, I mean I think eventually like it will be more like homeschooling because they'll have like all the curriculum and they're
Lot of parents want their kids to be like even a boarding school or not, you know, or regular school, you know, I think
Parents would like, you know, they don't want to have the kids there full time. It's like, you know, it's kind of like nice to have
The government take care of that kind of stuff, but you know, it's like you
It is that education really though. Is it really though psyche?
It's it's just brainwashed. I mean it's program
It's just all programming brainwashing and it's like, you know
It's like parents kind of like the TV set and then the public education raised their kids, you know, it's like
You know, there's a lot of weird entertainment. The YouTube stuff for kids is like, you know, very unusual
Strange content. There's a lot of I don't it's like my sister doesn't let
Her kids watch YouTube at all. You see things the internet was a lot more based when I was a kid though
Because it wasn't popular yet
Yeah, my youngest son's teacher told him happy Thanksgiving. My son educated her and he told her you mean happy
colonizing. So she fucks around and calls my house and my wife answers the phone. And my wife said,
well, is he in trouble? And she said, well, the teacher is like, well, that's why I called home to
And my wife asked her, well, was he wrong?
And the teacher said, well, technically no, he wasn't wrong.
My wife said, well, why should he be in trouble?
That was pretty much the end of that phone call.
Yeah. Well, I always like my I had a fourth grade teacher who was like, you know, she was very eccentric and, you know, she was, you know, have you said, you know, she had like long blonde hair and she was on her Jenny Craig or Weight Watchers program and she would tell the whole class, you know, which she fills in every day like, oh, we lost one.
Pretty much all F's, but the thing was she like liked me so much she wanted to keep me in the class
But she would have me right if I drop the pencil
If it's right down 10 times
I will not drop my pencil or my pen or like then I would give my signature forge and stuff like that like
autistic though
All right, but he's been through this Denison. I'm pretty sure you've been through this when you correct your teacher's mistake when they try to
Something and then that teacher wants to be mad at you because you corrected them on say a mathematical equation that they were wrong
Yeah, I'm the third literally happened to me in the second
Did me after that you're my teacher you should be proud that I did a good job
Well, yeah
Nobody likes to be like corrected by a kid especially it's about a grammar and stuff grammar and things people live
Youngest is correct in me on a few things and tell me a few facts because he's a high
Intellectual function autism and maybe you're just maybe maybe you just don't know enough
The kid knows this kid could be a fucking professor and shit. Yeah
Some people's brain
Like like I ain't gonna lie to you ghost. Yeah, sometimes he makes me feel stupid
But I take pride in that you sound like that
That's what I've raised. You know if he's gonna be that type person to have a higher intellect than most of society
Okay, what are you talking about?
Who's the next good time?
What do you mean? Are you talking about me?
And like, why are you...
It's gonna let me... Okay.
I'm not sure what you're talking about.
Oh, our poor teacher broke a rib.
Oh, but I remember on Easter, though,
like, you know, I had forged
the signature in this, like, you know,
this book, this journal,
she had to take home and get signed.
I forged it, and then she had, like, shown it.
I haven't been trouble for that, but I got in trouble in school. I'd write 500 times. I will not forge my appearance even sure
Well, I used to hate that I never have again. Did you have to do it on chalkboard too?
No, not like Bart Simpson. I just had to do it on piece of paper
But I remember we were on Easter it was on Easter and everyone else was out like doing the Easter egg hunt and I was like alone
Right doing that for hours. It was very bad. My hair you needed. Oh, okay. Hold on
Oh, yeah, my hair is like a good good time. Oh, no, I do need to you know, I don't want to be a hippie
I don't like it. I don't care for hippies too much
I mean, you are a hippie you smoke. I'm not a hippie. Yeah, hold on. You smoke weed. You're into spiritual things
I mean you you got long hair. I mean your free spirit it
What the fuck is not hippie about you psyche?
I'm very, I'm more, I'm kind of like economically conservative, I'm more like socially liberal, I'm like a libertarian, so I'm not very political, what's wrong with hippies, nothing's wrong with hippies, it's just like, you know, it's like, they're like, kind of like...
The hippies were very political, I mean, they were anti-political.
Yeah, I mean they were also like a lot of like, you know these non-conformists that just like, you know kind of like like
You know
In peace which you're about yeah
But didn't they like a lot of them would like leave their families like say oh you're the you're the man or you're like
You know trying to let you know they would you know
Want to be rebellious and it's like just Charlie Charles Manson's girls
He came from very good families, you know, they're just bored with their life and they wanted some crazy excitement
The Manson family yeah, the Manson
There's that there's really hey, really and the Manson family
Manson murder family. Yeah
Oh, yeah
That's the one you're talking about they got interviews of her like during her interrogations stuff
Yeah, probably like Patricia friend with friend Winkle and you know all this text Watson was one of that thing
Yeah, there's there's a bunch of I think one was just paroled
Actually is now out of prison. They've actually never you know tells man to never did any
Yeah, but yeah, but he did I think spend most of his life in prison
It's interesting how much how mind control is so powerful and like some people are responsible for
Mind control of other people sometimes and sometimes they're not held responsible
So if I just remember there's send us more to the story than you see I right
And the scary thing about people like Charles Mance and there's sometimes you know
It's the insane rambling but every once in a while is the viewpoints that they make that you're like
Oh, that's scary because that made sense
Well, yeah, I mean, he has, you know, he was the kind of a musician kind of type, and
so musicians, they can kind of have that abstract, you know, that abstract, and there's also
being a lot of drugs.
He's also working with the CIA and stuff through these prison programs, and he was being financed
to grow up and down from San Francisco to Los Angeles.
You had a question at the CIA is a cult a lot of activity
CIA like C is like seeing and then I like the eye and then a like all so all seeing I I don't know
Maybe there's a similar. I'm not sure
When it comes to the CIA a lot of their operatives, right? Yeah
Well, this is like a part of the cults
Yeah, oh, yeah, let's let's yeah, and that's sure there's and there's been story about that. We've been careful. Let's not even talk
Let's not let's not mention the new government agencies. I don't want to you know, I'm sure there are a
Lot of government people here and stuff like that's fine, but
People gonna be here regardless. I'm on right domestic terror watch list. Yeah. No, no, no, no. Yeah, but you're gonna watch this
I was like, you know, I've been on a watch list since like the early 2000s. It's okay guys. It's okay because you know
Guys, are we are we killing anybody are we hurting anybody? No, please please watch please watch me
Miguel says prairie. Good morning. Oh, that's sweet. Here we go. Oh my god. How are you? Hey easy?
Barbara came on to Barbara came on. Hey, what's up, Nancy? Yeah, Barbara
Barbara's
Nancy, yeah, we have but we do have I did add a few more mods. I think we're kind of almost getting back to the
The old monster, you know, but I just need to know I just want to make sure people like you know
I talked to the people I know the first time I just had so many people I didn't really know and I just
start over and
So thank you make a situation of I'll make like you make a picture of Barbara. Okay, it's Barbara on the panel
The home I can't really see Barbara that well home. Here's goes again. I'm Barbara. If you want to come on the panel
I'll draw you no problem. Anyone who gonna
Come on. Let me see. I do kind of see your picture. I don't know. I don't know. I'm
Yeah, it's kind of hard
There we go. I do. Oh, yeah, it's here. Oh, you're lovely Barbara
Okay, I can probably draw from that. Okay, I'll try I'll try
I can I'll draw you next to Nick Johnson. Okay, the page next to Nick Johnson. Okay, let's see far over and we stick with that picture
Okay
Hey site can you guys see come up
Marseille come on
Yeah, you feel like coming up sweet. That'd be great Marcy. We're having seven nice little chat
Oh, I'm just drawing some photos too. Okay, so I think I got oh, well getting along
Uh, they smile. Okay, huh?
Okay, there. Okay, and I
Take note. There's like, it's not, I don't do caricatures
So, but it's like, I'm trying to exaggerate
Um, let's see. It's just, I'm not the best
I mean, I'm, I'm, uh, hold on, my gosh, your hair. Hold on. I need to make it a little more. Okay. There we go
There we go. Okay. Oh perfect
Look like you earrings. Hold on
Okay, and then
Barbara all this right Babs, okay
Cuz I don't have really room okay when I see a Barbara. Hold on guys. Are you ready? This was a quick one, but there she is
Babs they're good. What do you think?
I'll try to fix there. Oh my god. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I know it
Hold on. I'll start hearts on it here. There you go
hearts and star, okay
You got hearts in a star. Isn't that cool? I'll give you like a little beat a V neck
Okay, how'd everyone react to that?
Sorry guys, there we go
That was a fast one. You liked it. It's cute. Okay. I just made her look at oh, I'm sorry
Ah
Some of my art is
What the drawing is horrible. Oh my gosh, guys, everyone's a critic, okay?
Everyone's a critic. There's people that have art where they literally just like, you know
Splatter diarrhea on the wall and they they sold it for money and then so and I can't I
Can't draw and you see it's horrible. I mean come on
Artists there are you know how much art is worth it's however, however the person's willing to pay for it
The but yeah, I mean it's not the best
Did you say caricatures I?
Yeah, I said I don't so I really I don't try to make care like the caricatures
I don't try to make it like exaggerated, but sometimes it does
My exaggerate like you know beat like beat is kind of looks like that like God
Oh
Christine's came out Christine kind of looks like you know, I don't know. I heard I made her eyes like an alien
I like I just like I thought I thought her eyes were kind of like he's mysterious and then
I think my smile my smiles do like like bananas. I don't I don't know I need to work on that
Christine's looks like that one
I didn't beat her
Just shared something it'd be nice for signal is called urine therapy
You're in therapy, I don't know
Well
See anyone this one on 98 fiance they had this woman and she went to you know
She married this guy from a brahman family in India basically the highest castin India
So there you know these wealthy Indian family and she goes there and they expect her to start learning the
Wifely duties or whatever so she goes in and then the mom comes and she's like oh, we're gonna bless the room
And so she takes that this bottle of
Cal year and she starts pouring it all like all over the windows. I'm in the doorway and
The woman's like oh my god
They've got it put it everywhere. It's mostly they has a sanitary. They got it's like a
It does have a
Aniseptic or something guys. I'm not sure but these in an Ayurvedic medicine some people drink it like a little bit
I mean
I don't know if it's good for the elder back. I just
think it's kind of like us to smoke weed like weed to us. We like the smell being weed smokers,
but everybody else it smells horrible like a skunk. Like maybe to those people the urine
smell and taste. No, I don't think I can't imagine it does. I mean, even the guy that
discovered phosphorus, he was like this sciences, he was just collecting his pee and it's like
crystal that would catch on fire. I mean it's like, it is some powerful, you know,
they have this element called, what is it, what is that, the phosphorus. Phosphorus
is in urine, so the guy discovered it. He actually was just like, probably like a
guy like Sig or, you know, Mr. Bigpipes, you just, he just collected big jugs of his
I mean, somebody, one day he woke up and he said,
oh, science happened, you know?
But I don't know if that will happen with them.
I mean, it's already been discovered.
I don't know.
I mean, because before I ever smoked marijuana,
I'd smell my stepdad smoking it.
I'd be like, God, that smells so horrible.
How could anybody ever?
And now that I'm older and I smoke weed,
I've been smoking weed since you go,
I don't need to go there.
But the thing is ever since I started smoking weed,
I mean, it smells good and tastes good to me now.
Yeah.
Well, it's like it's almost like I'm cheese in Asia like you know in China. They don't
I need to be asked to say these questions like how does
I've I've kicked off the panel. I do not want to hear the answers questions. It doesn't it doesn't taste good
I mean it's like okay. It doesn't taste good. I don't say depends on how the consistency of it, but
It's not a purpose, not a purpose, you know.
We'll see that in our counting.
Everybody has the time when we...
It's a voluntary thing to psych your mind into thinking it's...
No, I would not, yeah, I would not.
If the people think it's dimble full and they go,
it just seems to me like it's...
Wait, it's just basically like a salty...
I don't know.
We're so engaged in the subject, like right now.
I'm sorry. I forgot about it. I mean, I didn't want to talk about what said was up here
But then I seen another creator drop. So yeah, you're in there. Oh, so I'm like, yeah
I'm starting to get curious. No, but my point was in Asia and like China
In China they don't
They don't really like it. They think cheese smells like rotten feet like the feet and stuff like that
But we love it, you know, it's like we like the foot smell and like we'd like cheese
But so it's like there's different kind of taste but they also eat the the gooey duck and stuff like that and uh, yeah
It might just be a psychology thing easy wants the link the link isn't the link the link should be panned
I think the link is panned. I don't know. I didn't like it. Where's my phone? I think the link is panned
Is it link pain guys?
the
Chad don't pay attention to this. We don't pay attention to the chat. I
Don't have a sock. I don't even wear that. I don't either. I mean I have some
I
We're broken stuff definitely matters. It's like they're kind of like kids doing their own thing. They don't want us fucking with them
We're like doing our own thing up here, too. I guess in a long ways, right?
Yeah arguing with Barbara when she dropped the link of what okay, I see you can start
Stop bullying
Barbara Barbara and easy. Oh my gosh. I've got Barbara and easier mortal enemies. Oh my gosh guys
We can't have another feud in the chat guys at the cranes the wild
I was thinking it was alex that was beefing with barbara. So so it's easy. He's the one that hates. Oh my god
I mean it's the guy they it's so against it's so complicated. I mean, there's just a million relationships
And think about all the individual relationships and all the group relationship. I mean, it's just it's
because it's a group that's kind of you could do a documentary on this shit and believe it
even got enough footage to do so. I'm trying to write a book to do it. I'm trying to write a book
you know and be called my side by oh Jesus I mean uh what was it called? I had to rewrite
Dennis's character though after the other day. I didn't like Dennis's character but after I learned
some more deep shit the other day I'm like oh maybe I pretty judged and I was wrong.
Denvian they troll and you troll and trolling won't you speak at once you stoke accounts is the internet bitch
You don't like it. I get off. Okay. Yeah, I write by myself. Yeah. Well, no. Yeah, Jamie, right there's something
It's good to have you know people have your back to your phone. We have mostly I think most hated bloggers here
How long I think this most hated one second
one second
Oh, oh, yeah, hold on
Hello
Okay, I got you. What's up easy? Who you talking to you?
Hey, you gotta turn your mic up a little easy your mic is hella low, bro
That's how I like it cuz I when I start yelling I sound normal. Oh
My god, you know what there's nobody's gonna make you yell up here right now turn the mic up, sir
But no, I didn't say props to you the other day for hold that conversation you had cuz other than me
I don't see nobody standing up to anything over there the day you hold the issue with
They kind of hide corners over there. He blocked me for it
They did that's see that's that bitch move shit. Yeah
Yeah, I suppose
Chose line
She'd be mad cuz she you know, do you know to deal with me and Barbara? I didn't like somebody like say say
I don't like you psyche and I start arguing with you. She chose a side and ever since then she'd been trolling me
Who cares what psychiatrists right on windows
I bet you're back, easy, troll her back,
troll her until she loses her shit insanely.
Like, you're on the panel,
you have more power than you do.
The middle finger guy.
Okay, easy, easy.
You just have to not read the chat.
Fancy.
So just say you don't have garments,
just going back to the thing,
you don't have a green room.
Yes, I know it's not a real green room.
Yes, that's not an actual green room.
Ghosts, but, you know, it's just.
You just noticed that now,
that's been there for like an hour and a half.
the
So
Thank you, hold on
Because what she's trying to say is my jokes is is bullying us so I like joking on people
I call her which you be rich or whatever the case because I Afro
So she
Barbara are you serious? I think I really it's like those better not to have like
I'm a big foreheaded witch with creepy alien hands that shuffles too much if it's too nice so it's all good for her but you're fine.
Look at it like this easy. On this platform everybody needs that one top up. You know who your one top up is.
Yeah
Why are you why are you laughing like it's me for something like that?
I don't know you're like this is true everybody's got the one person today
Well, I wait you guys hate me
Understanding listen
That's beautiful respect beautiful in this game
You know what? You think you're outspoken and you know people might take you the wrong way
But you're harmless too. Like, you know what? I mean, it's just a misunderstanding if anything
Well, I mean it's a I mean, I would like not want to cross him in a dark alley at night, but uh
On the panel and expose they pass just because you hate them
You should no one should be doing nothing like that
Drop the link drop the link you stupid bitch drop it again. Drop it again. You stupid old witch
You're pretty young witch
Everyone's having fun. Everyone's having fun. Yes, like the Wizard of Oz says, only bad witches are ugly, only bad witches are ugly,
witches are beautiful.
Right, so I know we took it was good. Which is right. My first girlfriend was a witch
Everybody's got that one person. We're sure we got you got that one person
You really can't stand to see your chat and they always come here to fuck with you
Well, I've gotten those people that that's what yeah, that's what the fanings for it. They bother me too much
I don't have to deal with them. Yeah, or it's like the toxic relationships
I usually give that person a wrench with everybody else
Well, that's like, I mean, that's not maybe it's maybe not the best strategy that that was my strategy is
giving everyone a wrench of person and bringing trolls here and it turns into like some of them are
actually like kind of not very nice.
It turns into anarchy.
Yeah, it's like, I don't want to, you know, it's like, I'm trying to like
Have this a free chat as much as possible, but it's like I don't want to have like people like being political stances or
trying to make a show
To their agenda and really gonna protect the show and you know, it'll be my show and people don't like it
You don't have to be here, but it's like I think people do like it
I don't know that if my opp is in my room. They're still supporting me and then
I always got ops like Gotti's up Gotti's an enemy Gotti's one of them
I got it's not that bad of a dude though. He's a douchebag though. I know he hates
What they do what they do when you're not around like, you know in regards to that's when that's like the that's the real like
Um, it's not it's a great way to prevent yeast infections. It's a it's a it's a it's probably prevent you know
We've been from being hospitalized every year. It's a prevent it prevents my I support ladies who do shriek our smell
Yeah, and so yeah
There's a lot of guys that kind of exemplified the
Deusion there and that's a good lady's keep a trim and if you stick their head up there
It's own rewards, you know
Yeah, wow
Yeah, you're so so found very
I sound with your hand did you spoon it up just now? I don't know, but yeah, you guys are just being inappropriate
Okay, yes, I have the deck I picked out
I mean, I think it's gonna be the Wizard of Oz, you know, the Wizard of Oz.
Oh, we're getting the Wizard of Oz, people, stop playing.
Yeah.
Wizard of Oz.
Did I?
Yeah.
Ten is then you're not fun or funny, and there's, I think there's like a lot of gas
lighting or something going on in this chat, and it's like, it's just not, um, it's not.
Oh, here we go.
There goes all my haters popping up.
Look, look, EZ's here, all the haters is popping up.
I'm telling you, I got haters.
Are you okay, so it's oh, hey
Why did you kick out why people feel bad for people like kick, but it's like
I feel like I get these I get these feelings
I burst I have a strong like empath I get these strong feelings of like
Um, yes, and everyone is like I get some negativity from I guess bad vibes
Can I get a morning reading?
Yeah, of course. I just stabbed myself in the fucking head
See I didn't I didn't want you to leave so I thought I'm going to read it
Look like your hand was ready to click off
What did Denison get kicked for?
Denison got kicked because he annoyed me.
But, you know, I can always bring him back to my pleasure.
I think he can sit backstage for right now.
I'm doing a quiet reading of the page and I don't need to hear his sarcastic comments.
Let's do our thing. Let's do a collaborate for him.
People like that.
Okay.
Although I'll go for not that energy for the first a few. Okay, so you got this queen of cuffs. Okay, so this is
This queen of cubs, you've actually grown up a little bit emotionally, you've come into more
controlled emotions. I'm just noticing, I noticed different things in the car. Now it looks like
it kind of stinks this kind of snake a little bit. I don't know if it's this car or something.
There's also, you take notice that the cup, the cup is very protected right there. So also,
like, you know, we're in cancer season, this could be a cat, this is like, you know, the womb,
Well that has a lid on it. I just noticed. Yeah, it has a lid. Yeah, so it's very protected and it has like little claws like like a
Crab shoot a little bit. Yeah, interesting. Yeah. Yeah, I want to look at that also
Look at look at things a couple ways because you know, you can see like faces and stuff
But you can see the normal picture, but you can also see like a little faces and stuff like that if you like
Yeah, look, so this is like, you know, so this is like coming forward. You're just make out
I don't know. I'm just gonna be with your wife or
Somebody in your business world, but you're just like seeing eye-to-eye with somebody. There's like, you know
This is like an equal cup of love being exchanged. You got
You're coming together on something maybe like having a cheers, you know, I think if it's meant to be this the sun is orchestrating
No, or the solar angel this like the lion. That's some lion power. It's like some kind of sun solar power
Okay, and I'll do a couple more for easy. Okay, so easy. It's like you just gonna have to stay balanced
So that's a you know that card is this card is this card is like, you know, there's ways to be emotional ways. There's gonna be
different ways, different things that happen, you're gonna need to stay balanced, and it's like keep your perspective, like look at things from different
perspectives, you know, side to side. Also, there's kind of serpentine-looking eyes right there. It's like, you know...
Yeah, I mean why is this serpent's gentle as tough? I think it's a saying okay
And finally we have the king of wands and so I think you're coming into this king of wands power
Where you're finally I think you're once you master the emotions you're gonna master the passion that will probably come
Come next and you're gonna be very very well rounded. Okay, and I think maybe that your wife is the queen of cups
Okay, so I hope you enjoyed that and that's your message
I have some more people to bring on the panel once that can I mean I'll bring this the guy back. I mean
Don't be mean to them. Hi Gauri. Hey, what's up? Good morning everybody
Well, yeah, did you guys have a sleep or do you guys
Five and a half hours
I was gonna nap I have to work later today, too
Well, I was a dad nab it dad nab it
I don't think I was eating quite yet, but...
Hmm.
Interesting things to make you good. Okay. I'll put a page on the
Personal one or is it just for everybody?
Yeah, she can't read nobody's cards without permission easy to blow your nose
Okay
Did you okay, so I understand that your communication I'm seeing that there has been definitely
Obviously this card says is it something about communication?
And I feel like there was kind of like a divide in the household because of it at some point
And I feel like it is starting to get better, but I feel like
Feel like there's still not as much effort that could be putting being put in by either one of the you and the other energy
Which probably is your wife. I'm going to assume
But I feel like you need to like cleanse the house to like maybe move the furniture
I just try something different and like try dating each other again
Like you should never stop dating your your partner or your your wife or your husband, you know
And that's kind of where we leave some of those things
But I'm really happy that you're working on the communication thing, but I feel like
There's deeper issues that also need to be addressed and it's not just surface level stuff
You're gonna keep falling back into that same pattern because we as humans, especially as couples always do that
We always fall back into an old way of that's comfortable
um
But I feel like you guys need to start dating again and like being spontaneous about it like throw something different out there
Be like don't even make a plan just grab her be like hey, we're gonna go
You can even fib to her but make it like
It's just like a funny vibe like hey, we're gonna go let's go do this
We have to go do this really quick and then like surprise her
Because you're gonna get really really really good feedback and like really good reciprocal energy like
Giving back to you
So she's gonna want to do cute things for you if you do cute things for her and sometimes after like a long time of being with
Somebody it feels like it can be lost
but
It's always you can always start a fire even in the rain. You just need the right you need dry wood
You need like you have to find the right things. It's a little more difficult to do
Right, it's not impossible
So don't get discouraged because you guys have one little spat because it's gonna be like, you know a couple steps forward
And then a couple steps back
But that's okay because you're still making progress because either way
You're learning every step no matter what and then that's why
There's there's just like there's an understanding because you guys love each other, but you have stopped being friends
You've kind of become roommates like most of us kind of get that way after a long time
and unfortunately if we don't nourish our relationship properly and
And or you know, it's just some connections just need a little bit more work than others
You know some of them are easier and that's okay. We don't have to compare it to everybody
We're just doing our own thing anyways, but when it comes to this it's like
She's really like
Opening up to like
Every little positive bit of attention that you guys give each other
It goes so much further than either of you even like acknowledge of each other or tell each other because the communications not there right now, you know
Remember what you fell in love with her for you need to go back to the basics is kind of what I'm hearing
You know just remember remember the woman or the girl or the lady that you fell in love with
You know don't look at her as you're nagging life
It's just you gotta have a different mindset. So refresh reset your energy your your mind
and like just kind of try to renew it it's they're showing me renewal like watering a plant, you know, that's
Desperate for a drink. Just give it just give it a little bit of love until see and don't be so short with your temper
And she won't be in retaliation and vice versa. Lovely. That was a good push. Okay, so anyways, that's without the cards
I'll just like to down
Welcome
Okay
Who's next we were one of morning reading who came up here?
I
Not no, I
Told you I was gonna pull you two cards to clarify all the shit. I just spit people like that
Eight of Michael you can be be free you make a courageous choice to change your situation
So that you see things a little bit more clearly
Plus I don't need it easy. I'm one of those people that are already aware including the fuck shit soon to come my way
So we have the Five of Raphael. So this is, everything happens for a reason.
So releasing a regret and embracing the opportunities for happiness and searching for the silver lining.
So those two cards alone just clarify everything I just said.
Pretty much in the order that I did. And I can pull another one and we can just have an outcome card,
but it's going to be probably what I said.
I hate when they do this, the car, so I don't hate it,
but it's like, then I just, it backs me,
but it also is just like repetitive.
Do you know what I mean?
You're the energy that's so well that you don't got it.
I think you passed the car level already.
Oh, I did but I you guys need visual proof most the time right because skepticism is a thing
I even touched my own gifts. All right, we have the lovers. What the fuck did we just talk about?
So making choices from the heart and deeply emotional commitments in the power of love. There you go easy peasy
That was beautiful
Thank you. You're welcome. And he said he said he said is gonna is gonna say what she was just talking about and did
Who's KT? You guys know KT?
KT is from my community and she's a supporter in some places and good in some places but
then you know each is own. They hate me too.
Why do they hate? Why does she hate Marcy?
She hates Marcy. She hates every female that's like this is what I witnessed. Every female
that became famous on internet she hates them.
That's not no later. She's gonna end up. Hey, what oh somebody up here?
I got news easy ain't none of us famous creators. I'm saying this room
That's why she hates Marcy. That's why she hates anybody that was famous on the other side. She hates them for no reason. Oh
You brought her here
She she follows probably follows I share psyches a lot
She's a member
Let me start complaining about people being here is a network system where you can network
No, no, no, no stop there. You can apply that to everything. It's the internet
Yeah
Oh, thank you. She's been a member for a month. And look, she said
Who's this who's the psychic why don't you uh ban easy demon inside? I he is a oh my gosh
He has pure evil your evil peasy
I
She hated me the same time on Barbara started hitting me. We're not we're not we're not in the light. They broke him all the guy
Yeah, my my my
What if she's my
My my
I'm gonna
I'm gonna pretend I'm gonna go outside her apartment and and and protect her building
Marcy's amazing. I love you Marcy. I'm not Marcy. I wouldn't do that. I don't do anything. We squash it. Oh, yeah
Let me show so so easy sure a demon. Let me just tell you is the power of Christ
I don't think it's like he's really demons demons demons really are not your humans should have
You can always we can always shoe them out. It's like I have a book. I read this book is called
It's called pigs in the parlor or something that is it's like and it's about how it makes a metaphor about how these demons are kind of like these
But pigs with steam is kind of if you're very negative you may be a little bit evil animals not to be eaten and stuff like that
And if you if pigs came into your house and started like making a big mess you would like you know drive them out immediately
We let demons
Yeah
Break it down easier than that
Uh, what demons are considered is a disembodied neflon which are the children uh the fallen angels
and if you believe in any of those writings then if you're human you're called forth
to judge the angels and their children so well it's like the angels kind of like have no
The angels have no free will because their will is God's will, so the difference between the angels and the humans is that the humans work in their free will.
That's a musical conception, because in one case Lucifer and another 200 wouldn't have failed.
No, well, it's like they will be felt by the reason
They wouldn't be connected to the physical realm right by
200 almost almost around the exact time
Falling of angels is a mount of craters on earth
There
I'm going to because he asked nicely, so I have permission
Yeah
Gotty gotty when you said that you said about the test I think that is a very interesting concept a bit
But if you know what if it is a test, but it's like
The test was like kind of like not
Who would have thought the test was I don't know what if the test is not good if the test is something else
Yeah, have you or the perfume for like ever like you I just came I can smell that it's like a
I can't pinpoint the smell if I must be one of my mom's perfumes when she was alive. So
You're very very much
You have nice energy. You're actually quite an elegant person and actually I feel like
People might take you the wrong way and I don't feel like it's just here
I feel like it's other places because you're very you're not serious, but like
Okay, I okay. This is the way that I'm gonna put it. I
Look like I'm not even approachable if I'm not smiling like I've resting bitch face
But I'm the night. I'm really nice like if you talk to me. They're like, oh, I don't know
I was so intimidated or scared. You know what I mean? It's like well, I just I don't mean it sometimes
It's just the way that my fucking face is. You know, I mean, it's just that's the way it rests, but I
Feel like also
You've just gone through something that was quite uncomfortable and I don't
Well, I'm not gonna get into it too personally, but I'm just gonna say and I'm sorry for what it
Sorry and everybody lay the fuck off right cuz you don't know what's going on with people. Okay, so
Just
Remember that you're wonderful, and I don't know why I need to tell you that and that you
It's okay to hurt alone, but sometimes it's okay to not be so strong
You don't have to be so strong all the time you can and and I don't know what's wearing you down
I mean it get life is wearing you down life is wearing everybody down
But life right now is just you feel like a little bit a little bit less Barbara E. You know
But you're finding ways to re
Yeah introduce yourself to
Yourself like I don't know if it's something about your inner child that needs to come in to play more
I don't know. It's it's very strange. Um
It's like all over the place a little bit
It's a little bit of everything that needs a little bit of like replenishment. Does that make sense?
Um, also, I think you need to just kind of watch
Maybe eat you mean need to watch your like don't just nourish yourself more take care of you
You need to worry about you were a lot you worry a lot about other people. I can see that in her energy guys
She's actually really quite a
She'd be a great mother. She'd be a great friend. So don't judge so quickly
So I'm just saying that you know, you need to make sure that your little buckets are being filled to sometimes and
Don't let anybody break your strength your stride ain't nobody gonna break my stride
I'm gonna keep on moving like you need to just keep dancing to your own the beat of your own drum
Like you always do
And the people that are leaving your lifer who have left were meant to go because they're not on your level anymore
You're up here, and they can't come with you until they're it's their time to ascend
Okay, and it does feel difficult, but you'll be okay. So anyways, you got big things to come in like the next two months
I do see like
Just see I don't know if you're going somewhere. I don't there's something about
Some going connecting reconnecting to a place or a memory or something you're connected to from like your inner child
It's like a nostalgia
They gave me a scent, and I thought it was your perfume, but like I'm not sure maybe you just need to
As you can you tell me to stop and smell the roses bar, but stop and smell the roses remember that they smell good
I don't know we get distracted when we're
When we're not like fuck our nervous systems. Have you ever seen them outside of a body? They look fucking nervous
So like that's that's creepy. That's what's going on inside of us all the time. It's never calm. So
And I don't know if you like to take bubble baths, but there's just something about just like a like an aromatic like small like just
Essence you're very um, you're very nice energy. Don't forget that
And this, ooh, okay, there you go.
There's your three.
Six of vario.
Material needs get fulfilled in magical
and unexpected ways.
Acts of kindness giving or receiving
with a grateful heart, can I just say.
And we have the Empress. This is you. This is the Empress energy
This is what I was just describing to you that you the essence of you, you know
it's like you always just time to act upon your plans and
Creativity comes with great reward and luxurious or abundant resources. So it's just a matter of
You have the resources
It's just get your butt in gear
You know you have to just want it as bad as universe wants you to have it and so the queen of Raphael
She's kind understanding giving and also a little bit psychic herself
So follow your heart a love of home and family and trustworthy psychic information. I
Think that that um
Well well
One more Barbara just one more. Oh, look at that
The page of Gabriel so energetic brave optimistic and playful did I not say the word playful when we started this reading?
So that note that's for me knows this is last card. I didn't say that correctly
I know that this is now the last card
So follow your passion. You are ready for any challenge opportunities for excitement and adventure. There you go my girl
I hoped that that, I didn't even read to see if it clarified, but I could be totally bogus.
Oh, you're welcome.
Thank you for letting me tap into your energy, it was a pleasure.
Jesus, somebody said they were sick.
Awful.
You ready? I should be strong.
Have I creeped you guys out enough yet?
The last couple days showing you what to do.
Hey, stop reading cards. Just fill it.
I need you. All you got to do is hold somebody's hand
or listen to their voice and...
Yeah.
You good?
You ain't got to read the cards.
There's no use.
It's just a...
like a set of visual things for certain people.
Yeah.
Give or roll the bones.
She could throw bones and still read that shit. I can divinate with anything. Yeah, it's not even I
Just see her just to see her, you know, I know her a seer feeler healer. It's a thing. It's a thing
Let's see what they say
Yeah, 20 minutes goes on you about easy
Jesus, I love y'all save money write my name write my name
Are you up in the top?
Geez, oh my god
No, that's okay, we can do that yikes for sure I'm sure okay psych we're gonna take see where the fuck is my guy where'd he go?
Taking a shit about he's sleeping psych
You have to take a dump sometimes, you know, well then like let us know when you're going to get down
Don't just leave like yes, I'm right. I'm right here. What? Yes, I tell you wow
Thank you
Like I'm not leaving or I'm leaving. I drow. I'm just sharing the fuck up. I'm right now. I was I was living page
Okay, I was just you know
Like can you pull some cards for yikes, and I'll do it as well. I feel like when it's people. Yeah, very often
It's nice to give them the yeah, yeah, but it's your channel, and you're also a wonderful reader
Yeah, and I want to thanks and Patrick also. Thank you Patrick for the super chance during the day
Um, it's been really very generous, and I appreciate it. Thank you very much
Mwah Mwah, okay
My god
God he sent you a kiss
I'm going to give you a Hershey's kiss.
I give him a fist kiss.
You're not going to give him a Hershey's kiss.
A couple of those guys.
Okay, injuries, guys.
I know Barbara.
Okay.
Okay. Okay. Okay. So you have this like, okay, so we're reading this for their name is
Yikes
Yikes, we got first you got this ace of pentacles for you. So there's some kind of like recently some kind of new
opportunities some kind of
unexpected unexpected bonus or
Some kind of see the energy from the divine. This is how you can grow something very powerful
Oh, hold on, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got
You're in a relationship or somebody or it's gonna be a new business partnership
It could be something related to that that business partnership. It looks like they're doing in Cheers
We're going together and pouring this like one. It's kind of like if you'll make it similar right a little bit
and I would say that so coming together with somebody with this new opportunity and
Seeing eye to eye on that and yikes. I also have this temperance card the temperance card is, you know, they're kind of like
This is the Slots Manchettes, Ursula's, you know, her eel henchmen and they were kind
of like the yin and yang, they kind of, but they were kind of in trouble, you know, and
so you need to, you know, kind of tame these more wild energies and, you know, make them
into, you know, tame them into more immanageable pets and the advice is going to be the six
of swords.
Six of swords, it says keep your guard up, you know, you're there with your cat and you've
got your little home alarm system or whatever, you got your, you know, you know, home alone,
I don't know. I don't know what you got set up. You got some kind of security. You got some kind of guarding, guarding and protecting yourself and your loved ones. Okay, cats happy even though they're villains, but you know, they're not bad people.
I don't want to interrupt you, man. You got something on your forehead. You got some shit on your forehead.
Oh, my God.
Is that shit?
Yeah, sorry, bro. I didn't think you wanted it there. It's okay. I don't know
It's from the
Yeah, unfortunately the guy
What's that
I'm not quite I'm a fight. Oh page you something to their page. You're some on your
That's it right there you got it you got it
Second time you did that to me. No, it's actually like the fourth time
Okay, oh the chair's gotta go
My cheeks hurt
Well, okay, just stand up again your circulation. Oh your other cheek. I'm sorry
Okay, so how I cause
You got a you got a bong I just quick question you got a bong
No, I do but I don't like I haven't used it since like 1910
But you got to bring you got to bring it back out and bring back the bong
Yeah, I would like to see even if you don't use it
What's it look like? I don't know where the fuck it is. Just like
How about I think it's in the shed which is outside and I have to walk through spider. Describe it. What's it look like?
It's like yellow. It wasn't okay. It was my act like my ex who'd left just was saying his sister
She was going through cancer treatment and she had this bong
And because I got rid of all my and like after I graduated high school pretty much so anyways
And I used to have one you guys I had a hole with my feet
But I used to belong queen I did but not anymore anyways and Cory passed away
And so she I and I got all her like we'd paraphernalia
She gave it to me before she passed away like she was whatever and so I have it
But it's like this rubbery like silicone. It's not you can't break it like if you can drop it
Can burn it it doesn't
Break or burn or whatever. It's can't tarnish. So I'll find it. I don't know if it's I
Think it's in the shed, which is now. I'm not going out there right now, but I'll find it
Yeah, I thought that page I just don't use it
I just like they become a pre-roll queen because fucking pre-roll princess cuz I I think you pretty much described it those
Bongs are pretty basic looking. Yeah, it's not fancy
I know I used to have a bong that had like dice in the bottom of it like I just have some really cool ones, but 40 bucks
It was probably like 40 bucks
Patrick wants to know how much to get rid of me 40 bucks right now
Forty bucks to get rid of you forty bucks. Oh
Oh, hey, you got it
Okay, just he ruined the mafia he ruined the mafia
Yeah, he kept talking to the press
No, no assholes 24
Whoa, ah
was that that's too cheap that that's what I was thinking like how long that should only be like
20 minutes yeah how long is this kick for
this and how long is the kick for I don't know who wants to kick you who's wants to he said
he said how much to kick him forever oh kick from the panel for 24 hours for 25
Oh, yeah, that's a hell of a deal
Yeah, that's short sale. What is it boxing day sales or what?
Okay, that was a terrible joke. Yeah, he had nobody outside of Canada got that
I
Thought I was talking but I wasn't on the panel. Yeah, you know, I know it was I did post this that says
You know for 24 hours that that was the price and so it's not a live-same band. It'll be less
I'll probably do 20 out. You know, he didn't you know, is that okay 20 hours? I think that
Your donator
Pay up Bob this guy chef pay up KT
Pay up. Um, charisma. Y'all want me gone pay up stop talking shit in the chat
But thank you so much for the super super chat is so cool here. There you go. I'll put myself
There we go off the next day easy. Okay. Yikes. I'm gonna give you what I got I suppose. Um, okay. Oh, here
Yeah, so
Good get it out. What is it?
Well, he made me big screen. I was gonna do it. I was gonna do a read-in
Call me now for your free read-in
Well, you know what? How about you give me a reading when I'm done?
Yeah, I don't have any cards. Is that okay? Okay, you don't need cards. I don't need your heart. Yeah, we don't need a card
Okay, okay
Okay
Good night, Gotti
We'll see it. We'll see you tomorrow tomorrow tomorrow. We know the time
Yes, he did we got a $20 super chat from Patrick. Thank you so much Patrick for $20 super chat
You know, it'll be the you know, we'd less than a 24-hour period
Then we'd love you guys, you know, you know, you know, I would hope it would be a less than that
Oh, yeah, I have to make sure you know how I feel about the people buying
I know human trafficking well. No, no, no, no, no, no, it's not
$20 super chat which is super chat. They take roughly 40%
It is like also, you know, it's good to use their monetization. So hello
Pat oh Patrick are you there? Oh Patrick is here. Oh, hold on a second Patrick is here
And she's here Patrick are you there? He's talking away. I know it's near your audience
You're muted
He looks like he's trying to warn us all about Armageddon right now
Hello, can you mute the guy every once and just me and you were talking do you mute?
Yeah, okay
If you go back I'll say how much I want this guy out forever
Now all these other people talking trying to make up a deal. It was me. No
It's your screen. Yeah, it's my attention, but so what I said is like I said
I said you can make an offer and like there's no like deal made and then I posted
my normal thing is 24 hours for
I post it right here. I posted right here, sir, but now you're changing up
When I posted it right here, sir. I posted it right here. I posted it right here
I'll post you where I posted it right here. I posted it right when you said
I did it before I did it before I swear I swear to God
Don't I don't
$5 shut the hell up and a lot of people have
Everybody except for me and you cuz they're trying to fucking talk and it's just me and you between me and you okay
Okay, well, okay, so listen everyone just a quiet private private second. I don't want to kick everyone off the show
Just okay. Oh, okay. Oh, yeah, so I'm gonna fend it guys. I'm just gonna mute everybody don't be offended
I just you know, you can unmute. Yeah. Thank you for breathing. Oh, thank you and thank you. Okay. Okay. Let's okay
Well, now it's okay. It's you and I think we're alone now. Okay. Oh
Nothing that if you ain't my point is I wouldn't give you nothing if you was only doing it for 24 hours
This fuck the motherfucker. I want any more forever
I know I know but well, it's too fucking late, huh? Okay. Yeah, I did I did I did he unmuted himself
You know, I did I know one time I accepted the $50 for a lifetime ban for somebody and then that's for Alex
And I ended up you know letting him back on and it was a whole fiasco
I tried so I do like I have since then I've been very
Strict with my like $25 for 24 hours. And so as soon as you said it I typed kick and I think I think I'm odd or someone can
Clarify I did it and then you it's the second you have sent that and so I was saying okay
Well, it is a little bit less than like the $25 for 24 hours, but I'll you know, it's it
Because it's only ours if you want to you didn't take before I kicked the 20. I believe I did guys
I put it on the screen too before before you actually you said that very soon after I posted on the screen
But I did post it on the screen. You can go back and see that
Not before I put the 20
Yeah
It was because I know I typed I typed kick and then it then when I type kick it types it says 24 $25 for 24 hours
Now he saw it
Well, oh T
O.T., hold it down, hold it down, hold it down.
First of all, when I first asked, right, hold on,
I'm going to break it down right, I'm going to break it down right.
When you first asked, God, he said something about it.
And God, he said, it's $25.
You dropped $20 in the thing.
That's not our fault.
He said it, he said it.
You've been God, he said it, like, oh yeah, $25 to kick me.
Okay, okay, so
Okay, let me say so the conversation went and I'm we're talking I said you said how much
Block Goddy forever and I said I said feel free to make an offer and then you said I mean right now
You said $20 and then someone said
He's Gotti's dream boy, and then I said I typed kick when I type kick it says the nightbot comes up
It says kick someone from the panel 25 dollars for 24 hours
Then I see and that was a few messages before the super chat came in so I did say that before the super chat was sent
Okay, so I'm just I'm just saying I'm not it's all in the up-and-up. I was like it is you know
I'm sorry. There's this understanding, you know, I I
I want to well, let me tell you something it takes a minute for that 20 to post so that could have been
Takes a second
If I post another $30 you'll kick him for that'll be 50 that'll kick him for life
I mean, it won't be lifetime. It will be you know, it will be
You know a little longer. We have to you. Yeah, well tell me how much longer
Well, I see what days it's Wednesday about that other this up where we're fucking clown
I think it's the same as that's gonna be I think it's gonna be $25.24 hours
And if it's like you want to double up on days and everything, but that's I think that's the thing where I raise
How much to buy gotty back it's okay. No guy well Gotti can buy himself
I have to refund so I do 25. I have to refund the $20 to
No, you don't give him a refund if I have to pay to buy him back
Yeah
all I think I would have said you said everybody's broke or sippy it's up here let's see where you're
well let me see you do it let's go back and forth let's go back and forth
I said I didn't say no refunds then
I said where will it do it
no it's 25 to ban 50 to buy back
what would help you creep
or no it's 25 to block
He's paid 20 to ban. I'm gonna pay 25 to bring him back. And it's a
Superchats are also a different system basically like, you know, I usually like prefer to catch up
No, you can't it'd be 50 it'd be 50
Put it up or shut up.
OK.
He got to make some money out of it.
The man's got to make some money.
It's a capitalist country. You dumb you bunch of socialist bums
I
Know but there's a guy to be guys
Lost the mouse key the
Hey, hey, Patrick Peter wants to talk to you for the page is the voice of reason in the chat page go ahead
Please have this
Make this better for you, sir
Get gaudy gaudy dies right now and that guy the werewolf guy both dropped you with a fucker jacket off in the back stage
It was you that's a fucking lie. He's
There's scumbags and liars
There's not a real back state
Listen JT
This guy didn't lose his legs to some Chinaman so that you could sit around here on this panel
Guys, let's all pieces
Hey, I don't know pages writing notes about me
I'll be good page. I promise already got rid of the other goof evening for five minutes get them just get them
That motherfucker disappeared forever. That's what makes me happy.
I
So I can buy back Goddie for 25 right
Why does he get to ban him for 20 and I have to pay 50 to get a head because
I refund him his 20
No, you don't refund the 20. That's not how that works
If you refund him the 20 then he didn't pay to have him banned so then you just bring Goddie back for free
No, because the people that's with Alex
Okay, yeah
Like I keep it simple. It's like we're doing no response. Oh, okay. Who's Michael night. Let's say sick. Let's say no refunds
Oh my god. Yeah, that doesn't make any sense whatsoever. No fuck refunds. I can't I don't know
that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that
Well, I mean, I really I don't want to I don't want to be like, you know, it's like
Big deal Alice Alice
Alice paid what he was paid to be blocked and then he got blocks again
He paid I think he paid to get unblocked. He didn't pay like a hundred dollars. I mean he yeah, and so you know
I it's like, you know, it was crazy and that's crazy
But uh, then he did he did he the next day he like started yelling at me and they got me on matter
So it's like I don't know it's like I've been with some
I don't know. He's a little bit a little bit. I pull her a little bit, but I love you Oz. I love you Oz.
But tonight a kickoff game, Psyche. You want the kickoff game to be enticing to people to keep the money flowing.
So if he pays 20, somebody else pays 25. It'll get you confused. It'll get you confused. It'll get you confused.
on the show we're going to do evil spirits or evil sutra.
Psyche.
Evil sutra.
told me psyche you told me that if I sent you a picture of my dick fully hard
You would not ban me anymore, and you keep you never said it you never sense it you never sense it
That was a picture of
No, it was it was a picture
You're putting a pickle through your gene it was purple and and had warts all over or green and it looked strange
I win, I win, God is gone, God is gone, God is gone.
KT
My boys lost without his fucking buddy his homo buddy
How much money to kick mr. Iki bono off the panel
For 24
Weenies! Weenies!
Guy you could tell this... Hey, hey, you know I wish I was an Oscar Meyer wiener
That is
If I were Oscar Mayer
I'm with the refund system like and I was a refund that was I mean on cash app
I mean, it's like I really cannot refund the super chats because I don't there's not a mechanism on YouTube for that
I mean, it's like I have to I put through cash up
I would just go the cursey if I didn't keep if I made a deal and then I didn't stick to the deal
I mean, it's like I have no problem with refunding, but it's like sometimes
There are misunderstandings. I just want to be
Okay, bye
Wolfman, I'll see you later. Wolfman. I love but it's you. You're a great guy though. Hey, thank you
This is all
Man, it's lazy. Oh no, hold on. Hold on. That was the wrong person. I'm sorry. He banned you. I'm sorry
They banned you. I bet I miss you bond, but I won't the old man said I could take any rug in the house
Thank you
You you want a free seat to the chat
Winner
Because I did get it I just got a I just got a nice
You know
I do have to I do I'm gonna be right back. I do have to just end the stream just to make sure you know
I just uh, I just want to make sure everything is cool with the stream and I'll be right also
I'll be right back. So guys just join join back. We're back. Okay, so we're leaving. Okay. Bye. We're back. We're right back
Love you guys